Chapter 752: Change in the Demon Race

If they hadn’t been in battle with the Divine Race, then the groups might have something to say. But now that they had experience, they knew that Zhao Hai made the right choice.

All of them understood that choosing the Elves would be the best choice when it came to resisting the Divine Race advance.

After seeing that nobody was in opposition, Zhao Hai turned to the Elf leader and said, “Noah, bring this potion back to your camp. Upgrade your strengths as soon as possible.”

Noah nodded, then he took the potion bottle before giving Zhao Hai a bow and leaving. Noah knew that the most important thing right was was to make the Elves break through, other things are irrelevant in comparison.

After Noah left the room, Zhao Hai looked at the others and said, “After the Elves gets promoted, the Dwarves will go next. Having the Dwarves get to 9th rank would provide us with more diversity in the battlefield. After the Dwarves would be the Beastmen and then the Humans after that. Don’t worry, I can assure all of you that there’s enough potions for everyone.”

The group nodded, then Zhao Hai continued, “Although the Divine Race has yet to attack, everyone still needs to be careful, especially the Dwarves. We’ll leave it up to you to make the ground under the city into a huge battlefield.”

Baker nodded, then Zhao Hai turned his head to the Beastmen representatives and said, “Have your mounted scouts investigate the surroundings as well. We wouldn’t want the Divine Race to know about our situation and decide to make a pre-emptive attack.”

The Beastmen nodded, then Zhao Hai looked at the Human commander and said, “You’re humanity’s most elite soldiers. Before you reach 9th rank, you can man the magic cannons for me. You should know that the magic cannons have limited uses, the same goes for the crystals as well. So you need to know when to fire. Behind you, there are 9th ranks working hard on charging the crystals. I want you to find ways to use the magic cannons in the most efficient way possible.”

The Human commander nodded. He was someone from the Rosen Empire, so he held great respect to Zhao Hai. He knew about Zhao Hai’s status inside the Rosen Emperor’s heart.

After discussing these things, Zhao Hai said, “If there’s anything you need, tell me, there’s no need to be polite. Baker, make your men drink less liquor, otherwise if you get drunk, then I’ll personally beat you up.”

Baker embarrassingly smiled and said, “Elder’s liquor is just too delicious. The Elder can feel relieved, we’ll control our drinking in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to the Beastmen and said, “Beastman Brothers, I know that you’ve taken a liking to eating green vegetables. But you cannot eat too much of it, or else you’ll get weak. I won’t stop giving you vegetables, but you should eat meat as well, understand?”

The beastmen bitterly smiled as the scratched their head and they nodded. Zhao Hai couldn’t blame these Beastmen, green vegetables were very rare to them. Before coming to the city, all of them were yearning of eating some. Now, it seems like these people had turned into Elves, exclusively eating green vegetables every day, causing many soldiers to suffer from diarrhea. Zhao Hai was just giving them warning.

After the taking care of all his matters, Zhao Hai concluded, “Alright, all of you head back, today’s matters end here. Make sure to explain our decision well, unity is very important for us.” The group nodded before they stood up and left.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath and then sat back on the chair. Shue stood by Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, will sending Beastman scouts really be useful?”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Not really, but you must think about balance. Only after the Beastmen reach 9th rank can they display their strength. If we don’t have them do anything, they might think that they’re useless. That wouldn’t be great for their morale. We need to keep them satisfied before they reach 9th ranks and show their usefulness.”

Shue nodded and didn’t speak anymore. He understood firsthand how Zhao Hai was very busy. Not only did he need to think about the Demons and the Divine Race, he needed to keep the balance on all races as well. This would ensure that the Continent would keep its peace, this wasn’t an easy matter.

Zhao Hai turned his head to Shue and said, “The dead raging bulls, have they been handed over to the Beastmen?”

In the previous battle, Zhao Hai released large quantities of raging bulls to deal with the Divine Race’s heavy cavalry. This caused raging bull losses that numbered in the hundred thousands. Zhao Hai didn’t turn these raging bulls into undead, instead, he gave them to the Beastmen to process. Although the raging bull meat couldn’t compare to potions, they can still improve the strength and defense to those who ate it. Moreover, their skins can also be turned into leather armor, providing additional defense. At the same time, their bones can become long distance weapons for the beastmen. Not only were the bones hard, they were quite heavy as well. In the hands of the Beastmen, they would definitely turned into great weapons.

One could say that when it came to using iron to make weapons and armor, the Dwarves would come on top. On the other hand, when it came to leather armor, the Dwarves were actually inferior to the Beastmen. Almost every Beastman wore leather armor, and these were all made from beast skins. Leather armor made by the Beastmen weren’t only defensively strong, they were quite comfortable to wear as well.

Shue nodded and said, “Young Master can feel relieved, it has been handed over to the Beast King. He would definitely be able to process them properly.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Give some blood lightning beads to the Beast King as well. Have them make weapons that can launch these beads for a long distance. This way, we can provide more blood lightning beads to the Beastmen.”

Shue nodded. He knew that Zhao Hai would tell these matters to Laura, the only reason he was told about it was because Zhao Hai needed help. If Zhao Hai forgot about this, then Shue can remind him.

At this moment, Berry looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you must help the Dwarves develop these kinds of weapons as well. The Dwarves’ long range abilities are just too weak.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he was aware of this issue. He had always wanted the Dwarves to be able to effectively use the blood lightning beads, he just couldn’t think of any way.

He thought for a while, he really couldn’t think of any material that was able to accomplish it, so he couldn’t help but stop his thoughts and turned to Shue, “Shue, after heading back, tell Patriarch Billy about this situation, make them try to find a solution. Right, tell them that the blood lightning beads are quite unstable, they couldn’t undergo strong impacts and vibrations.”

Shue nodded, then Zhao Hai looked at the skies outside the city lord’s mansion before they returned to the Space. After arriving, Shue immediately processed the things that he needed to do. At the same time, Berry and Zhao Hai went to the Processing Machine to take a look, then they returned to the villa.

In less than two days, the tiny pagoda would finish its upgrade. Zhao Hai didn’t know what would happen after the tiny pagoda gets upgraded, but he was certain that it wouldn’t be weak.

At this point, the potion materials in the Space can be produced fast enough to make God-ranked potions nonstop. When these potions gets made, Zhao Hai would make Shun use it first. After Shun reaches God-rank, Zhao Hai would then proceed to promote others.

Zhao Hai was now hoping that the materials in the ten magic backgrounds become produced as soon as possible. When that happens, Zhao Hai would be able to bring up a lot of God-rank Experts. As long as they have an army of God-ranks, then even if the Ark Continent couldn’t expel the Demons and the Divine Race, they could still manage defend the continent with no problems.

While sitting inside the Space, Zhao Hai turned the monitor on, looking at the Divine Race and the Demons. The two parties were also busily making their barracks and city.

The Divine Race had turned the cities of the Radiant Empire into military barracks. Magic cannons were arranged on the city walls, patrols could even be seen from time to time.

At this time, Laura and the others walked over. They just came back from dealing with Zhao Hai’s matters. At this time, those who were extremely wounded and disabled in the city have been sent away. Having these people return to the continent would also make a great impact.

The various groups had dispatched their elite, but they were still hard pressed to defend against the Divine Race and have been injured to this level. If Zhao Hai was not present, then they might not have survived.

The people in the continent were now looking at the Divine Race in horror, but Zhao Hai didn’t mind it. The Demons and the Divine Race were truly horrible, however, the people in the continent have never truly realized to what extent. Zhao Hai also didn’t want them to have any misconceptions.

This misconception was about Zhao Hai’s capabilities. Since he could block both the Divine Race and the Demons almost single handedly, people might think that the threat was no big deal. If Zhao Hai didn’t show them, then they might not know how strong Zhao Hai was.

Now that the injured soldiers had returned, they were able to tell the others about how fierce Zhao Hai was. Zhao Hai had shown strength capable of toppling any Empire and race in the continent. This kind of strength was simply unimaginable in the past.

At the same time, since the injured soldiers weren’t a lot, their testimonies wouldn’t raise too much disturbance in the continent.

Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to pay attention to any of these right now. There was a change on the Demon side. Their army had now reached 20 million, moreover, their God-rank experts had numbered to thirty thousand. And since they didn’t have enough space like the Divine Race, they were now covetously eyeing Rising Sun City.

Chapter 753: Talents Needed To Be Kept

Zhao Hai was currently standing on the wall of Rising Sun City, listening to Besmir’s report. Besmir wasn’t doing anything in the city right now. Currently, outside the city was a huge underground area dug out by the Dwarves. Retreat tunnels had also been dug for easy escape whenever things go wrong.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t stingy when it came to Rising Sun City. At this point, all of the troops in the city, whether they be Humans or not, had become 9th rank experts. Even the Elephant Beastmen were turned into 9th ranks. After all, Zhao Hai took care of this city much earlier compared to Upper Bank City.

During the start of Zhao Hai’s large scale promotion, he also took care of prioritizing the people in Rising Sun City. This was because the Demons were the bigger threat at that time, and Rising Sun City was at the forefront of the battle. Therefore, Zhao Hai attached great importance to the defenders.

And Besmir didn’t disappoint him, the preparations in Rising Sun City was more developed compared to Upper Bank City. This made Zhao Hai satisfied with the result.

After Besmir relayed his report and seeing Zhao Hai’s satisfied expression, he relaxed his heart as he said, “ Mister, did you come just to inspect the defense?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly before he shook his head and said, “Not just this, I came here this time mainly because of the development in Demon City. It seems like the Demons will make their move soon.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Besmir stared, then his expression changed and said, “If Mister is here, then what about Upper Bank City?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Presently, the Divine Race aren’t making any sounds. They seem to be waiting for reinforcements. On the other hand, the Demon Army has now surpassed 20 million. With the increasing troops in Demons City, I believe that they would make their attack quite soon.”

Besmir knit his eyebrows and said, “With the current strength of the Demons, we wouldn’t be able to stop them by relying on Rising Sun City alone. The defensive line behind us has already been arranged. However, most of the people there haven’t been promoted, they’re still unfit to fight with the Demons.”

Zhao Hai agreed “This is truly hard to deal with. However, the thing we need to do right now is to delay the enemy as long as possible, allowing Accra Mountain more time to prepare. As soon as our Accra Mountain fortress finishes its preparations, then we would have a proper place to ambush the Demon and the Divine Race armies.”

Besmir nodded and said, “Alright, I understand. We’ll certainly delay the enemy. However, I’m afraid that also means that we’ll waste a lot of magic cannons, crystals, and blood lightning beads.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Rest assured, I will provide you with enough supplies. If Upper Bank City gets attacked, I’m afraid I won’t be here to assist you. When that time comes, I’ll need your help in promoting the levels of the other cities, providing them with strength to deal with the Demons.”

Besmir nodded and said, “Mister, feel relieved, we’ll definitely be able to stop the Demon Race.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ll leave some God-rank undead as well. However, it would be impossible for these undead to win against the Demons. So you still need to be careful. As long as the Divine Race hasn’t attacked Upper Bank City, then I will definitely come and help you. However, if Upper Bank City is under attack, then I’ll have to leave everything in your hands.”

Besmir gave a firm nod as he felt the weight on his shoulders increase, but he was still very happy.

Besmir didn’t know who Zhao Hai really was before meeting him. At that time, he only heard that Zhao Hai was very overbearing and was short-tempered. But now that they had been in touch multiple times, he knew that Zhao Hai was actually a selfless person. He was running around the continent, taking all of his goods for support while leading the frontlines at the same time. It was at that point that Besmir started to see Zhao Hai as his idol, the one he looked up to. Because of this, when Zhao Hai gave him this heavy task, he couldn’t help but feel very happy. At the same time, he can also feel the pressure, he was afraid of disappointing Zhao Hai if ever he failed.

Seeing Besmir’s tense expression, Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s going to be fine, there’s no need to be nervous. Actually, Accra Mountain is almost ready, you only need to stall for a short amount of time. The Demons can easily defeat our people, so what we need to do right now is to keep our people safe. Those who have fought with the Demons before will be great weapons in dealing with the Demons in the future. You’re a general, so you should know about the difference between veterans and recruits. What we need in this war are veterans, make sure to preserve them as much as possible. Understand?”

Besmir stared, he really wanted to use Rising Sun City in order to stop the Demons. In any case, he was even prepared to fight to the end just to stop the Demons from advancing. But now that Zhao Hai said so, he nodded and said, “Yes, sir, I understand.”

Zhao Hai patted Besmir’s shoulder and said, “You can do it. I’ll be honest with you, a lot of people in the continent weren’t taking the Demons and the Divine Race seriously. I can block them myself, however, this wouldn’t make their current mentality change. So the only thing that I can do right now is to depend on the frontline soldiers. At the same time, I can also use this opportunity to gather more undead, but only the enemies, I won’t do that to my allies. Because of this, I need every single soldier in the battlefield, I need people like you.”

Besmir’s eyes turned moist, he was just a soldier, so he didn’t know much about the complicated matters of the continent. However, seeing Zhao Hai express his grievance, he couldn’t help but resent the people of the continent. At the same time, he was also moved by Zhao Hai’s statement.

Besmir’s voice almost fluttered as he replied, “Sir, what are we going to do? We’re using our lives to protect the continent, but the population seems to take it lightly. Are we really that important?”

Zhao Hai looked straight into Besmir’s eyes and said, “Besmir, there’s no need to doubt it. Who are you? A soldier. And what do soldiers do? They protect homes and defend the country. This is your main responsibility. This in itself is an evidence to how important you people are. Even the most successful Merchant cannot do this. We are resisting against the Demons and the Divine Race because we wanted our children to have a great life in the future. We will not be slaves to the Divine Race nor will be die to the Demons, understand?”

Besmir made an effort to wipe a tear on his eye, he nodded and said, “Yes, sir, I understand.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “Besmir, your family, where are they right now? I’ll get them sent to the Black Wasteland, making sure that they are safe from harm.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Besmir couldn’t help but get excited. He can understand what Zhao Hai wanted to say, Zhao Hai wanted to recruit him over to his side. So he immediately told Zhao Hai about his address. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Demons are yet to attack, but you must still be ready. I’ll go back and handle some things first. When the Demons come, I’ll return.”

Besmir nodded, then Zhao Hai turned around to leave. Before long, Zhao Hai had Shue get Besmir’s family and had them sent to the Black Wasteland. This action was equal to having Besmir as his own person.

Zhao Hai already discovered Besmir’s talent in command. He needed talented people right now, so he gave special treatment to Besmir.

Lizzy and the others were paying attention the Demons. It can be said that the Demons were more prepared than the Divine Race when it came to making their move. They had already stockpiled massive amounts of military supplies in Demon City. Moreover, their logistics weren’t slow as well.

Lizzy was currently frowning as she was observing the Demons, she didn’t even manage to notice Zhao Hai. Seeing Lizzy so serious, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “What happened? Are the Demons really that hard to deal with?”

Lizzy recovered, then she looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Very difficult. Brother Hai, as you can see, they are quite used to these things. Although they are in their territory, they didn’t have any point of relaxation. Most importantly, their coordination is very fluid. Their army composition can deal with anything thrown at them. It can be said that in a frontal battle, the Demons are more powerful than the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled, “That’s natural if you think about the matters of the Demon Realm. All year round, wars happen in every corner of the plane. Therefore, it wouldn’t be strange for the Demons to be this formidable. Don’t worry too much about it, thinking about possibilities at this time is useless. Just wait for the real battle and then form conclusions then. Make sure to conserve your energy, we still have the Divine Race to attend to. You can leave the matters here for Besmir to take care of.”

Lizzy shook her head and said, “I just want to see how the Demons conduct their war preparation. However, I still haven’t thought about a good way to deal with them. Forget it, I’ll just turn my attention to the Divine Race. I’m afraid their reinforcements would arrive in the next few days. It seems like we will have to fight in two fronts. Brother Hai, are we prepared for this?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile, “We already did all we could. The Divine Race seems to be anxious while the Demons wanted to take it slow. I can still deal with the Divine Race, but we could only delay the Demons. In any case, as long as Accra Mountain completes its preparations, we can just proceed to slowly retreat and hand the Buddha Empire over to the enemy. I don’t believe that the Demons and the Divine Race would get into an agreement to divide the Empire by half.”

Chapter 754: Dark Mist In The Icefield

In the Northern Polar Icefield at this time, the icefield was not so frozen like before. After all, the source of the ice has been taken away. However, due to its relation with the sun, the icefield was still one of the coldest place in the Ark Continent.

After Zhao Hai acquired the wind bead as well as Bubble, he didn’t go and explore the place anymore. This was because Zhao Hai’s main purpose at that time was to retrieve the Beast God’s Spear. So when he found the spear, he immediately thought nothing about the Northern Icefield.

To be honest, nothing really did happen inside the Icefield. But now, it was different. Just as Zhao Hai was having a headache about the Demons and the Divine Race, an unknown change suddenly happened in the Icefield.

In the icefield, no matter day or night, the landscape had always been white. One almost couldn’t see any other color except white. Now, this white has been tainted by a little black spot.

But even if it was just a dark spot, its area was still quite bit. The spot was a black mist of over a hundred meters in diameter. In the white icefield, this black spot looked just like an ink blot on a sheet of paper.

This change happened without anyone’s notice. If Zhao Hai were to discover this black spot, then he might be able to calculate that it appeared just as the Elves’ Tree of Life started withering.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t have the time to pay attention to the icefield. The Demons and the Divine Race were already giving him headaches, he wasn’t so relaxed to turn his gaze towards the barren icefield.

As time passed, the dark mist became thicker and thicker as the area it took increased. After becoming about ten thousand meters in diameter, the center of the dark mist was already as black as ink.

Then inside that ink black mist, white smog started to bellow. But this white smog wasn’t anything normal, it can actually corrode everything in touched. This corrosive smog appeared more and more.

But this dark mist was nothing more than just a screen. Two days later, a black circular hole has been corroded by the white smog. Then from that hole, more and more dark mists started appearing, making the existing dark spot bigger and bigger.

The suddenly, a bony hand extended from that round hole before a skeleton walked out. He was fully bone white with a slippery bald head. It started to look around the place in puzzlement as it randomly walked around.

Shortly after the skeleton walked out, another skeleton appeared. This skeleton made the same action as the first one, then a third skeleton came.

More and more skeletons appeared from that hole and had started to walk in all directions. It might seem like they weren’t doing anything, but in fact they were actually fanning the area around the dark hole.

After an uncountable number of skeletons appeared, a giant bony claw suddenly extended out of the hole, making it bigger in the process. Then a huge magic beast appeared. This beast looked like a wingless skeletal version of the Demon Realm’s dragon. It was actually smaller than a dragon and it even had a few bones missing. The skeletal dragon looked like it had been ravaged by battle.

After this undead dragon came out of the hole, it immediately made a large roar. Although it was only a skeleton, the roar that it made was actually very loud. With this roar, the undead close to it started to group up before standing still. It seems like the undead were listening to the orders of this undead dragon.

As the loud roar spread, the skeletons in all directions suddenly proceeded to walk, slowly leaving the dark mist and walking further and further.

After this undead beast appeared, more undead started to appear from the hole. Then after a moment, a zombie with green hair started to climb up.

After these green haired zombies walked out, blue-haired zombies started to appear. Then behind those zombies were an uncountable amount of dark creatures. These creatures did the same as the skeletons before them, looking around before proceeding to walk.

At this time, Zhao Hai was actually worried about the Demons. The Demons were still camped up inside Demons City, this made Zhao Hai quite impatient. Moreover, the Demons have also started to send scouts.

Zhao Hai had always been thinking about the Demons. And now that they had started to send scouts, Zhao Hai began to worry.

For the other party to send scouts, then this meant that they were already prepared to attack. Yesterday, Zhao Hai and the others had discovered that the Demons have increased in Demon City. And now that they had sent scouts, then it seems like the Demons have decided to make their move.

After looking at the scouts, Zhao Hai let out a sigh before turning to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, should we send some Elves to deal with these Demon scouts?”

Lizzy looked at the Demon scouts and then said, “Brother Hai, to be honest, dealing with those scouts would be a good idea. However, you also need to think that the Demons are pretty strict about their methods. These scouts should have their own methods. And even if we eliminate them, then this will definitely attract the Demons’ attention.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he replied, “We still have to send the Elves to deal with them. In any case, they would still attack. If we don’t make a move, the Demons might think that we are cowering in fear. Eliminate those scouts, let’s see how the Demons respond.”

Lizzy hesitated for a bit, but she still transmitted the orders without saying anything. Although the people in Rising Sun City weren’t afraid in facing the Demons, they still kept from sending scouts outside. Zhao Hai’s sudden order actually made them surprised.

However, Besmir immediately obeyed Zhao Hai’s order. He believed that there must be a reason for Zhao Hai to make it. Zhao Hai’s understanding of the Demons and their methods were much stronger compared to him. Therefore, he didn’t say anything about the order as he quickly dispatched some Elves to deal with the enemy scouts.

Zhao Hai looked at the Elves’ movements on the monitor. The Elves in Rising Sun City had already reached 9th rank. Moreover, they also provided with a lot of blood lightning beads. One can say that this motion was made to examine how powerful the beads could be in the hands of 9th rank Elves.

Before long, Zhao Hai saw the Elves group up into a hundred people per squad. All of them were advancing in the direction of the Demon Race’s forces.

These Elves were the elites of the Elven Race. And now that they had been supplied with blood lightning beads, it can be said that they were now the strongest combat unit in the continent. If they cannot defeat these Demons, then Zhao Hai’s investment would go to waste.

However, the Elves didn’t disappoint Zhao Hai. After the Elves departed, it didn’t take them too long before they found the Demon Race’s scouts. One must know that the scouts held the most versatile soldiers in an army. Naturally, this would also apply to the Demon race, their scouts were some of the elite forces of their respective armies. But after coming to the Ark Continent, these Demon scouts were yet to face the Elves. This made them look down on the approaching opponent.

Naturally, the Elves didn’t become polite as they immediately shot some stone beads. They didn’t use their blood lightning beads yet, they wanted to see the capabilities of these Demons first.

Finally, the stone beads had revealed how formidable the Demons were. One should know that these Demons weren’t 8th or 9th, they weren’t that high ranked. Therefore, the stone beads should be enough to cause them some damage.

However, the facts had shown that the Elves’ stone beads were unable to damage these Demons at all. This meant that without the blood lightning beads, the Elves would be useless in the battlefield.

If this was the case, the Elves could only deal with the Demons while in mid-air. The blood hawks were much faster than the Demons, so the Elves weren’t worried about them catching up.

At this moment, the Elves suddenly decided to fire their blood lightning beads. One must say that Zhao Hai’s blood lightning beads were quite lethal. A blood lightning bead was able to cause injury in a 20 meter circle within the opposite party. And with multiple of them fired at the same time, this would cause a chain reaction that enabled the beads to become much more deadly than before.

Firing on mounts was the best way to utilize the Elves. The scout troop that the Demons sent wasn’t large. But after seeing that the Elves were unable to cause them damage using their stone beads, the Demons started to think that the Elves can do nothing to them, that they had the strength to deal with the Elves easily. This caused the Demons to go and pursue the Elves.

It was at this time that the Elves started to use their blood lightning beads. These beads were things that even the Divine Race started to dread. Not to say 8th ranks, even the 9th rank Demons have exploded after being subjected to the might of the beads. They weren’t able to use self-destruct, even their formidable life force was unable to resist the explosion caused by the blood lightning beads. Almost instantly, the group of Demons vanished from mid-air, completely eradicated by the blood lightning beads.

Chapter 755: Dreaded By The Demon Race

There was a long distance between Demon City and Rising Sun City, so it would be impossible for the Demons to see what happened in Rising Sun City. It was also because of this that Besmir was unable to know what the Demons were doing unless he sent out scouts himself. He only managed to get information because of Zhao Hai.

One must say the Besmir really wanted to constrain the Demons, however, he was inferior to Zhao Hai when it came to commanding the other races. Because of this, he thought that unless it was Zhao Hai, it would be impossible for the city to work together in repelling the Demon Race.

This matter can be seen in Rising Sun City. In the city, the most suitable scouts would be the Elves. However, Besmir didn’t have the authority to command the Elves. This essentially meant that the city had no scouts to use.

The Elves only accepted Besmir as their commander because they were giving Zhao Hai face. However, this didn’t mean that they would listen to him.

But this time, the orders that Besmir sent out came from Zhao Hai. The Elves might not give Besmir any face, but they couldn’t just disregard Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai had always been fair in his treatment to other races. If they were punished by Zhao Hai, then not only would their races do nothing, they might even get more punishment instead.

Because of this, the Elves immediately went out to deal with the Demon scouts, and with an overwhelming victory at that. Although they were smaller, they still managed to eliminate the group of Demons. Even if this was a small achievement, this was still a huge morale boost for the people in Rising Sun City.

Seeing the actions of the Elves, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but feel delight. It seems like his decision with the Elves was correct. Most importantly, he also gained a metric about how strong 9th rank Elves could be. In the future, they would be able to understand how to utilize the Elves to their full potential.

The Demons wouldn’t know about what happened to their scouts, but as Lizzy said, the Demons have reached a state of complete mastery when it came to troop management. If their scouts don’t come back in a few hours, then it meant that they had an accident. Otherwise, the scouts would be punished if they came back late.

Because of this, when the Demons discovered that their scouts hadn’t returned, they immediately knew that something happened. They quickly sent a battalion in order to seek those scouts, but in the end, they were unable to find anything.

The Demons also understood that if nothing was found, then the only possibility was that they had been eliminated by the Humans. The Demons knew that there won’t be anything left once the scouts were defeated. This was because Zhao Hai was present, and he always turned his enemies into undead.

Because of this knowledge, the Demons decided to send a large unit to find the scouts. And even if a battalion was sent, they still didn’t dare to approach Rising Sun City.

It was clear that the Demons were dreading Zhao Hai. They wouldn’t dare face him before they had completed their preparations.

Zhao Hai looked at the actions of the Demons in the monitor. When he saw that they didn’t attack immediately, he couldn’t help but sigh in relief. This time, Zhao Hai sent the Elves out because first, he wanted to see how powerful the Elves were, and second, because he wanted the Demons to dread him even more, making sure that they would hesitate in making a move.

However, this situation held its advantages and disadvantages. They Demons might hesitate to make their attack, but when they do, then one could be assured that the Demons will be giving it their all. At that time, even if Zhao Hai personally went out, he would still be unable to stop their advance.

But the most fear that Zhao Hai had was the fact that he might not even be able to come out when the time comes. Although the Divine Race reinforcements were yet to arrive, there were all sorts of signals showing that they were on their way.

The Divine Race armies were very busy in the military barracks all the time. They had cleaned up every city in the Radiant Empire, this was a clear sign that the reinforcements would arrive.

After seeing the Divine Race, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh. He really couldn’t understand why the Divine Race would want to obtain the Ark Continent. The Divine Realm was a plane that was a level above the continent. Properly speaking, there was nothing in the Ark Continent that was worth their effort. But they still decided to come, was this because the Divine Race had an inborn desire of conquest?

One could say that it would be unjustified if one were to compare the people in the Divine Realm and the Ark Continent. In the Divine Realm, children were born as 8th ranks, become 9th ranks through adulthood, and God-rank after some practice. In this case, why would they look into the Ark Continent? Even reaching 9th rank would be difficult for the people in the continent.

However, Zhao Hai suddenly changed his mind when he thought about the Divine Race’s heavy cavalry. They seem to not be part of the Divine Race. Each and every heavy cavalry rider looked very much like wild men. It was impossible for the Divine Race to have those kinds of people among them. This could only point to the fact that the heavy cavalry units were the Divine Race’s slaves. It might be possible for Iron Hammer and the others to be unaware of this fact.

This kind of situation was not impossible. Iron Hammer and the others hadn’t been to the Divine Realm in tens of thousands of years. A lot of things can happen in those years and it was impossible to know about the actions of the Divine Race during that time.

If those heavy cavalry soldiers were really slaves of the Divine Race, then Zhao Hai could understand their motives. They wanted to do to the Ark Continent what they did to the heavy cavalry soldiers.

To be honest, Zhao Hai also held belief that the light cavalry soldiers were slaves of the Divine Race as well. It would be impossible for the Divine Race to send 9th ranks of their own people to the frontlines. One should know that no matter how formidable, light cavalry losses were also quite high.

If the light cavalry and the heavy cavalry were slaves of the Divine Race, then the Divine Race had become scarier. This was because it was possible that they had subdued this people not in the Divine Realm, but on other planes instead.

Zhao Hai’s speculation was not based on nothing. The Ark Continent only had a written history of less than 10 thousand years. And the matters that Iron Hammer told Zhao Hai was only a few years before that. At that time, the Ark Continent still had people ascend towards the Divine Realm. This meant that, at that time, the people in the Ark Continent were quite strong.

Moreover, Iron Hammer’s tale had told them that the ascendants of the Ark Continent had waged war with the Divine Race. There were the gods of the other races as well as some human gods that had fought with them. This might look simple, but when one looks at it carefully, they could see that the Ark Continent held enough talent that their ascendants were able to form a force that can fight with the Divine Race.

If this was the case, then this meant that the Ark Continent had been sending God-ranks for more than tens of thousands of years ago. This showed the longevity and strength of the Divine Realm.

And through all these time, the Divine Race had managed to stay formidable. If they can use their power to invade the Ark Continent, then why can’t they use it on other planes? If the Divine Race used this method on other planes, then this would explain the existence of the light and heavy cavalry units.

This would also explain the reason why the Divine Race decided to invade the Ark Continent. They wanted to make a colony while at the same time, take revenge against the ascended God-ranks from the continent.

Zhao Hai thought about all of this while he was staring at the monitor. As the Divine Race got busy, the worries in Zhao Hai’s heart increased. The military barracks that had been set up can accommodate at least several tens of millions of troops. However, the overall number of troops that the Ark Continent had not reach that number.

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and consoled him, “Big Brother Hai, don’t worry about it. At the very least, we know that the Divine Race and the Demons aren’t allies. As long as they don’t group up, then we would have our opportunity.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he held Lizzy’s hand as he replied, “I’ll be fine. After all, even if they become allies, we can just abandon the Ark Continent.”

Lizzy nodded. The without notice, a day passed by. Just as Zhao Hai got up, Cai’er flew over to him and said, “Young Master, good news. The materials have matured enough to provide for one God-rank potion and I’ve already started its production. Also, in a few minutes, the tiny pagoda would be finish. Young Master should head over there and see.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll go. Just wait a minute.” Then he went back to his room and cleaned himself up before he went towards the Processing Machine.

Laura and the others had also got up by now. They had also received the information before they quickly took care of themselves.

Laura and the others were different from other women in the continent, those that would need to do their makeup in half an hour, sometimes even over an hour. At this point, they had already abolished that custom. First reason was because they simply don’t have the time to do so.

The second reason was because there was no need. In the past, they would apply makeup in order to make themselves more attractive. But there was no need to do that right now. They had been drinking spatial water everyday and also ate the things in the Space. This allowed their skin and complexion to be as delicate as a baby’s skin. In this case, they would only ruin their face if they decided to put makeup on.

Because of these two reasons, Laura and the others didn’t bother to do their makeup as they immediately went towards the Processing Machine. They just adjusted their hair and wore some decent clothes.

Chapter 756: Immortal Cultivators Really Exist

Zhao Hai’s group were currently in front of the Processing Machine. The tiny pagoda’s upgrade would be finished in two minutes. On the other hand, the God-rank potion nearby had just started being processed.

After looking at the Processing Machine, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown as he looked at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, do we have enough money in the Space? Even if we use the materials in the magic backgrounds, we would still use gold coins to make God-rank potions. When that time comes, our expenses surely wouldn’t be small.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, you don’t need to worry. After the Space leveled up to 70, using the materials grown in the magic backgrounds would reduce the price of making God-ranked potions by about half. Moreover, in addition to the materials for the potion, I’ve also planted some highly prized crops in the magic backgrounds. Those things would definitely sell well in the Space, allowing us to be self sufficient in making the potions. Additionally, the materials in the magic backgrounds also reduced the time to make God-rank potions. Originally, the potions would take 48 hours, but now, they will be prepared in eight.”

Zhao Hai felt relief after he heard this. He didn’t think that the magic background would actually have this much benefits.

Laura turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, keep some potions for us. I heard that after becoming God-rank, one’s skin would improve. Moreover, one could also reach immortality.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but wipe a cold sweat on his forehead as he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, your skins are already soft. If you become God-rank, then I’m afraid I’d slip whenever I embrace you.”

The faces of the women couldn’t help but turn red, Laura slapped Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Talk less nonsense.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master has a point. Actually, the God-rank potion mainly restores the energy of the body, making every cell of a person more energetic. This allowed the person to look as though they are young. By staying in the Space daily, all of you had already achieved this point. So there really is no need for you to use the God-rank potion.”

Laura stared, then her face lit up as she replied, “Really? Then as long as we don’t leave the Space, then we would live longer than people outside?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Correct. However, because the Space’s level is still quite low, people couldn’t achieve immortality inside it. If we can obtain more plants and items, making the Space level up, then the lives of the people would get longer. Even if it cannot make you immortal, at the very least it won’t make you age.”

All of the women were now looking at Cai’er with shining eyes. Then they turned their heads to Zhao Hai. Seeing their blazing gazes, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but put his arm up as he said, “What do you want? If you want to push me down against my wishes, then I will definitely resist.”

Looking at Zhao Hai’s expression, the women didn’t know whether to laugh or get angry. All of them reached out to Zhao Hai’s waist at the same time and twisted it so hard it even made Zhao Hai scream.

After pinching Zhao Hai, Laura snorted and said, “Why do you always talk nonsense? Brother Hai, if we go to the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm, then we must get some rare plants and magic beasts in order to upgrade the Space as soon as possible.”

Zhao Hai was currently holding his own waist, he smiled bitterly and said, “When the time comes, we’ll do just that. Right, the tiny pagoda is almost complete. Let’s see what it looks like right now.”

Just as Zhao Hai said that, the Processing Machine let out a white light before the tiny pagoda appeared in front of Zhao Hai. The pagoda was totally different compared to its past appearance. Originally, the tiny pagoda was black all over. But now, the pagoda looks almost transparent, it looked like it was made out of ten thousand year old ice.

Laura and the others were also looking curiously at the tiny pagoda. Apart from the translucent white appearance, the tiny pagoda had also become eight sided. Wind chimes were still present on each corner of the pagoda, but these chimes were now white, blue, black, red, and yellow.

Zhao Hai understood that these five colors represented the five elements. And these colors were actually arranged according to the eight trigrams position. They were divided into two whites, two yellows, two blues, one red, and one black. These eight represented the five attributes that the eight trigrams were representing. The water and fire elements correspond to their own trigram. The trigrams for heaven(天) and lake(澤) correspond to the gold/metal element. The trigrams for thunder(雷) and wind(風) belong to the wood element. And lastly, the trigrams for mountain(山) and earth/soil(地) corresponds to the earth element. This explains why the eight wind chimes had five different colors.

On the top of the pagoda was a small yin yang pattern. This pattern was always turning, making the pagoda look mystical.

Zhao Hai extended his hand as the tiny pagoda flew over. The pagoda revolved around Zhao Hai’s hand as the wind chimes ringed. It sounded delightful, it was as soothing as a child’s laughter.

Zhao Hai was somewhat attracted to this tiny pagoda. It was too attractive, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stroke it with his hand. This action surprised Zhao Hai since the tiny pagoda acted just like a child. It gently rocked back and forth as it rubbed his hand. It was the same as a child rubbing its small head on the arm of his father.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile as he made his divine sense sink slowly into the pagoda. When his divine sense entered, a surge of information suddenly came to his mind. Zhao Hai stared blankly as he comprehended the information. It didn’t take too long before he was able to discover how to use the pagoda as well as its innate abilities.

The pagoda was quite strong. It can attack and defend, it can also utilize the power of the eight trigrams, five elements, and the yin-yang. It had a handy sound attack that can affect the minds of the enemy. However, its defense was more formidable. The tiny pagoda can emit a shield that can protect Zhao Hai. The shield can block physical, spiritual, and magic attacks. It was a very extraordinary defensive skill.

Most importantly, the tiny pagoda had also kept its swallowing attack. As long as the enemy gets swallowed by the pagoda, it can turn that enemy’s flesh, bones, and soul into energy. As long as this person is within the realm of the eight trigrams and the five elements, then that person would be unable to escape.

And this didn’t even count the fact that the tiny pagoda can use the five elements and transform them into dark energy, providing useful resource to dark creatures. At the same time, it can also transform dark energy into five element energy, allowing it to nourish the world. This property alone made the pagoda an extraordinary item of the world.

After knowing the abilities of the pagoda, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. He never expected the pagoda to reach this height.

Upon withdrawing his divine sense, Zhao Hai immediately called, “Artifact Spirit, come out.”

Just as Zhao Hai’s voice fell, a figure appeared on the tiny pagoda. This person wasn’t the one who fought with Zhao Hai, instead, it was a small child who had a yin-yang belly band. It had a round head with black hair that was tied up with two small five colored ropes.

When Zhao Hai saw this artifact spirit, he couldn’t help but stare. His complexion changed as he said, “You’re the artifact spirit? What happened to the original one?”

The artifact spirit immediately replied, “Answering to the Master. The original artifact spirit has been turned into pure energy and has been absorbed by me. However, master can feel relieved, I had inherited the memories of the past artifact spirit. If master wanted to know something, then I can provide you with an answer.”

Zhao Hai became relieved, he nodded and said, “Just call me young master. Tell me the background of the pagoda’s original master. Tell me the realm where he came from.”

The small child gave a nod and replied, “Yes, young master. The pagoda’s original master is from a world of cultivators. In that world, cultivators rule over countless planes. The Ark Continent is just one of the smaller planes among those.”

Zhao Hai stared, he couldn’t help but frown, “If they rule this plane, then why can’t they directly come here, but instead chose to send a projection?”

The small child quickly replied, “Answering the young master. They rule thousands of planes, but they aren’t running them directly. Instead, they would compel powerful people in those planes to worship them and regard them as gods. This would provide the immortal cultivators with faith power.”

Zhao Hai frowned, “Tell me about the stages of cultivation in that plane. And then tell me what this faith power is.”

The small child replied, “The stages of cultivation are divided into eight parts. The first and second stage had 12 levels each while the 3rd to 8th stages only had nine. The first stage is called Body Tempering, it was a stage where the focus lied on strengthening the body of the practitioner. This would prepare them for immortal cultivation as well as make them able to study immortal arts. The second stage is called Qi Refining. This stage mainly tackles a person’s breath. This stage would adjust the shortcomings of one’s body as well as fix the damages caused by Body Tempering.

The third stage is the Foundation Establishment stage. Reaching this rank would allow a person to be a true Immortal Cultivator. Their breath would transform along with their bodies. This stage is said to be the starting point of immortal cultivation.

The fourth stage is called the Gold Core stage. People of this rank can reach lifespans of 2000 to 3000 years. They can form a golden dan in their body which can help them absorb energy from the surroundings more efficiently. Their rate of absorption is said to be ten times faster than those in Foundation Establishment.

The fifth stage is the Nascent Soul stage. Immortal cultivators of this rank would crush their gold cores to form a nascent soul inside their bodies. This nascent soul would be like another personification of the immortal cultivator, helping them cultivate and absorb energy. People in this stage can also use advanced level immortal arts .They can attach their divine sense on objects and turn them into incarnations. And even if their bodies were destroyed, as long as their nascent soul escapes, then they can seize a body from another being. The immortal cultivator that the Young Master had fought with is a Nascent Soul Expert.

The sixth stage is the Spirit Severing stage. Immortal cultivators of this rank can separate their divine sense. This separation is completely different to those in Nascent Soul. Nascent Soul Experts needed magic treasures to attach their souls into. Moreover, the strengths that these incarnations have would only amount to about a tenth of the expert’s true strength. However, for those in Spirit Severing stage, their Divine Sense can exist independently to form incarnations. These incarnations would have about a sixth to a fifth of the Spirit Severing expert’s true cultivation.They could also attach their souls to magic weapons in order to increase its strength.

The seventh stage is called Transcending Tribulation stage. Upon reaching this rank, the Immortal Cultivator would enter the peak powers in the realm. They can have as many incarnations as they can. And each incarnation would have nine-tenths of their true body’s cultivation. Their main bodies were also allowed to study the Heavenly Dao of time as they prepare to face their tribulation. This is the reason why this stage is called Transcending Tribulation.

And the eight stage is the True Immortal stage. After reaching this stage, an Immortal Cultivator would live as long as the heavens and the earth. The heavens and the earth could no longer control their fate, thus they are called True Immortals!”

After speaking up to here, the small child caught his own breath, then he continued, “Faith power is a type of ability that Immortal Cultivators possess. However, average cultivators are unable to use it, even feel it. Only upon reaching Nascent Soul would one start to discover this ability. Faith power not only helps a person cultivatie, but it can also improve an immortal cultivator’s magic treasures. Because of this, as long as an immortal cultivator is from a great sect, they would be allowed to have access to several planes in order to gather faith energy. These planes are inferior planes where the most powerful people are Foundation Establishment experts.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown, “So is it impossible for immortal cultivators to descend on a plane?”

The small child nodded and said, “It is impossible. Cultivators below Nascent Soul would find it difficult to break the Space by themselves. Only if one were to ascend to a higher plane would this be allowed. Nascent Soul Experts are also too powerful to descend, this is the same for Spirit Severing Experts and Transcending Tribulation Experts. On the other hand ,Immortal Stage cultivators can achieve this. But even if they did, they still needed to merge with the heavens and the earth in order to break the space between two planes. And this would be a violation of the laws”

Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai’s frown couldn’t help but turn tighter. He said, “But the Divine Race just destroyed the laws of the Ark Continent. Isn’t this a violation to the heaven and earth?”

The small child shook his head and said, “What I was saying before refers to what the Immortal Cultivators describe to be major planes. These major planes have small planes under them, this included the Ark Continent, Divine Realm, and the Demon Realm along with countless other planes. These major planes are all managed by Nascent Soul Experts. These major planes have their own laws of the heavens and the earth. And if one were to look at the entire universe, the number of these major planes were also countless. So a change in a small plane like the Ark Continent wouldn’t have a huge impact to the entirety of the universe. This meant that even if the Divine Race had broken the laws, it was still the law of a major plane, not the universe itself.”

Chapter 757: Five Gates Sect

Zhao Hai nodded. He had understood so much from what the small child had said. He looked at the artifact spirit and said, “What is the name of the cultivator that fought with me? What sect did he belong to?”

The small child replied, “Young Master, that person is called Lu Wei, an immortal cultivator of the Five Gates Sect. A Nascent Soul Elder.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown as he asked, “What sect is this Five Gates Sect?”

The child replied, “Five Gate Sect is created by a person know as Five Gates immortal. He was a talented person ever since childhood. But because his family was poor, he lived on as a monk. Later on, when it was discovered that his root was extraordinary, he was immediately selected to become an outer disciple in a famous sect called the Golden Light Temple. However, nobody thought that his talent would surpass what everybody expected. In just three years, he managed to breeze through the 12 levels of Body Tempering, going on to become an official disciple. And then in five years, he would break through to Foundation Establishment, becoming an inner disciple. Then ten years after that, he had managed to form his gold core, becoming a Golden Core cultivator, propping him into a position of a core disciple. This is also the stage that divided disciples from each other. If one’s root is good, then they can become an official disciple, if it wasn’t, then one can only do chores. If a disciple can reach level 9 or more in Body Tempering within five years, then they would be promoted to being a formal disciple. If he can reach Qi Refining within ten years, then he can become an inner disciple. And within 100 years of entering the temple, if one were to reach Gold Core stage, then he would become a core disciple, a genius within the temple.”

The small child stopped for a moment here to look at Zhao Hai’s expression. Seeing that nothing has changed, he continued, “But afterwards, when FIve Gates immortal went out to do a mission, he was ambushed by someone, causing him serious injuries. Although he has been able to protect his live, his cultivation has been lost. The person who ordered his ambush was suspected to be from a very high background within the temple. In the end, he was expelled out of the sect.”

Zhao Hai gave a nod. Being heartless was a common trait of immortal cultivators.

Seeing how Zhao Hai was interested, the small child went back to his story, “But who would’ve thought that when Five Gates immortal got kicked out of the temple, he would actually meet a famous person. This person was titled Five Resolves Daoist. Five Resolve Daoist was a rogue cultivator that had become famous among the immortal cultivators. His cultivation method is known as the Five Resolves Art. To practice this art, one needed to achieve five goals in their emotions: absolute kinship, absolute love, absolute morality, absolute friendship, and absolute justice. It can be said that one needed to be resolved to be righteous in order to practice this art. After Five Gates immortal met Five Resolves Daoist, nobody knew what Five Resolves Daoist did or used, but he actually managed to restore Five Gates immortal’s cultivation. Moreover, it seems like his cultivation had shot up to more than what he had before. After Five Resolves Daoist died, Five Gates immortal began to spread his name to the world. With his talent, he managed to use the Five Resolves Art in order to reach Transcending Cultivation stage. Afterwards, he created Five Gates sect and became the Sect Master. This was something that even Five Resolves Daoist haven’t done.”

Zhao Hai nodded, it seems like this Five Gates immortal was truly formidable. After thinking for a moment, Zhao Hai turned to the small child and said, “Where is this Five Gates immortal now? How strong is the Five Gates Sect? What status did Lu Wei have inside the sect?” The small child replied, “Nobody knows where Five Gates immortal is since he hadn’t appeared for a long time. Some people said that he had survived his great tribulation and had become a True Immortal. Some said that he had lost his life during his closed-door cultivation. However, all of these are rumors, nobody knew exactly where and what happened to the immortal. As for Young Master’s second question, although Five Gates Sect can’t compare to the extremely powerful sects, it can still be considered to be first rate. As for Lu Wei’s status in the sect, it isn’t that high. He only became an elder because of his cultivation level.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Although he looked quite calm, his heart actually turned heavy. He wasn’t worried about Lu Wei, instead, he was worried about the Five Gates Sect. If they become enemies with this sect, then their futures wouldn’t be very good.

Laura and the others were currently standing by Zhao Hai’s side as the small child answered the questions. Although they couldn’t understand the conversation, they still knew that immortal cultivators were extremely terrifying people. In the eyes of immortal cultivators, they might just be like ants.

Zhao Hai looked at the small child. The child’s face was adorably plump, looking just like China’s olympic games mascot. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile and said, “You’ll be called Fuwa from now on. Tell me more about this plane where the immortal cultivators reside.” Fuwa immediately replied, “Yes, Young Master. The immortal realm is incomparable large. Nobody knew how many planes it it had but these planes are connected with transmission formations. At the same time, there are also major planes larger than the Ark Continent and Divine Realm. In these planes, there would be a constant number of people who will ascend to the immortal realm. But to accomplish that, one needed to have cultivated up to Gold Core stage. Upon ascending, the best result that one could come up to is becoming a disciple to a big sect.”[1]

Zhao Hai nodded, just as he thought, the immortal realm was much stronger than the Ark Continent. Lu Wei also said that when Zhao Hai ascends into the higher planes, he would then deal with him. People with a high enough cultivation would indeed ascend to a higher realm, much like how God-ranks of the Ark Continent ascend to the Divine Realm.

When Fuwa saw that Zhao Hai was listening intently, he said, “Young Master, there are also many large sects in the Immortal Realm. In addition to Five Gates sect and Golden Light Temple, there are also the 180 Buddhist Temples, 81 Supreme Dao Sects, 36 Demonic Sects, and 72 Earth Fiend Sects. These are the most famous sects in the realm.”

Zhao Hai frowned as he said, “What is going on with this 180 Temples? Do they belong to one group or are they separate sects?”

Fuwa answered, “Young Master, one could say that they belong to different sects. Golden Light Temple is actually one of them. The 180 temples is just a collective name for the sects that cultivate in the way of Buddhism. The 81 Daoist sects are the same. However, one couldn’t say that they are an alliance. Some of these sects are quite hostile to each other. The 30 Demon Sects and 70 Earth Fiend Sects also follow the same description. These sects can be said to be the actual rulers of the Immortal Realm. After them are the powerful cultivation families and then the different Rogue alliances. However, their overall strength is far worse than the big sects, so they don’t have much say in the decisions of the Realm.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Fuwa and said, “Alright, we’ll talk more about these things later. What I want you to do now is to improve the undead. Can you do it?”

Fuwa nodded and said, “Young master, that is not a problem. Although Young Master’s undead aren’t that strong, it is still not easy to upgrade them. I can only upgrade 81 undead at one time and it would take nine days to do so.” Zhao Hai nodded, then he sighed, “Alright. However, can you still fight while you are improving the undead?”

Fuwa nodded, “I am, however, it would slow down the progress of the upgrade.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then upgrade these 81 first.” Then he waved his hand as 81 undead appeared around him, these undead were dragons. The fighting strength of the Dragon race was much stronger than the Humans. Although the undead had the same rank of 9th rank, the dragons still held an edge compared to the other undead. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to upgrade the dragons first.

At this point, Zhao Hai had placed his undead in the Hell background to upgrade them as soon as possible. But although the background was useful to the undead, its effects couldn’t manifest in a short time.

Fuwa didn’t say any words as he received the undead inside the tiny pagoda. Then he proceeded to stare at Zhao Hai, looking quite adorable while doing it.

Zhao Hai had no reaction to this stare. On the other hand, the eyes of Laura and the others were shining. Laura couldn’t help but stretch her hand out and touch Fuwa. Fuwa seems to know about Zhao Hai’s relationship with the women, so he didn’t hide. However, even if he didn’t, Laura still couldn’t touch his body. Fuwa was just an artifact spirit, he didn’t have a corporeal body, only the tiny pagoda. Because of this, Laura’s hand just went through Fuwa’s body.

Laura stared, she couldn’t help but look disappointed at Fuwa. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then said, “Don’t worry, as long as Fuwa gets upgraded, then he will slowly turn into a genuine child.”

Fuwa nodded at Zhao Hai’s words and said, “Indeed” Laura smiled when she heard this, then she turned to Fuwa and said, “How can you be upgraded?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That would have to depend on me. The stronger I get, the more benefits he would have.” Then after that, the tiny pagoda entered his mouth and settled in his lower dantian, where it was nourished by Zhao Hai’s body.

Since the tiny pagoda has been received by Zhao Hai, Fuwa naturally disappeared. But at this time, Laura and the others were staring at Zhao Hai. Laura couldn’t help but say in surprise, “Brother Hai, did, did you just eat Fuwa?”

* * *

It can mean either lucky doll or blessed baby

Chapter 758: Slaves of the Divine Race

When Zhao Hai heard Laura, he almost lost himself and fainted. He looked at Laura and said, “Why would I eat him? I just placed the tiny pagoda inside my body, nourishing it with my energy. Only through this can Fuwa slowly improve.”

Suddenly, Laura seemed to have found something out, “So it’s actually that. So after nourishing him, he would become a true child? Then Brother Hai, wouldn’t that be the same as you being pregnant with Fuwa?”

Zhao Hai’s jaw slammed into the ground. As he looked at the laughing women, he couldn’t help but shout, “You actually dared to tease me! Let’s see how I’ll deal with you all!” Then he went on to chase the women who were still laughing with glee.

After having fun for a while, the group returned to the villa with Zhao Hai’s mind becoming very relaxed. After entering the living room, Zhao Hai immediately turned on the monitor to see the situation back in the Demon Race’s camp.

The Demons were still calm despite having their scouts killed. However, starting from then, they began to send large scouting parties. Due to their numbers, it would be impossible for the Dwarves to kill them all.

It seems like the Demons had already decided to have a steady approach in their  attack. This made Zhao Hai frown, this was because the more the Demons prepared, the less flaws their plans would have. It was just like how a worried farmer would double check every single piece of land, making sure that everything was plowed properly. This fastidiousness would allow the farmer to see which parts of his land was plowed quite shallow. On the other hand, a farmer that was in a hurry would never find any problems with his job.

The Demons were just like worried farmers right now. They were considering every more they make before taking a step forward. As long as they find no problems, they would proceed. Although their crops were slow, they can be assured that their harvests would be good.

Zhao Hai frowned as he lightly sighed and said, “I really am not sure if these people are Demons anymore. Aren’t the Demons quite known for being aggressive fighters? But from what we see, it seems like they are taking things quite slow. It should be really hard for them to endure this long.”

Laura was also frowning, “The behaviour of the Demons are really unusual. It can be seen that their commander is quite the patient fellow. This calm advance could only mean bad things for us.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned the monitor to look at the Divine Race. The Divine Race had already made good with their military barracks and had already started to send troops to the Buddha Empire’s border. They already had the Radiant Empire under their full control.

What surprised Zhao Hai the most were the people that came from the Divine Realm today. Although these people came from the Divine Realm, Zhao Hai can clearly see that they weren’t natives.

These people were short and small, similar to the Dwarves. However, they didn’t have the strong bodies of the Dwarves, instead, they were quite thin and looked weak. Additionally, they had green skins, two sharp ears like the Elves, and big black eyes. They didn’t have any shred of fur on their skin. They looked very strange, quite the opposite of cute.

At this moment, these small creatures were being driven forward by a Divine Race person using a whip. These little creatures were almost naked, only wearing a pair of shorts. A lot of them had injuries on their bodies, and their skins were almost sticking to their bones. They looked just like the starved slaves of the Ark Continent.

Upon seeing these people, Zhao Hai immediately knew that they were slaves of the Divine Race. But he didn’t know where these slaves were taken from.

Laura and the others couldn’t help but feel sympathy towards these creatures. Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, do you know who these little creatures are? Why haven’t I heard about them from Iron Hammer?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t know. Iron Hammer hadn’t mentioned these people as well. I reckon these creatures were captured by the Divine Race in the past ten thousand years. This might explain why Iron Hammer and the others weren’t aware of them. They seem to have the same nature as the heavy cavalry units.

Laura nodded, then she continued to look at the small people and said, “Why would the Divine Race send them here? Are they here to help build more military barracks?”

Zhao Hai sneered and said, “Not to build. Look, you can see that they had brought grain along with them. At this point, bringing supplies from the Divine Race to here would be an inconvenience, it would cost them too much. And although the Radiant Empire is the smallest Empire in the continent, there is still quite a large arabel area inside its territory. If they use these lands for farming, then it would be possible to help supply the Divine Race army. It seems like the Divine Race had already decided to have a long and drawn out war.”

Laura nodded, “That seems to be the case. If we didn’t have the Space, then transporting food and supplies would truly be very costly. And the Divine Race didn’t want it to be this way.”

Zhao Hai sighed, “I’m afraid that with this move of farming inside the Radiant Empire, the Divine Race had started to take root in the continent. Later on, if we want to drive them away, the resistance would be more intense, it wouldn’t be easy for us.”

Lizzy knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, do you think that the Divine Race has already conquered other small planes? Did Fuwa ever say any of these? We are in a major plane composed of smaller planes. If the Divine Race decided to deal with the Ark Continent, then its possible that they had done it to other planes. The heavy cavalry and their other slaves should have come from those smaller planes.”

Zhao Hai had already thought about this, so he said, “Correct, that is highly probable. If this is really the case, then things would become quite troublesome. No wonder the Divine Race started to move in after occupying the Radiant Empire. It seems like this isn’t their first time doing it.”

Lizzy gave a nod, “The Divine Race are truly formidable, they’re as difficult to deal with as the Demons. It seems like these two races would become great headaches in the future. I hope that when the time comes, they would get into a conflict with themselves. Otherwise, our burdens would only increase.”

Zhao Hai can understand Lizzy’s thoughts. Lizzy was referring to the time when they have already retreated to the Accra Mountains. They would block both parties there and then hope that they would fight each other. In this way, they would be catching fish without the help of a fisherman.

Zhao Hai gave out a sigh, he knew how cunning the Demons and the Divine Race were. If they want the two of them to fight, then Zhao Hai’s side needed to have the capability to do so. Only when the two parties were unable to capture the Accra Mountain would they possibly fight. Otherwise, they would deal with the Ark Continent’s residents first, fighting each other wouldn’t be too late after the residents have been taken care of.

And just as what Zhao Hai thought, the slaves that the Divine Race brought had started to cultivate the ground. From their skillful actions, one could see that they were already used to this lifestyle.

Zhao Hai sighed, the Divine Race was truly determined to get the Ark Continent. With these slaves, they wouldn’t need to care about the getting slaves from the Ark Continent. It seems like they would be more ruthless from now on.

After some time, Zhao Hai let out a loud breath before he stood up. Then he turned to Laura and the others and said, “From now on, we’ll prepare a lot of spatial water in order to promote every single person in the continent. At this point, its is either the Demons and the Divine Race perishing, or us. We couldn’t just wait here to be slaughtered, we need to take the fight to them.”

Laura nodded, with a firm expression she added, “Alright. I agree with Brother Hai. Even if we can’t make them God-ranks, as long as we have 9th ranks, we can deal with the attacks of the two races. Additionally, we also have our 9th rank magic beasts.”

Megan gave a nod as well. “There are a lot of troops in the continent. But since their strengths are too low, they couldn’t provide that much help. As soon as they get stronger, the average strength of the continent would rise. This would make it more convenient for us to deal with the Demons and the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and couldn’t help but bitterly sigh, “However, if we do this, the secret of the Space will be exposed. Forget it, this is the only way forward. If we don’t resist, then there would be no hope for the future. When that time comes, what will be the use of the Space? Laura, immediately contact the Rulers and Patriarchs of the various powers. Tell them about our plan to release massive amounts of potions in order to promote the troops of the continent. Tell them that we would upgrade them to 8th ranks and that the 9th rank potion would be on the way.”

Laura and the others immediately nodded before going off to settle the affair. Then Zhao Hai turned to look at the Divine Race and sighed once more. To be honest, his decision to release spatial water was actually influenced by Fuwa.

Fuwa made him understand a lot about the Immortal Realm. The Divine Race might be powerful, but in the end, they were just pawns of an elder of the Five Gates Sect, used in order to gather faith power. The people of the lower realms were just livestock to them, just like pigs, chicken, and sheep.

Moreover, the Five Gates Sect wasn’t the biggest sect in the Immortal Realm, only one of the numerous first-rate sects. From what he understood listening to Fuwa, the Five Gates Sect wasn’t even a member of the 180 Buddhist Temples, 81 Daoist Sects, 36 Devil Sects, nor the 72 Earth Fiend Sects. In other words, the strength of the cultivators in the Five Gates Sect can only be ranked at most in the top 400 sects in the Immortal Realm. If a normal elder of such a sect is enough to control the lower realm, then how about those more powerful than him?

The great strength of these immortal cultivators had stimulated Zhao Hai. He didn’t want to become just a pig inside a pen. He didn’t want to become an ant in another person’s eye. He wanted to rebel, he wanted to be competent enough that these immortal cultivators wouldn’t dare to look down on him. He wanted to prevent himself from being stepped on under their feet!

Chapter 759: Asking Them Over To See

A strange phenomenon can be seen in the Ark continent. It was already known that the Divine Race and the Demons were invading the continent, however, people seemed to not worry too much about it. They were just leisurely constructing military barracks, farms, and other essential structures. They seem to act like they were doing a chore in their house.

At a time when the invaders and the invaded were quite passive, Zhao Hai suddenly released a lot of spatial water into the continent. This was good news for the people, especially those in the army. The armies had already heard about the frontlines thanks to various channels. They also knew that they currently had no strength to combat the invaders, if they ever fight, then they would only be seeking death. But since they needed to protect their home and family, they made a resolve to fight no matter what.

But their worries changed when a large amount of spatial water suddenly flowed towards them. No matter what levels they were in, as long as they drank the water, then they would become 8th ranks in a short time. For some soldiers, this was something that they could only achieve in their dreams.

Although these people had already resolved themselves to die, this didn’t mean that they wanted to die. Nobody wanted to die, if given the choice, everybody would prefer life.

So how can people refrain from dying when fighting against the Demons and the Divine Race? Simple. As long as their strengths were improved, then their survivability would increase. Once they reach 8th ranks, then their chances of perishing in battle would significantly decrease.

These people were full of gratitude for Zhao Hai, and the next information almost made them worship Zhao Hai like a God. They had heard from other people that Zhao Hai has a potion that can make them 9th ranks. This was the strongest rank in the continent, they were people who can fly to the sky. Not a lot of people can reach this rank. And now that Zhao Hai has a potion to help people reach this rank, the soldiers couldn’t help but feel breathless.

Naturally, this mere fact alone wasn’t the most important. They had also heard that Mister Zhao Hai was producing these potions en masse and was planning on making all soldiers of the continent into 9th rank experts.

Moreover, these soldiers knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t talking nonsense. They were completely aware that Zhao Hai had these potions. They had seen the results in several of their peers.

Because of this proof, the soldiers couldn’t help but believe the news. This information caused a surge in morale for the Ark Continent, especially from the soldiers in the frontlines.

And Zhao Hai hadn’t gone back on his word. Large quantities of potions were delivered to various cities and settlements in the continent. As long as one was a soldier, frontline or reinforcing armies, all of them had been promoted to 8th rank. And after reaching 8th rank, they would need to wait later on for the 9th rank potions to arrive.

It didn’t take too long for 8th ranks to pop up all over the continent, they look like bamboo shoots going out of the soil after a rain. 3rd and 4th rank soldiers had become 8th ranks, the same level as those they looked up to. This made the people in the continent excited. At the same time, all of them held Zhao Hai with very high respects.

Moreover, Zhao Hai also gave an announcement that later on, commoners of the continent would be upgraded to 8th rank as well. Once they had drank this potion, it didn’t matter if they didn’t cultivate magic or battle qi, the potion would still improve one’s bodily strength. Additionally, if these commoners bore a child in the future, the effects of the potion would benefit the offspring as well.

This turned the people of the continent crazy. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this crazy and provide potions to the commoners as well.

Several Kings and Patriarchs tried to dissuade Zhao Hai, but after hearing his explanation they stopped doing so. Zhao Hai’s explanation was very simple. Both the Demons and the Divine Race are formidable, and it would be very hard to deal with them once they decided to join up. This time, the reason he decided to provide the potion to the masses was to prepare for a time where the frontline would get destroyed. This way, the civilians would be able to arm themselves and fight for the continent. After discussing this matter with them, Zhao Hai also made them prepare some troops to train the civilians to be emergency militia.

The various Rulers and Patriarchs of the continent didn’t expect Zhao Hai to resolve into this drastic matter. Did this meant that the frontlines weren’t able to stop the advance of the Demons and the Divine Race?

Has the situation turned too serious? Are the Demons and Divine Race really that strong? The armies of the continent had already been promoted to 8th rank, were they not enough?

Zhao Hai can understand this mentality. All of them had grown up in the Ark Continent, so it was impossible for them to completely understand the might of the Divine Race. They didn’t know that they were treated as milking cows for faith power. In their opinion, 8th ranks weren’t weak.

Zhao Hai was currently inside the living room, listening to Laura’s report. At this time, various Patriarchs and Rulers of the continent were still suspecting whether it was a good idea to promote the strength of the population. In their opinion, there was no need to do so.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “So those guys still don’t believe me, thinking that I’ve been wasting my resources. Laura, talk to them and ask if they would agree to visit the frontlines. We’ll take the initiative and show them how strong the Demons and the Divine Rae are. Then let’s see what they think after then.”

Laura knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, this is too dangerous. If those people gets into an accident, then our problems wouldn’t be small.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “I’m aware of that. But there is no other way for them to believe us. Right, tell them to have some of their higher officials come over as well. This way, they can relay what they had seen even faster.”

Laura was still frowning, “But will they come? Won’t they think that this is only our plan and we might be plotting against them?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “They won’t. They are already aware of our strength. If we decided to deal with them, then we wouldn’t do it in this convoluted way. Take care of this matter and discuss when all of them are able to come. We’ll prepare here as well.”

Laura nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll give it a try. Will you really attack the the Demon camp?”

Zhao Hai gave a nod, “We’ll make an attack, but we won’t make it to big. If we do so, then it might cause a strong counterattack from the Divine Race and the Demons. And we wouldn’t want that.”

Laura nodded, “Alright, then I’ll prepare what is needed.” Zhao Hai gave a nod before Laura turned around and left.

Just as what Zhao Hai expected, Laura’s invitation had gone very smoothly. They had also agreed to state a time on when they will visit the frontline. They had a strong desire to see how formidable the Demons and the Divine Race really were.

In order to unify the schedule, Laura gave them a date, which was three days after. In other words, three days later, the Patriarchs and Rulers of the continent, along with high ranked people in their respective nations, would arrive at the frontlines in order to watch Zhao Hai’s performance.

Three days went by fast. In the past few days, Zhao Hai didn’t make the Elves annoy the Demons, especially now that the scout troops have more people inside them. If the Elves were to clash with them, then it might be possible that casualties would arise, and Zhao Hai didn’t want such an outcome.

Three days later, the Rulers and Patriarchs of the various powers started to bring their trusted aides and subjects to Rising Sun City. Naturally, all of them were brought over using Zhao Hai’s Space.

When these people arrived in Rising Sun City, Zhao gave them a short introduction. The most populous people here were the Beastmen. Almost all of the Patriarchs of the Warring races have come, their number had easily reached several hundred. Adding the Emperors and their aides, the visitors had easily surpassed a thousand.

After greeting them, Zhao Hai said, “I know that everybody here wanted to see how strong both the Demons and the Divine Race are. Because of this, I called all of you over to witness today’s battle. I will attack the Demons with my undead. Everyone can just stay behind the army, however, please do follow our instructions. Otherwise, if something were to happen, this Zhao Hai will be unable to forgive himself.”

Those who came didn’t say anything, their relationship with Zhao Hai was very good. Even the Mermaid Queen didn’t say anything, she just gave a gentle nod.

However, the Rosen Emperor decided to speak, as he nodded, he said, “Little Hai, since you arranged it, we definitely won’t doubt you.”

After scanning the crowd, Zhao Hai nodded before he summoned large quantities of undead dragons. These dragons were like Alien, all of them had spaces inside to go into. Zhao Hai invited the visitors to go inside the bodies of the undead dragons. Since there were a lot of them, they were split up into several bone dragons.

But even so, Zhao Hai still used about 100 bone dragons in order to accommodate all of them. Then he summoned Shue and Berry along with more undead before they began to fly towards Demon City’s direction.

Zhao Hai already saw it, Demon City has been completely occupied by the Demons. Their number of God-ranks had also reached 50 thousand. It seems like the Demons were already geared for attack.

However, they didn’t think that even before they attacked, Zhao Hai decided to make a move. Zhao Hai didn’t want the Demons to think that the Ark Continent was just a soft persimmon, something that they can just pinch whenever they want.

Chapter 760: Worries of the Demon Dragon King

The Demon Dragon King was still the commander of the troops in Demon City. This wasn’t because he was the strongest God-rank Expert, but because he was very good at strategy.

It can be said that if the Great Demon King didn’t appear, then it might be possible for the Demon Dragon King to unify the Demon Realm. His mind for strategy was very formidable, but compared to the Great Demon King, he was still lacking in other aspects.

But this was where the Demon Dragon King seemed strange. Instead of going against the Great Demon King, he decided to devote his heart to help him, winning the Great Demon King’s trust in the end. This made the Great Demon King entrust important matters to the Demon Dragon King. For example, the operation of conquering the Ark Continent.

While the Great Demon King stayed back, taking care of the logistics and manpower, the Demon Dragon King took charge of the frontline, commanding the fight against the residents of the Ark Continent.

The Demon Dragon King was currently dread towards Zhao Hai, especially when the latter started to send Elves to deal with the Demon Scouts. The Demon Dragon King was aware of Zhao Hai’s strength, so it was no wonder that he had been very hesitant in making a move. Even amidst the satisfaction of the other Demons, the Demon Dragon King still decided to take things slow.

These newly arrived Demons haven’t fought with Zhao Hai, so they weren’t aware of how scary he was. The Demons didn’t think too highly on the residents of the Ark Continent. They had forgotten that conquering the Ark Continent wouldn’t take a day or two. In this conquest, the price was the entirety of the Ark Continent. And this price was exactly what made the Demons look down on the people in the Ark Continent. In the minds of the Demons, these people were not worthy of having such a paradise.

Additionally, the Demons haven’t heard of Zhao Hai’s name before. Zhao Hai’s rise was too quick, and because their information was inferior to the Divine Race, they haven’t gathered enough about him before their arrival.

This day, the Demon Dragon King was processing something in Demon City. He has already moved the Demon Race’s center of operations in the city, in preparation for conquering the rest of the Buddha Empire.

Although the Demons have yet to attack, the background matters still needed to be managed. The assignment of commodities was also an issue. The people in the Demon Realm weren’t less than those in the Ark Continent, and some of these people held grudges towards each other. Although they were under the summons of the Great Demon King in order to attack the Ark Continent, this didn’t mean that they would just forget their hatred. Because of this, the Demon Dragon King had to meticulously assign each troops. If he were to make a mistake, then he might be able to offend a certain group, causing internal strife in the Demon Army.

As the Demon Dragon King was working, a mixed sound of disagreement suddenly sounded outside. The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but knit his brows, he can recognize who these voices belonged to. It was from a famous race in the Demon Race, it was a voice from a Demon Brute.[1]

Just from the names of these Demons, one would know that they specialize in strength. They were the strongest but most temperate race in the Demon Realm. Their average height was three meters while their taller members can reach four. They might be very strong, but their weakness was their brains. They weren’t too smart, which caused them to be used as mere tools.

However, there were still no group in the Demon Race that dared to underestimate these Brutes. This was because the entire race was very united. If you use them as tools, and weren’t discovered, then that would be fine. However, if they were to find out, they would be willing to fight you to the death. And this didn’t just mean a single person, the whole race would attack you. Because of this characteristic, people still needed to think twice before taking advantage of them, even if they weren’t that smart.

At this time, the Demon Brutes had pledged themselves to the Great Demon King. But besides the Great Demon King, they wouldn’t listen to the words of other people. Even the Demon Dragon King needed to use the Great Demon King’s name in order to keep them calm, otherwise his words would be useless.

The one being noisy outside were precisely Demon Brutes, this caused the Demon Dragon King to develop a headache. He knew for certain why these Brutes were causing a ruckus. They’ve always wanted to attack the Ark Continent, but the Demon Dragon King have always stopped them since he thought that the time wasn’t ripe. He had sent the scouts to see and probe Zhao Hai’s reaction. If Zhao Hai was entangled with the Divine Race, then the forces in Rising Sun City would be reduced, which will hamper the city from dealing with the Demon scouts.

If the scouts can smoothly traverse the city’s vicinity, then this meant that Zhao Hai was with the Divine Race. This would be the best opportunity for them to attack. Otherwise, if Zhao Hai was free, they would have to wait for more time.

The Demon Dragon King had talked about this matter with the Great Demon King, of which the latter agreed. After all, the Great Demon King was the sovereign of all the Demons, even he doesn’t want any unnecessary losses among his people.

However, it was evident that this sentiment didn’t go through to the heads of the Demon Brutes. They thought that the Demon Dragon King was afraid. Moreover, they didn’t believe that the Great Demon King agreed to this plan, and that the Demon Dragon King was just deceiving them. These people had always pestered the Demon Dragon King to attack, every single day. Now that the heard their voices outside, the Demon Dragon King knew that they came to cause trouble once again.

The Demon Dragon King gently rubbed his forehead. To be honest, he was really bothered by these Demon Brutes. However, he wouldn’t dare to offend them. They were quite numerous, and their fighting strength was much needed by the Demon Army. Most importantly, they were completely unafraid of war, they were one of the most genuinely fearless Demons in the Demon Realm.

But these people were just too noisy, they were a constant bother to the Demon Dragon King’s busy life.

After some time, the Demon Dragon King sighed, then he stood up and prepared to head outside to appease these Brutes. No matter what, he needed them to wait for more time.

Just as the Demon Dragon King arrived outside the room, he saw several of his soldiers blocking a group of God-rank Brutes. Although these Brutes were only Demigods and were yet to become Full Gods, their strengths were still very valuable to the Demon Dragon King. But this value was slowly starting to vanish as the Demon Dragon King developed headaches from their constant disturbance.

When the group saw the Demon Dragon King come out, one of them loudly said, “Demon Dragon, why haven’t you led to battle yet? You even dared to lie about the Great Demon King’s words. Wait until we get in front of the Great Demon King, we’ll definitely denounce you. Give the order quickly, let us fight!”

Although this Brute didn’t have any respect for the Demon Dragon King, he was extremely respectful to the Great Demon King. Since the Great Demon King appointed the Demon Dragon King to be the commander for the frontlines, the Brutes wouldn’t dare to undermine his orders. One must know that the Demons were very strict when it came to discipline. If they dared to attack without the command of the Demon Dragon King, then they would have to answer to the Great Demon King when the time came. Because of this, they could only pester the Demon Dragon King until he gave the command for attack.

Just as the Demon Dragon King was about to appease them, a Vile Demon suddenly flew over to the Demon Dragon King’s courtyard. After the Demon Dragon King saw this person, he knew that he was from the scout troop that he had sent out. At this time, the Vile Demon seems to be very anxious while looking for him, something must have happened. The Demon Dragon King didn’t have the mood to care about the Demon Brute at this time as he turned to look at the scout and said, “What’s the problem? Did something happen?”

After descending from the sky, the Vile Demon immediately gave a salute to the Demon Dragon King before saying, “Your Highness, Zhao Hai came. He also brought his undead, he is directly heading here.”

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but stare upon hearing this information. His expression sank immediately as he said, “Quickly sound the drums. Prepare to meet the enemy!”

As soon as the Demon Brutes heard this command, they all couldn’t help but make an excited cheer before they turned around and ran. Naturally, they didn’t want to go and fight Zhao Hai right now, they were going back to gather their own people. The Demon Brutes were very united, so when they go to war, they would gather their kin and fight together.

The Demon Dragon King didn’t have the mood to deal with these Demon Brutes right now. Those Demon Brutes were already good as they are. They didn’t need to or have the capability to discuss strategy with. Because of this, pre-battle conferences were usually devoid of any Brutes. What the Demon Brutes generally do was to gather their people and then wait for further orders.

Before long, several Demons have arrived in the Demon Dragon King’s room. There were a lot of Vile Demons among these people, while the others were from diverse Demon Races. All of their forms and faces look terrifying, and all of their auras were strong. Every single one present in the room was a God-rank expert.

The Demon Dragon King looked at the group and said, “I think everyone already knew why you were called. Do you have any thoughts?’

A Vile Demon opened its mouth, “Naturally, we fight. But as for how to fight, we need to leave it up to you.”

Another Demon nodded, “We have been waiting for many days expecting that the Divine Race and the people of the Ark Continent are going at each other’s throats. But who would’ve known that they seem to have small losses. This is not good for our side. And now that the enemy is knocking at our door, it would be impossible for us to wait any longer. Otherwise, this would affect morale, and that wouldn’t be good for our future plans.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, then he let out a long breath and said, “The Ark Continent and the Divine Race only having small scale battles is already part of my expectations. I’m afraid that the Divine Race has the same idea as us. I also don’t expect the people of the Ark Continent to think about cooperating with the Divine Race. I heard that the Divine Race has used the people of the continent as blood sacrifice in order to descend as well as destroy the laws of the Ark Continent. At this point, the Ark Continent would definitely be in an irreconcilable feud with the Divine Race. it is also precisely because of this hatred where I hoped that the Ark Continent wouldn’t be able to hold back for long. It’s a matter of time before those two go into a large-scale battle.”

* * *

It’s something like “strength Demon”, I don’t know what that was so I settled on the closest description.

Chapter 761: Verbal Debate

The other Demons nodded, they were aware of this. In fact, they were confused as to why Zhao Hai still didn’t launch an attack towards the Divine Race.

The Demon Dragon King looked at the people and then said, “Zhao Hai has strange methods. I have met Zhao Hai a few times. It was when we still haven’t recovered our strength. At that time, Zhao Hai was just a Demigod. But when we fought, he suddenly was able to become a Full God. Moreover, his fighting prowess was very strong. At that time, we only managed to hurt him even though there were five of us. He also managed to take Shiying with him. From what I heard, Shiying is already dead and was turned into a God-rank undead. What I dread the most is the fact that Shiying didn’t lose any of his strength despite becoming an undead. Zhao Hai is not a simple person.”

When the group of Demons heard this, they couldn’t help but turn silent. They didn’t expect that something like this has happened. No wonder the Demon Dragon King always had a shade of dread whenever he mentions Zhao Hai.

After a while, the Demon Dragon King continued, “We can’t underestimate Zhao Hai. For him to come to our doorstep means that he has something in hand. Everyone must be careful. Also, Zhao Hai seems to know a lot about the Demon Realm. I don’t know why but he has information that people from the Ark Continent would never find out. Alright, let’s end here. Gather the men, we’ll have to drive Zhao Hai back.”

The group nodded before they turned around and left. The Demon Dragon King also went out and rode his Black Dragon Carriage as it flew into the skies above Demon City.

At this time, the Demon Brutes have also gathered and were flying in the air alongside other Demons. The Demon Dragon King brought a battalion along with him as they slowly flew out of Demon City. Zhao Hai didn’t make them wait for a long time. The undead weren’t slow as the cube formation quickly appeared in front of the Demon Dragon King’s army.

Zhao Hai’s group of three were currently standing on top of the bone dragon’s head. The Demons flying behind the Demon Dragon King curiously looked at this ordinary looking young man. They didn’t expect that this person would be the one who the Demon Dragon King dreaded. And most importantly, it seems like there was a Succubus right beside this young man.

Zhao Hai bowed to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Your Majesty Demon Dragon King, we meet again. It seems like you’ve already recovered to full strength. I don’t know if I should congratulate you or not.” The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai and gave a smile, “Mister, it has been too long since we’ve met. Did mister get in contact with the Divine Race? Can I ask who is stronger, the Demons or the Divine Race?”

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “Your Majesty has been working hard. I have indeed clashed with the Divine Race. Hehe, although I can say that there weren’t much difference between the two of you, but seeing how large the Demon Army has become, I couldn’t help but feel worry.” The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, to be honest, although I admire your methods, I’m afraid you can only block one of us. Did you consider what would happen if the Demons and the Divine Race team up?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle, “Haha, don’t worry about it, I can certainly block both of your advances. But first, I want to ask you, even if the Demons and the Divine Race team up, how would you divide the Ark Continent later on? Is it an equal split? The division doesn’t matter, more importantly, will you even agree to share the Ark Continent? Even if you agree, will the Divine Race be alright with it?”

Just as the two met, they immediately started a verbal debate. The Demon Dragon King was a veteran in this aspect, and Zhao Hai wasn’t very bad as well. This made the others around them open their eyes.

Seeing that he was losing, the Demon Dragon King said, “Mister doesn’t need to worry about that. Are you here just to talk to me? Or do you want to use our strengths to prove facts?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ll be impolite then.” Then he, along with Shue and Berry vanished in front of the Demon Dragon King. When they reappeared, they were already in the middle of an undead battalion.

The Demon Dragon King and the others were already prepared for this. The Demon Dragon King established his Domain along with the others behind him. Almost all at once, different kinds of Domain appeared in front of Zhao Hai.

At this moment, several hundred blue lights suddenly projected from the undead and hit the Demons. This made the Domains of the Demons sway, making them somewhat unstable. But this was not the end, another two batches of blue light came and attacked the Domains. This time, those who were hit had their Domains destroyed.

The Demons around them immediately reacted, immediately blocking the attacks from reaching those affected.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but stare blankly at this blue light. Zhao Hai had a new weapon, what was this blue light. Was this a Domain from a God-rank expert?

The Demon Dragon King didn’t have the time to wait for an answer as the other party’s blue lights were too strong. If they wait, they would only be pushed back further and further.

It wasn’t strange for the Demon Dragon King to think that way. Zhao Hai had installed his magic cannons inside the undead. This blue light was precisely the attack that came out of the magic cannons.

The Demon Dragon King immediately gave the command, “Kill them!” Then he urged his Black Dragon Carriage to go forward.

At the same time, Zhao Hai put forth a large number of undead to welcome the Demon Dragon King. These undead might just be Demigods, but their numbers couldn’t be underestimated. About five hundred thousand of them threw themselves towards the Demons. The speed of these undead were quick, moreover, their imposing manner was strong. It was surprising that they only had Demigod-level strength.

The Demon Dragon King’s heart couldn’t help but jump, he immediately said, “Everyone be careful. All of these undead are Demigods. There are too many of them, arrange into formations in order to deal with the enemy!”

The Demons had grown up in war since childhood, so they didn’t take too long before they responded to the Demon Dragon King’s warnings. All the Demons immediately grouped up and connected their Domains, uniting together to deal with the sea of undead.

Zhao Hai looked at the back of the enemy’s army and to the Demon Dragon King. Zhao Hai didn’t like how quick the Demons were in responding. They were truly formidable enemies.

The army of Demigod undead quickly got in contact with the formations made by the God-rank Demons. These undead actually made their own formations, but this credit went to Lizzy and Megan.

At this point, Lizzy and Megan were getting better and better in coordination. Lizzy commanded her undead to fight against the God-ranked Demons while Megan took care of the others. The skies above Demon City were lively and full of action. However, Zhao Hai has yet to gain any advantages from the fight.

Inside one of the undead, the Beast King had found himself having an ugly expression. He had always thought about how strong the Beastmen were when it came to warfare. Their savageness in the battlefield was something that was feared in the Ark Continent. No power dared to annoy the Beastman Race.

But in this fight, the Beast King saw severely wounded Demons voluntarily exploding themselves. Not only did this eliminate them being turned into undead, they also managed to take some undead along with them.

The Beast King can see it clearly. Zhao Hai’s undead were all at least 9th rank. One of the Demons blew themselves up and turned the undead in front of him into ash. Several undead close by were also affected by the shockwave, severely damaging them in the process.

This scene wasn’t rare in the battlefield. As long as Demon was seriously injured, they will immediately blow themselves up, causing damage to their enemies.

While looking at those Demons, the Beast King couldn’t help but feel terrified. He can be assured that the Beastmen wouldn’t be able to reach this point. Moreover, what made him startled was the raw strength of these Demons.

When a person goes head to head with an equally ranked undead, then that person would suffer greatly. This was because the undead weren’t afraid of death nor pain. If you slash them with a sword, they wouldn’t care to defend, instead, the undead would just swing a sword at you at the same time. In the end, the one who would profit off of this trade would be the undead. Because of this, people would only fight an undead whenever their strength greatly surpassed it.

On the other hand, the Demons weren’t only fighting with the undead, they were also in equal terms. Only when they were killed by the undead would they stop fighting, otherwise they would explode, taking some undead along with them. Such ways of fighting could terrify any person.

It wasn’t only the Beast King, the heads of the major powers were also shocked at the Demon Race’s manner of fighting. They were too savage, too scary. They can affirm that no soldier, even those who had turned 9th rank, would be able to single handedly face these Demons. Except for Zhao Hai’s undead army, all other armies would surely find it difficult to stop the Demon Race.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the battlefield before him. To be honest, he didn’t want to fight with the Demons yet. This was because fighting them at this time would give him no benefits. Unlike the Divine Race, the Demons would almost always blow themselves up before being turned into undead. Now only would this keep Zhao Hai from gaining profits, he would also lose a lot of undead.

Chapter 762: After the Battle

But this didn’t mean that Zhao Hai didn’t want to fight because he can’t. He was just compelled to do so because of the underlying reasons. Moreover, he also decided to use this time to see if the Demons had any weakness that he can exploit.

However, after half a day of battle, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to find something out. The life force of these Demons were just too strong. Only when their heads were chopped off could they be safe. Otherwise, no matter what injury they had, they would still manage to survive, and then they would proceed to blow themselves up.

Chopping the heads of Demons required huge skill, which Zhao Hai’s undead cannot voluntarily do. Because of this, Zhao Hai manage to lose a lot of undead in this battle.

The Demon Dragon King had already tied down the Demigod-level undead. However, the undead were still going strong. Otherwise, if they weren’t undead, they would have already fallen to the attacks of the Demon Dragon King’s group.

Zhao Hai looked at the battlefield and then frowned. The Demon Dragon King was doing the same thing as well. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s undead had caused him great headaches. Even the undead that the Lich summoned weren’t as hard to deal with compared to Zhao Hai’s undead. The team of Demons that can block the undead can only be so much compared to the numerous Demigod-level undead.

Both sides went on for two more hours, causing damage to both sides. At this time, Zhao Hai gently waved his hand as Megan and Lizzy led the undead to retreat, then Zhao Hai went forward. After seeing this, the Demon Dragon King also waved his hand, stopping the Demon Army from chasing. Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Dragon King and said, “Your Majesty, I just want to persuade you once more that the Ark Continent isn’t necessarily suitable for the Demons. Now that their spatial rift has been opened, the Divine Race had already started to flood into the continent. They are very greedy, managing to conquer multiple planes. If you decide to join with the Divine Race to deal with us, then after that the Divine Race would surely deal with the Demons. To be honest, after clashing with both you and the Divine Race, I can say that the Demons will surely face heavy casualties if you and the Divine Race were to fight. I’m saying this in order for the Great Demon King to take this matter into consideration.” Then Zhao Hai turned around and led his army to retreat.

The Demons didn’t chase after them, they wouldn’t dare to do so. At this time, the Demons finally understood why the Demon Dragon King had always held them back from attacking the Ark Continent. If they wanted to attack, then they have to consider this existence called Zhao Hai.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai until he was already far away. Then the Demon Dragon King sighed. To be honest, he was starting to believe Zhao Hai’s words. The Ark Continent might be a beautiful place, but it was not necessary for the survival of the Demon Race.

Why were the Demons strong? It was because they grew up in a place such as the Demon Realm. In that place, if you weren’t strong, then you will either be eaten or be turned into slaves. In this case, all the Demons needed to go all out, which resulted in the formidable Demon Race that it is now.

But the Ark Continent was different, the environment here was fantastic. There were food everywhere, moreover, there weren’t any dangers in living in this place. If the Demons were to get idle, will they still belong to the formidable Demon Race? It’s still hard to say.

On the other hand, it was really hard to give up on the Ark Continent. The place was too beautiful for the Demon Race, abandoning it would be a pity. Not to say the others, even the Demon Dragon King didn’t want to just give up. Although he knew that the continent would dull the fangs of the Demon Race, it was still too good to give up on.

The Demon Dragon King’s army slowly returned to Demon City. After arriving at the city, the Demon Dragon King immediately had a meeting with his subordinates. The Demon Dragon King also called the Demon Brutes over, he wanted to hear what they thought.

Although the Demon Brutes were the most violent race among the Demons, they were not that stupid. When facing a strong enemy, they would still make the right choice. This can be seen by the fact that they submitted to the Great Demon King. For each race to survive, they would need the necessary skills to do so, especially in a place like the Demon Realm. The Demon Brutes not only survived in this hellscape, they also managed to expand. If they were really the boorish fellows that were described, then they wouldn’t have reached their current status.

The Demon Dragon King sat in the hall, he looked at those present and said, “Everyone, tell me your thoughts about today’s battle.”

The people in the room looked at each other, but nobody spoke. After some time, a Demon opened its mouth, “Formidable. This Zhao Hai is stronger than what I thought. Conquering the Ark Continent was proving to be difficult.”

Then with this, the people in the room immediately expressed their thoughts to each other. One of them said, “I don’t understand. How could he have a lot of strong undead? This doesn’t add up.”

Another Demon said, “Right, and he didn’t even make a move, only his undead creatures fought.”

A Demon Brute in the audience stared at the others and said, “What? You’re all afraid? Are you really Demons? That Zhao Hai, even if strong, is still one person from the Ark Continent. Do you think there are more of him out there? If that was the case, then they would’ve driven us away a long time ago.”

The Demon Dragon King looked at the Brute as he nodded, “Right, out of all the people in the Ark Continent, this Zhao Hai is the only one that I dread. After investigating, I can affirm that the people in the Ark Continent are relying on Zhao Hai. If not for him, the continent would have already been conquered. Because of this, after knowing that the Divine Race has come, I decided to hold back from attacking. First, we can use this time to construct important structures for the rear army. And second, to have a look at the strength of the Divine Race. We need to know about the Divine Race in order to have the confidence to deal with them. And lastly, I want Zhao Hai and the Divine Race to fight, hopefully causing major losses on both sides. What do all of you think about this?”

The Demon Dragon King’s two cold eyes scanned everyone in the room. All of the couldn’t help but unconsciously lower their heads. They were ashamed of themselves for berating the Demon Dragon King with criticisms when he decided to refrain from doing an attack.

After seeing the response of the group in front of him, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but laugh inside. The relationships between the Demon Races were very complex. And now that they had been placed in a single place, they needed to be well managed. Even the Great Demon King was having difficulties in this matter, let along the Demon Dragon King.

Normally, the Demon Dragon King would find it hard to calm them. But now that Zhao Hai made a move, these people started to behave themselves. It was advantageous for the Demon Dragon King if these people were to stay this obedient.

After scanning the group, the Demon Dragon King said, “Alright, something major happened today, all of you should go back. Go and check the casualties in your respective groups. Those injured needed to be taken care of immediately. We don’t want to make a sudden move and make a drastic mistake. We need to be careful from now on.” Then the Demons nodded before they turned around to leave.

Demon City slowly calmed down. However, the same cannot be said with Rising Sun City. Zhao Hai wasn’t able to get any advantages in today’s battle, he might have even suffered some losses. However, Zhao Hai didn’t think too much about it. On the other hand, the Rulers and Patriarchs of the continents were very shaken, their expressions were ugly to see.

Zhao Hai welcomed them to the city lord’s mansion of Rising Sun City. After everyone had sat down, Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “Everyone should have witnessed the strength of the Demon race. To tell you the truth, those undead that I sent out had God-rank strength. However, they are only Demigods, the lowest level a God-rank expert can be, about the same strength as Origin Sword Saint. And I have used five hundred thousand of those undead to fight the Demons.” The Rulers and Patriarchs didn’t speak. In the past, since they haven’t witnessed the strength of the Demons, they couldn’t believe the tales told about them. But now, they finally understood that Zhao Hai didn’t lie. The Ark Continent was indeed in a very dangerous situation.

Zhao Hai looked at their faces and said, “The Divine Race’s strength is no weaker than the Demons. And there are more people from the Divine Race. In their army, their weakest troops are their Heavy Cavalry, with an average level of 8th rank. However, even if their Heavy Cavalry are unable to fly, they still have strength comparable to a 9th rank expert. Their innate strength is astonishing as well. If they were to charge, then I’m afraid that neither the Elephant Tribe, the Bull Tribe, nor the Rhinoceros Tribe are able to meet them head on. Moreover, after reaching 9th rank, their strengths have undergone a huge change. 8th ranks would be nothing in front of them.”

After speaking up to here, Zhao Hai continued, “Aside from the Heavy Cavalry, there are Light Cavalry units as well. The lowest rank of these Light cavalry is 9th rank, God-ranks were among their numbers. In addition to their strength, they are quite quick as well. I’m afraid only the strengthened Elves with blood lightning beads can contend with them in the skies.”

Chapter 763: Actually, We Are Sheep

As soon as Zhao Hai finished talking, he could see that the faces of those present here has become ugly. Zhao Hai looked at them and said, “I also suspect that the Divine Race’s light and heavy cavalries aren’t real members of the Divine Race, but slaves that came from the planes that the Divine Race has conquered. Naturally, their status in the Divine Race should be just cannon fodder. Every fight, they would be placed in the front while the Divine Race stays behind. At the same time, the Divine Race army is also very powerful. They almost don’t have any 9th rank member, most of them are God-ranks. If we didn’t have the magic cannons in the last encounter, then we might not have been able to stop them from going forward.”

Then Zhao Hai gave out a sigh and continued, “This is truly the Ark Continent’s greatest tribulation. The Demons and the Divine Race, any one of them would be difficult to deal with, much less two. The reason why I had the commoners promoted was because I’m afraid that we wouldn’t be able to stop the two invaders from going forward. When the time comes, we would need all the manpower that we can get.”

Nobody spoke, although they hadn’t yet seen the Divine Race, seeing Zhao Hai equating them to the Demons was enough to prove their prowess.

Zhao Hai scanned the group and then gave a bitter smile, “Actually, there is another matter that I still haven’t told all of you. I’m hesitating to tell this because I’m afraid that you would become too terrified.”

When the Rosen Emperor heard Zhao Hai, he paused for a moment before he said, “Little Hai, what else can scare someone as old as us. Just say it. Can it be more terrifying than the arrival of the Demons and the Divine Race?” Zhao Hai looked at the Rosen Emperor and smiled, “Father-in-law, this thing is more terrifying than that. Let me tell you. I’ve already fought with the Divine Race for two times. The first time, I faced with their infantry units. They’re very strong. I managed to drive them away using my undead, the magic cannons, and a lot of crystals. On the second encounter, I faced against their regular army, the heavy cavalry, the light cavalry, and the summoners. I’ve already told everyone about the cavalry units. But those summoners are special units specifically trained by the Divine Race. These summoners summoned strong magic beasts. And most importantly, when these summoners combine their powers, they were able to summon a person.”

Those present gawked, summoning a person, they had heard of summoners able to summon humanoid magic beasts. However, from Zhao Hai’s tone, it seems like it wasn’t a magic beast. What does this mean?

Zhao Hai looked at the group and continued, “Right, it is an actual projection of a person. And the Divine Race called this person ‘Deity’. For the Divine Race to call someone Deity is already very strange. Afterwards, this projection and I had a huge fight. In the end, I almost lost my life when I was attacked by that person’s spiritual attack. Luckily, I was able to survive and eliminate the projection.”

The group continued to stare. Although they didn’t understand what this projection was, they can fairly imagine that a projection wasn’t a person himself, but something like a shadow instead. A shadow-like thing actually managed to almost kill Zhao Hai? This information made everyone panic.

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “To be honest, that was the most dangerous situation that I have been in. My mind was completely out of it. Fortunately, I have some potions in my hand, allowing me to recover quickly. That projection didn’t think that I can recover so fast, so he didn’t expect it when I came out and destroyed his weapon, eliminating the projection in the process.”

After speaking up to here, the room finally relaxed. Before this day, they wouldn’t easily believe Zhao Hai’s words. But now, all of them didn’t doubt him anymore. Even after seeing Zhao Hai doing well in front of them, they still couldn’t help but be nervous for Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai continued, “After killing the projection, I used a secret Dark Magic technique in order to obtain certain information from that person’s mouth. This information was what startled me.”

The Rulers and Patriarchs were all looking at Zhao Hai, waiting for him to say this information. Zhao Hai looked into their eyes and said, “From that person’s memory, I had found out that in this universe, planes like the Ark Continent, Demon Realm, and Divine Realm were aplenty. However, our Ark Continent, the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm were no more than the most common type of plane. They were under these so called major planes. That man from the projection was supervising this major plane in order to collect faith power from these common planes. In other words, in that person’s eyes, our use is just to provide them with faith power.”

The group stared, puzzled at what Zhao Hai said. Then the Rosen Emperor said, “Little Hai, what is this faith power that you speak of?”

Zhao Hai replied, “This faith power is a type of invisible energy. Actually, the Radiant Church’s purpose was precisely to offer this energy. As long as one becomes faithful to the point where one can sacrifice themselves, then they will provide faith power to the Deity. This energy might be useless to us, but for that man that the Divine Race summoned, it is very useful. Whether it was the Demons, Divine Race, or us, we are just like sheep raised to be sheared to provide wool.”

As soon as they heard this, the people in the room couldn’t help but be in an uproar. These people were used to be the ones stamping their feet, ruling the Ark Continent in their high positions. But now, in the eyes of the man that was summoned by the Divine Race, they were just like Sheep. How unbelievable was this?

Zhao Hai saw their reaction and smiled bitterly. He knew that this was a hard thing for these people to accept. They had lived their lives being aloof, but they were actually just sheep in the eyes of others. How could they just accept this fate?

After some time, the group calmed down, but each of their expression stayed quite ugly. Zhao Hai looked at them and forced a smile, “I know that everyone isn’t feeling any better. But no matter what, I need to say this. Although that projection was just like a shadow, but that thing had about the same strength as me even though it only had 1 percent of the true body’s power. In this case, if that person himself came here, I would have surely died. This person might seem strong, but from what I had gathered, he was only a normal person in his realm. In this case, how could they possibly place us in their eyes?”[1]

Zhao Hai’s words made those present turn pale. It was just unbelievable. If the enemy can send someone that can fight 100 Zhao Hais then that would be too scary.

Zhao Hai continued, “But everyone doesn’t need to worry about this. It would be impossible for that person to arrive at our Ark Continent, just like how hard it was for the Divine Race to arrive here. And since that person is too strong, he would have to expend more energy if he decided to personally descend.”

Seeing that the crowd had relaxed, Zhao Hai then said, “But even if they can’t come over, the aid that they could provide to the Divine Race was still problematic. The method that the Divine Race used to break the Ark Continent’s space came from that person. After all these years of guiding the Divine Race, who knows what weapons they have in their hands. Because of this, I couldn’t help but pay attention to the Divine Race.”

The group nodded, they didn’t dare underestimate the Divine Race after this. Then Zhao Hai said, “But I’m still afraid that the person would come here despite the difficulties. When that happens, then that would be the end for us. I don’t want to frighten you, but I want all of you to give your all in preparation. When both the Demons and the Divine Race decides to attack, then we would have to give up on the Buddha Empire and go all out in defending the Accra Mountains. In the mountains, our Ark Continent would have a chance for survival. We need to wait before my God-rank potions get finished, then we would have more God-ranks in the Ark Continent. When that time comes we can counter attack. And as long as we block the two races, it would be possible that they would go against each other first, that would be a good outcome for us. So when everyone gets back, they must train every single person they can. It may be possible for us to use them the war. But preferably, I want them to stay as reserve.”

The Patriarchs and Rulers nodded. After witnessing the Demons today, their previous mentality has already vanished. They were now very convinced to turn the commoners into experts that the continent may possibly use.

Zhao Hai looked into their eyes and said, “I know that everyone of us is busy, so I won’t be keeping you here for long. I only hope that after you head back, you will put your best in training the troops. The Divine Race has already turned the entire Radiant Empire into their military outpost, waiting for their reinforcements to arrive. On the other hand, the Demons have never stopped sending their troops over. If we combine those two armies, then my undead would prove insufficient. I need more people to help defend the frontline.”

The people present held a very heavy heart, but as Zhao Hai said, these invaders weren’t simple people. The continent couldn’t idle for too long.

After having their talk, Zhao Hai immediately used his spatial rifts to send everyone back to their territories.

* * *

It said 10 percent last time, but now its 1 percent xd

Chapter 764: Shun Becomes A God

After sending the Rulers and Patriarchs off, Zhao Hai gave out a sigh. Then he returned to the Space and sat inside the living room as Meg served him a cup of tea. Laura and the others were also sitting beside him.

Although Zhao Hai didn’t tell the whole truth, Laura and the others can understand that some matters cannot be said, especially when it came close to exposing the Space’s existence.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, do you think that those people would change the way they think? We didn’t really need to do that much”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I hope they do. Otherwise, he would have wasted our time.”

Lizzy had a complicated face as she said, “Brother Hai, why didn’t we go fight the Divine Race? Battling them would show father and the others a more formidable side of our enemies.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “The Divine Race is different from the Demons. The Demons are currently afraid of us, moreover, they desired for us to battle the Divine Race. Because of this, before the Divine Race makes their move, the Demons wouldn’t make too big of a move. On the other hand, the Divine Race has always been prepared for a fight. Also, after monitoring them for quite some time, you should know how arrogant the Divine Race are. If we decided to poke them a bit, then they might go and attack us in full force. When that time comes, the Demons would also make their move. The Demon Dragon King isn’t a simple person, that would be the result that he desired the most. Moreover, I chose the Demons because they don’t have magic cannons, completely different to the Divine Race who had huge ones. Although we haven’t seen the might of their cannons, we can be assured that they are more threatening than ours. From what I can see, threatening the Divine Race would cause us to lose more undead in the end.”

Lizzy gave an understanding nod. The Demons were also better targets because they didn’t have any strength with regards to defending a city, their prowess completely relied on field battles. But the Divine Race is different, their defensive strength was also very strong, those huge magic cannons aren’t just for decoration. If Zhao Hai went on to attack the Divine Race, then his losses would certainly be huge. And at this time, Zhao Hai cannot afford to lose so much undead.

Lizzy sighed and said, “Big Brother Hai, you’ve actually thought up to this point. I feel kind of useless right now.”

Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy and smiled, “What are you saying. Aren’t you and Megan the ones commanding the undead? Also, Laura, Ruyen, and Meg are also doing the logistics. It is only because you took these matters off my shoulders that was I able to make extra considerations. Moreover, you should know that your ability in commanding the undead is far superior than mine. If I were the one controlling the undead in the recent battle, then I might have even lost all of them.”

Lizzy and the others couldn’t help but smile upon listening to Zhao Hai. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you said that the Immortal Cultivator won’t come to the continent. However, what would we do if he did?”

Zhao Hai gave a bitter smile and said, “Lu Wei’s status isn’t high. Additionally, it would take a lot of resources for someone like him to come here from the cultivation world. Remember how much the Divine Race sacrificed in order to come here? Lu Wei would certainly pay a much bigger price compared to the Divine Race. Because of this, it would be close to impossible for him to come. The price would be too much for someone like Lu Wei to pay. What I’m worried right now is when we get stronger in the future. If we manage to ascend to the cultivation world, then we would have Lu Wei to worry about.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “There’s nothing to worry about that. He wouldn’t know that Brother Hai has the Space. Right, Brother Hai, when do you think the Divine Race would attack?” Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I don’t know. The Divine Race aren’t too anxious right now. Forget it, the God-rank potion should be done quite soon. When it’s made, Immediately give it to Shun. Then we’ll have him participate in battles in order to awaken his Domain. Cai’er, how long will it take before we can use the materials in the magic backgrounds?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “Young Master, they should be ready in a few days. There are already some that are available, but they are still yet to mutate. Having mutated ingredients would make it much easier for us to produce God-rank potions, so I chose to wait.” Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll leave it all to you. I’m quite tired, so I’ll take a break.” Then he stood up and went to his room.

Zhao Hai got up early the next morning. After having his breakfast, he went to the living room and looked at the screen. The movements of the Divine Race weren’t small. Their little slaves have already been sent to cultivate the lands. Moreover, they also had more of their troops stations near the Buddha Empire’s borders.

After seeing this scene, Zhao Hai’s complexion couldn’t help but sink. He knew that the reinforcements were coming, and that the Divine Race would soon start their attack. And from what he can see, they were going full force!

Laura and the others were also looking at the monitor. Although they had expected this situation, their imaginations were still less than the display before them. Their hearts couldn’t help but turn cold at what they had seen.

Zhao Hai let out a long breath and said, “It looks like it’s time to fight a major battle. I’m afraid the Divine Race would be attacking within a few days. These guys, it seems like they aren’t placing the Demons in their eyes. They clearly knew what the Demons are planning, but they still chose to be this arrogant.”

Laura and the others sighed, they didn’t say anything. Zhao Hai changed the monitor’s display to see the situation of the continent. He couldn’t help but let out a sigh of relief, the continent was now starting to train the commoners. Although it was just the start, it was still a welcome development.

After looking at this, Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Immediately tell the continent that the Divine Race’s reinforcements are coming. Moreover, they would be attacking in the next few days. Give them the 9th rank potions now, have them promote all the armies into 9th rank.”

Laura and the others nodded, then they proceeded to handle the matter. Zhao Hai was still quite worried. Although having a lot of 9th ranks was great, he wasn’t sure if they were able to fight the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai shook his head and disposed of these ideas. Then Zhao Hai released Fuwa and asked him about the undead dragons. Fuwa told him that they would still need more days before being done. It might have been fine if there wasn’t a battle, but now that one was coming, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but think about how hard it was to acquire God-ranks.

The next day, the God-rank potion had finally been made. Zhao Hai immediately called Shun over, making him take the potion. Shun smoothly became a God, but he was yet to comprehend a Domain. This time, Zhao Hai didn’t deliberately find trouble with the Divine Race or the Demons, the situation was just too volatile. For now, Zhao Hai had Shun get familiarized with his new strength.

And Zhao Hai made the right decision, although Shun can’t make a lot of clones like Shue, he was still a powerful assassin. With his promotion to God-rank, Shue’s hidden weapon skills became even stronger. From Zhao Hai’s calculations, not even 10 Demigods would be able to face Shue and his unstoppable hidden weapons.

Now that Shun and Shue, the two friends, were on the same ground once again. Zhao Hai was thinking about promoting Blockhead and Rockhead next. The mental synergy between the two was very strong. Once they become Gods, their combat strength would surely soar.

Zhao Hai was now acting like a Merchant, thinking carefully where to invest, making sure that every step was perfect.

Zhao Hai and Shue helped Shun get used to his own strength. In order to improve Shun’s power, Zhao Hai spent some gold coins in the Processing Machine in order to produce a batch of hidden weapons. He also gave Shun a couple of spatial bags filled with those weapons. The weapons in the bags should last him for a few years.

After leaving Shue and Shun, Zhao Hai felt more relaxed. In the past, the two had been worried that they weren’t able to help Zhao Hai, but now that Zhao Hai had things he couldn’t handle, the two can proceed to show their usefulness. While the two were looking at the monitor, Zhao Hai went on and got used to the tiny pagoda’s abilities.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to wait for the pagoda to make the first batch of undead before testing its defensive and offensive capabilities. But now it seems like that wouldn’t be the case. Not knowing when the Divine Race would attack, Zhao Hai decided to do his tests right now. If he cannot fully make use of the pagoda, then that would definitely be a loss. It was more important than upgrading the undead.

The tiny pagoda’s power was in the level of Demigod. But if Zhao Hai can utilize all of its strength, then he would be able to face 100 Demigods alone. Naturally, this required being familiar with the pagoda.

Using the pagoda will consume its energy, delaying the undead’s promotion. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about it right now.

Two days later, Shun can finally make use of his Demigod level strength. At the same time, a large scale reinforcement from the Divine Realm just arrived at the Ark Continent. The war is ready to set off!

Chapter 765: Tactic Most Suited For The Space

Zhao Hai was currently looking at the Divine Race displayed  in the monitor. This time, the Divine Race reinforcement were mainly infantry. This meant that the reinforcements were true members of the Divine Race.

Besides the infantry, there were also Summoners as well as a race that Zhao Hai hadn’t seen before. There weren’t anything strange about this race other than their height. They were about six meters tall, able to see eye to eye with any tall Beastman. Their bodies looked very strong as well, judging from what can be seen through their beast skin garments. Their weapon were huge wooden trunks, and engraved on these trunks was a pattern of a vine.

From their looks, one could say that they seem to be wild men. Zhao Hai didn’t doubt these people’s strength. Each one of them were God-rank, moreover, there were quite a lot of them, about a hundred thousand.

A hundred thousand might not look great in an army of ten million, but with their builds, a hundred thousand robust men looked very terrifying.

Laura and the others were also in the living room, looking at the Divine Race’s reinforcements through the monitor. In total, the reinforcing army numbered about 20 million. Adding on to the previous army, the Divine Race now numbered at 30 million, the same number as the Ark Continent’s entire military unit.

What kind of concept was a 30 million soldier army? In addition to the little slaves that cultivated, the Divine Race had now completely filled up the entire Radiant Empire.

Laura frowned and said, “It looks like the Divine Race is ready to march. Brother Hai, what can we do about this? They wouldn’t be so easy to stop.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “They truly are quite hard to deal with, but we need to do it regardless. Anyway, most of the Ark Continent’s army have already been promoted to 9th rank. They should be enough to make a dent on the Divine Race. To be honest, I’m not quite afraid of the Divine Race. Unlike with the Demons, I can make undead out of their dead soldiers. They wouldn’t blow themselves up so I should be able to replenish our forces.”

Laura nodded, then she said, “We should also give our army some magic beasts. This way, they would have more mobility in the battlefield.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “Alright, do that immediately. Later on, we can only battle in this way.”

Laura gave a nod before she, along with Lizzy and the others, made their move. They had already discussed this matter before. They would supply the armies of the continent with fast magic beasts in order to make use of the beasts’ mobility. As soon as the Divine Race attacks, the armies would continue on and harass them whenever possible using blood lightning beads. They wouldn’t make the Divine Race relax even for a little bit.

Zhao Hai’s methods turned out to be the same as what he repeatedly used in the past. Using guerilla warfare, they would continue to nibble at the Divine Race, making them unable to breathe properly.

This method was completely compatible with Zhao Hai. Because of the Space, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid that the soldiers would be ambushed, so it was a relatively safe way for them.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the means to deal with the enemy right now since his side was still quite weak. Because of this, they can only resort to making the Divine Race stumble on every step they make.

Zhao Hai’s side sent large quantities of magic beasts to the various armies in the continent. Since the Beastmen had their own mount, they didn’t need to be provided with some. On the other hand, even if the Dwarves still had their iron armored beasts, those mounts can only be used to dig, so they were very unsuitable for mobility purposes.

The Elven race has been completely transformed as an aerial unit. Their blood hawks have become very good in coordination. The ones who mainly needed the mounts were the Human armies. On the other hand, the Fishmen had special bodies. Although they have become 9th ranks and can leave the water for a long time, they would still need some time to get used to it.

As the Divine Race army arrived at the continent, they went on and recuperated for a few days. In any case, they weren’t in a hurry. In their opinion, the Ark Continent was already in their bag, so they went on their operation with leisure.

Zhao Hai took this time to complete the distribution of fast magic beasts. These magic beasts had already reached 9th rank, even the fastest pegasus mounts wouldn’t be able to catch them.

After handing the magic beasts out, Zhao Hai immediately led the troops to the battlefield, which was the cities in the Buddha Empire. Zhao Hai had already prepared the materials for those who would be stationed there. And as soon as they leave the place, the Space would just reclaim them. The Space was Zhao Hai’s ultimate weapon, it gave him the confidence to tussle with the Divine Race.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t have much problems in using the Space. When it came to command, he was already leaving it to Lizzy and Megan. This would also provide them with more experience for later on.

But although Zhao Hai wasn’t very good in commanding an army, he was still someone who had lived during the Information Era. Even if he wasn’t a commander, he can still apply the tactics that he had heard before, like the guerilla tactics. When he proposed this, Lizzy and Megan were actually shocked. They thought that this was the best way to combine tactics and the Space.

When he heard the reason for their surprise, Zhao Hai understood that he had been underestimating the Space. It would definitely be a waste if they didn’t use the Space in their plans to chip away at the Divine Race. But since he didn’t want to reveal the Space to the soldiers, he can only transport the troops from one point to another. But even with this, they can still attack the Divine Race momentarily before turning back.

Because they had planned a guerilla warfare, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried about the success or failure of a city. And since this was the case, Zhao Hai withdrew the magic cannons and then placed them inside his undead.

The corpses in Accra Mountain that were meant to be consumed had been transformed into undead by Zhao Hai. This was especially true for those with large bodies, they will become moving turrets, helping the mobile army in both attack and retreat.

Zhao Hai sent these moving turrets into the armies earlier so that they can get accustomed to using them in battle. More efficiency on their part would allow Zhao Hai to gain more undead.

Although the blood lightning beads were very strong, its targets would get vaporized once hit, leaving Zhao Hai with no bodies to turn into undead. Because of this, Zhao Hai was prepared to use these magic cannons along with the soldiers in order to gain more undead. At this point, the promoted 9th rank soldiers were extremely obedient towards Zhao Hai. They were very grateful for Zhao Hai for providing them with a way to improve their strength.

It can be said that if Zhao Hai commanded them to kill their monarchs, these soldiers would do it. In any case, the entire Ark Continent was depending on Zhao Hai. At this point, the Kings were less important compared to him.

The other races might not have this sentiment, but their feeling of gratitude for Zhao Hai was still quite strong. These races might not listen to anyone, but they will completely obey Zhao Hai.

As the continent was completing its preparation, the Accra Mountain’s defense line continued to be constructed. But at this time, the Demon Race’s side also underwent some changes.

The Demons were continually listening for news regarding Zhao Hai and the Divine Race. Therefore, it would be impossible for the Demons to be unaware that the Divine Race reinforcements have come. Moreover, they also knew that the continent had started to move. With this information, how could the Demons just let go of this opportunity.

The Demons were very clear about the fighting strength of the continent. They also knew that Zhao Hai had provided 9th rank potions to the continent. They even managed to get a potion for themselves. Then they sent the potion off to be researched. However, they had no idea how hard would it be to study the spatial water.

The reason why the Demons were aware of all of these was because they had people inside the Ark Continent. One shouldn’t forget about Engraved Ark. At present, none of them had been rooted out yet. Even if Zhao Hai has the Space, it would be impossible to catch all of them, especially at this hectic time.

Seeing the Demon Race’s changes, Zhao Hai knew that the true war has come. Once the Divine Race made their move, the Demons would soon follow suit. If they don’t, then they aren’t the Demon Race.

In the face of this situation, Zhao Hai can only turn to the armies in the Buddha Empire. What they needed to do was stall the invaders for as long as possible.

The Divine Race didn’t make Zhao Hai wait for long. Five days after their arrival, the Divine Race finally started to move. They gathered two battalions of mostly infantry and giants to head towards the city. On the other hand, the light and heavy cavalries became the second army and third army which directly went to the heart of the Buddha Empire. They thought that this army was enough, they were thinking that they were far superior to the Ark Continent’s army. The infantry and giants would face Zhao Hai while the 2nd and 3rd armies would circumvent Upper Bank City in order to target the other cities further inside the empire. Once these cities were taken care of, they would go back and deal with Zhao Hai. Even if they allowed Zhao Hai to escape, at least they already held control of the Buddha Empire.

This plan was good. But unfortunately for them, the weren’t aware that the Ark Continent’s armies had already been promoted. Moreover, they had also changed their tactics, they weren’t going to hold a city anymore!

Chapter 766: God of Thunder’s Army

Thunder Yun was a famous general in the Divine Race. He was called the God of Thunder because first; he was a lightning element divergent ability user. Second, because he had a booming voice that was just like thunder. And third, because of his Thunder Army.

The God of Thunder’s Army held fame in the Divine Race. Belonging to this army were the Giants. Just as Zhao Hai thought, the Divine Race had already conquered other planes. Some of the races in these planes were subdued, like the heavy cavalry, the winged pegasus cavalry, and the Giants.

The status of these people wasn’t high in the Divine Realm. The heavy cavalry unit was treated just the same as those little green creatures that currently cultivated the Radiant Empire’s land. The only difference between the two of them was that the green creatures were labor slaves while the heavy cavalry were battle slaves. Although the heavy cavalry held higher status that the green creatures, they still couldn’t escape the title of being a slave.

There were divisions when it came to the status of the slaves. The heavy cavalry held lower status compared to the winged pegasus cavalry. And the winged pegasus cavalry held lower status than the Giants. And the status of the Giants was almost no less than the commoners among the Divine Race.

The Giants in Thunder Yun’s army were called the Totem Division. They were a very powerful part of the army. Not only were their close combat capabilities strong, they can also use their totems to summon vines that would help them in battle. These vines were actually a kind of lightning element creature.

Thunder Yun has been fighting for the Divine Race for many years. With the God of Thunder’s Army in his hands, he had won many victories for the Divine Race, gaining awe and popularity in the Divine Race. He was even awarded a plane as his territory. This plane was where the Giants resided in. He directly named this plane as the God of Thunder’s Plane. The original name of the plane was Lightning Continent, precisely because of the lightning element creatures.

Thunder Yun was over 400 years old, a not so old age for a Divine Race person. If compared to a Human, he would be just like a middle-aged man. He silver hair on his head. However, the hair was quite strange. It looks just like Thunder Yun was hit by electricity, the hairs were standing up, and even looked a little burnt.

He also had a full silvery-white beard. He also had silver white armor as well as a silver-white weapon and silver white horse. His horse was not the same as a common one. This horse was just like the horned pegasus, but without wings. Also, the horn on its head would constantly flash with lightning. It was evident that it was a lightning element beast.

Although Thunder Yun didn’t think too much about the Ark Continent, his many years of experience allowed him a habit of collecting information. So when he arrived at the Ark Continent, he immediately asked Cloud Ying and Silver Shuke about the plane as well as Zhao Hai.

In the past, the Radiant Church had amassed information from Zhao Hai. But naturally, all of that was useless right now. When the Divine Race clashed with Zhao Hai, they discovered that Zhao Hai’s strength was better than what they imagined. The only trusted information that they had right now was from the two battles. Although some of them were useless and there were only a few good points, Thunder Yun was still able to get an idea about how strong Zhao Hai was.

When Thunder Yun saw the estimation of Zhao Hai’s strength, he couldn’t help but be surprised. He didn’t think that Zhao Hai would be this strong. He managed to repel their advance twice, without losing too much on his side.

Although this made Thunder Yun look down on Cloud Ying and Silver Shuke, this also allowed him to pay close attention to Zhao Hai. He knew about the strength of Cloud Ying and Silver Shuke’s armies. Silver Shuke was assigned to be the vanguard, this alone explains how much trust the Divine Race had on him. On the other hand, Silver Shuke’s regiment was able to summon the Deity. In addition to the light and heavy cavalries, the two armies couldn’t just be underestimated.

For these two regiments to be driven away by Zhao Hai was in itself proof of how strong Zhao Hai was. Because of this, Thunder Yun became alert towards Zhao Hai, despite his inner belief that the two regiments should be able to take the city on their own.

Thunder Yun was currently sitting on his magic beast. On his side was someone who held his weapon for him. This person was quite tall and big, about four meters tall. Beside carrying Thunder Yun’s weapon, he also had his own wooden trunk. This person was the leader of the Totem Division of Thunder Yun’s army.

Although this person wasn’t as big as the other Giants, he was actually a Highgod. With his two feet, he was innately fast. Now that he had become God-rank, he was unnaturally quick, he can even catch up with Thunder Yun who was on top of his mount. Because of this, Thunder Yun decided to have him as his own personal guard.

Thunder Yun was moderately advancing. In his front was his army, along with the Giant’s Totem Division.

One could say that the Totem Division was Thunder Yun’s most trusted men. This was because in addition to having them in his army, they were also residents of his own plane, whose families were very loyal to him. Moreover, their fighting strength was great. They were totally unafraid of war and were the most obedient troops.

In multiple wars, the Totem Division had secured him victories just by smashing through the enemy’s army. Because of this, inside the God of Thunder’s army, the Giants actually held greater status than the Divine Race.

Thunder Yun, who was going forward, suddenly muttered, “It has been a long time since we had met an interesting opponent. Fei’er, how do you think Zhao Hai would deal with us?”[1]

Fei’er was the Giant that stood next to him. Although this person looked stupid, his head wasn’t like that at all. He was Thunder Yun’s most trusted man, he would confidently discuss everything with this giant.

* * *

Can also be called Little Swift. However, I always think of Phil Swift when I type it. That guy from the ‘That’s a lotta damage’ meme >.>

Chapter 767: Engagement

Aiken was a Ten Thousand-man commander for the Rosen Empire. His former post was the commander for Rosen Empire’s elite heavy armor infantry. It was said that although he was just a Ten Thousand-man commander, his status wasn’t any lower than a local regiment army commander.

In the Rosen Empire, a local regiment commander generally commanded a hundred thousand to a hundred fifty thousand troops. For a ten thousand-man commander to be placed in the same status as a regiment commander was saying something.

Presently, Aiken was 40 years old. He was an 8th rank expert before but had just recently become 9th rank. His promotion was something that Zhao Hai gave him.

Aiken was in admiration towards Zhao Hai. In a short time, he managed to turn the Buda Clan into one of the most powerful families in the continent. That in itself was great, but he also married several beautiful women with powerful backgrounds, eliciting envy from people all over the continent.

And most of all, what made him very famous was his fighting strength. He was too strong, not only was he able to extinguish the Dragons, he even blocked the advance of the Demons and the Divine Race.

Aiken was one of the first people to be sent over here. Because of this, he was clear about the strength of the Divine Race. Seeing Zhao Hai drive them away was something that Aiken would never forget. Adding the fact that he was made 9th rank because of him, Aiken’s gratitude for Zhao Hai was something that only he could describe.

Zhao Hai’s plan had already been told to Aiken. Since Zhao Hai gave them horse-type magic beasts, they took off their heavy armor and donned light armor in exchange. The weapon that they held weren’t their heavy shields, but javelins instead. These javelins looked simple, just wooden poles that were sharpened.

However, Aiken knew not to underestimate the javelins. This was because he was aware that although they looked simple, these javelins were actually holding blood lightning beads.

But Aiken wasn’t thinking about this right now as his hand touched the small bag on his waist from time to time. Those who followed him were looking over with an envious gaze at the little leather bag, as if it was a rare treasure.

It can be said that the bag was indeed a treasure, it was a spatial bag. It was one of the smaller bags, only having ten or so cubic meters of space inside. What made it important was the thing inside it, a messenger fish.

Zhao Hai already had a lot of messenger fishes inside the Space. Therefore, he put them in good use and gave the leaders of each army group one. Ten thousand man commanders like Aiken would lead his army to harass the Divine Race, and in his group, only he obtained a messenger fish.

And although Aiken’s group were already 9th ranks, their flight speed wasn’t that quick. This was supplemented by Zhao Hai providing them with magic beasts. This magic beast wasn’t acquired from the Ark Continent, it was actually something bought from the Space’s shop, a Ferghana Horse.

Ferghana horses were animals from Earth. It was one of the most expensive ones not only because of their speed, but also their great endurance.

However, these ferghana horses were clearly different compared from those back on earth. These horses were now 9th ranks, so they were able to fly. Moreover, they still kept their speed and endurance. They were very well suited to be mounts, especially for a cavalry unit that needed to be quick.

The place that Aiken’s group were currently in wasn’t far from the Radiant Empire’s border. However, they were unable to see the Divine Race’s army. After all, if they can spot the Divine Race, the Divine Race can spot them as well.

Hower, they would still send some squads to monitor the Divine Race Army. This wouldn’t cause any problems with the Divine Race since they were already aware that Zhao Hai would send people to monitor their movements. If he did not, then it might even arouse their suspicion.

Aiken’s group had very excited expressions right now, they knew that they would be the first batch to face the Divine Race. For them, this was the greatest honor, this meant that they had Zhao Hai’s trust.

Aiken was a great military leader, otherwise he wouldn’t have become the commander of an elite heavy infantry unit. HIs family didn’t have a deep background, they were just an average middle grade noble family.

He relied on his military exploits in order to climb the ranks and end up where he was right now. Because of this, he was someone who was unafraid of war. Conversely, he liked going to war, only through battles could he gain more military merit.

Aiken touched the spatial bag once more, muttering, “Will it be soon?”

The guard at his side, upon hearing Aiken, calmly said, “Sir, it should be quite soon. Mister said it, so we should trust him.”

And just as the guard finished talking, Aiken’s two eyes shined. Then he took his spatial bag and took out the glass bottle inside. Soon after that, Zhao Hai’s voice came, “Aiken, go towards the left front. If you see any Divine Race troops, attack them then immediately retreat.”

Aiken quickly responded, “Yes, sir. We will head out immediately.”

Then Zhao Hai’s voice replied, “Be careful and don’t go too near. Killing the other party isn’t important, I want all of you back alive.” Aiken gave a sound of affirmation, then he placed the messenger fish back into the bag.

After putting the messenger fish away, Aiken turned to his men and said loudly, “Brothers, Mister Zhao Hai has ordered us to attack. We have 12 javelins, so when we meet the Divine Race, we will throw them out in the shortest time possible before we withdraw. Don’t hesitate and remember Mister’s instructions.”

The men gave a loud shout. In the eyes these frontline soldiers, Zhao Hai was a supreme existence. As long as Zhao Hai gave word, they will surely respond.

Then Aiken held his hand out as a banner was passed on to him. Embroidered on this flag was an ox, the symbol of Aiken’s troop.

Aiken looked at the banner and lifted it as he said, “Mount your horses, then we go forward!” Although they were heavy infantry, they were still used to riding horses. In the Ark Continent, there were many homes which had lower level magic beasts. These can be used to haul goods or plow the lands. And since Aiken himself was a nobleman, it would be impossible for him to be unable to ride a horse. After all, it was a compulsory lesson for nobles like him.

The others were similar as well. Some of them even came from military cavalry families. The reason they joined the heavy armor infantry was because they were deemed to be the elite forces of the Rosen Empire, their salary was the best. Therefore, any outstanding soldier would sign up for the heavy infantry division.

For this reason, Zhao Hai didn’t worry too much when he gave them their mounts. These people were already decent cavalry units without any need for training.

Aiken’s group got ready very fast. It didn’t take too long before the four hooves of the ferghana horses started to flutter. They seemed to be running on clouds, but this was just an illusion caused by how fast they were going. Soon, they were able to see the Divine Race army.

This Divine Race army had about 20 million troops in it. It can be said that their presence managed to blot out the sky. Compared to the 20 million, Aiken’s ten thousand troops looked utterly significant. Anyone weak willed would see their legs give out after facing such a display.

However, Aiken and the others were unafraid. In the past, Zhao Hai used tens of millions of undead to face the Divine Race army, they were already used to the scales of the current war.

The Divine Race also saw the approaching troop. Almost immediately, a similarly numbered troop went out of their formation in order to meet Aiken’s cavalry. After seeing the approaching enemy, Aiken’s eyes shone bright as he bellowed, “Prepare!” Then he took out two javelins from the leather bag by his side. The others did the same.

They didn’t stop going forward, seemingly intent on facing the ten thousand troops of the Divine Race. The Divine Race troops were all infantry, one can clearly see that they weren’t weak.

As these people went toward Aiken’s troop, they also adjusted their formation accordingly. They spread out and when they were a kilometer away they immediately established their Domain.

Although they were just ordinary God-rank experts, this display was already extraordinary. There were almost no Demigods among the Divine Race army. With how much they fight, it would only take a short time before they comprehend a Domain after reaching God-rank. After all, their Divine Race Demigods either comprehend a Domain or die in the battlefield.

Aiken already knew about Domains, but he still didn’t retreat. Instead, they went forward faster. As they quickly approach, the properties of the Domains started to show up. Seeing the spear shaped Domains, Aiken said, “Beware of long ranged attacks!” But even if he said that, they still didn’t stop and rushed forward with the same tenacity.

The distance between the two got closer and closer. When they were about 200 meters away, the Divine Race army suddenly released 10 thousand spear attacks towards Aiken’s group.

After feeling the might of the enemy’s approaching attack, Aiken immediately shouted, “First volley, fire!”

Then he switched to his other hand and said, “Second volley, fire!”

Two rounds of javelins, twenty thousand in total, darkened the skies as they flew towards the Divine Race’s ten thousand man army.

Chapter 768: Wave After Wave

However, these two volleys didn’t hit the Divine Race, instead, they clashed with the spear attacks that the Divine Race sent out. Upon hitting the spears, an explosion suddenly happened as both spear and javelin disappeared in mid air.

Aiken didn’t stop there, upon seeing this, he immediately commanded, “Shoot all ten javelins!” Then he swung his arms continuously as he threw javelin upon javelin towards the opposing army.

After emptying their ammo, Aiken commanded, “Retreat!” Then without any hesitation, he turned his horse around and escaped.

On the other hand, upon releasing their first attack, the Divine Race thought that they would get into close combat with Aiken’s troop. They had already seen that Aiken and the others were only 9th rank, therefore, their attack shouldn’t have been able to penetrate their Domain.

But they didn’t expect that Aiken’s side would only throw two javelins each in order to eliminate the attack that the Divine Race had sent out. Then just as the Divine Race were stunned, Aiken’s next attacks came in. A wave of ten consecutive volleys were currently facing the Divine Race.

The Divine Race was already aware that the Ark Continent would use blood lightning beads. Because of this, they quickly established their Domains in order to defend themselves. However, they weren’t expecting that the attack of the enemies would be this severe.

As they stared, the ten waves of javelins exploded. The first five waves eradicated their Domains, the latter five were for the Divine Race to take.

One must say that the region taken up by 10 thousand Domains weren’t small. If average people were to throw the javelins, it would be impossible for them to even touch the Divine Race.

However, one shouldn’t forget that Aiken and the others were 9th rank experts. 9th ranks used to be the strongest people in the Ark Continent. The javelins that they threw out could easily reach 1 kilometer away. Even if the Divine Race were God-ranked, they still wouldn’t be able to quickly dodge the javelins given how close the two parties were.

Both sides were 200 meters apart and had attacked virtually the same time. It can be said that when the attacks happened, both were already quite close. Fortunately, Aiken’s horses were very agile and were able to turn corners immediately, conveniently dodging the attacks from the Divine Race.

When the Divine Race reacted, and sent people to pursue Aiken’s troops, they were already too late to catch up.

Thunder Yun didn’t care too much about small engagements like these. In his opinion, a ten thousand man troop was pretty insignificant in front of a twenty million man army. Let along those troops being 9th ranks, he can just send out an army to swiftly kill them.

However, he didn’t think that this underestimation would make him suffer a loss. Of the ten thousand people he had sent out, nobody came back. Moreover, none of them were critically injured, not even corpses remained. All of them were directly vaporized by the blood lightning beads.

Thunder Yun looked at where Aiken clashed with the ten thousand Divine Race infantry. He couldn’t help but say, “Fei’er, send an order out. Tell them to make use of ranged attacks whenever they come in contact with the people from the Ark Continent. Don’t make them go too near.”

Fei’er nodded then relayed the orders. The faces of the Divine Race wasn’t too good. They had just left the Radiant Empire in a great mood, but they had already lost ten thousand people. It can be said that losing people this early wasn’t a good sign.

At this moment, on the Divine Race’s right side, another cavalry unit from the Ark Continent came out. This unit did the same, they were riding the same horses and had brought javelins. However, these people had received orders from Zhao Hai to fire at a safe distance before retreating immediately.

Zhao Hai was aware that although Domains can attack at a long distance, it was impossible for it to reach one kilometer. On the other hand, 9th ranks can confidently throw javelins at this distance. Because of this, after seeing that Aiken had caused severe losses, he instructed the others to take it easy and attack at a safe range.

This tactic was just like how mounted archers fought against infantry in the battlefield. They would pepper you with arrows in the distance and retreating when you decide to chase them.

The Divine Race rarely encountered such a thing. In the past, when the Divine Race conquers a plane, they would just saturate the place with experts, overwhelming the local residence with strength.

This would be even easier if the invaded plane didn’t have any God ranks. Without any way to resist the Divine Race, the plane would fall quite soon.

Before the Ark Continent, the Divine Race’s hardest conquest was in God of Thunder’s plane. To conquer the plane, the Divine Race had to expend a lot of resources. This was because there were a lot of God ranks in that plane. Moreover, their subordinates were also quite numerous. But even with this, they still managed to take control of the plane, despite the losses of several million lives.

That was the most dangerous situation the Divine Race had faced. But even then, they hadn’t experienced the same methods that Zhao Hai used.

It was obvious that the Ark Continent didn’t have any God-rank divisions. One can say that there were only very few God ranks among the Ark Continent’s residents. But the strange thing was, despite having low amounts of God ranks, the continent was still able to produce blood lightning beads in a quantity enough to threaten the Divine Race’s God ranks.

Although there were a lot of God ranks among the Divine Race, it would still be impossible for them to have an endless supply of blood lightning beads like the Ark Continent. In fact, blood lightning beads weren’t conventional weapons in the Divine Realm. This was because the method of making these beads was very troublesome. If a God rank made one, the damage on their vitality would be enormous. Because of this, it would be impossible for the Divine Race to use blood lightning beads the same way as Zhao Hai had.

But nobody could blame the Divine Race, even they wouldn’t have expected Zhao Hai to have an ultimate weapon such as the Space. It can be said that the blood lightning beads were just an amalgamation of two energies, of which the Space had unlimited amounts of. Zhao Hai already had the Blood Pond for the blood of a God rank expert, at the same time, he also had the Dao lotus to provide the lightning element. These two allowed the Ark Continent to have an endless amount of blood lightning beads, making them a standard weapon for the Ark Continent.

After the cavalry unleashed their 12 javelins, they immediately retreated. Even if the Divine Race wanted to chase after them, they were still unable to do so. This time, the Divine Race lost 1000 men. This amount was still insignificant compared to the 20 million that were currently here.

However, Thunder Yun didn’t feel good about it. The current situation made him frown, the other party was starting to prove to be a headache.

While Thunder Yun was thinking, another wave of attack came in. It was still the same javelin attack from a different cavalry unit. They were also firing from afar before retreating. They provided zero chance for a direct confrontation.

The brows of Thunder Yun crunched up, he turned to Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, transmit these orders. Have the quickest long ranged attackers stationed out front. Once the enemy comes, immediately attack them. We can’t have these cavalry units continuously chip at our troops.”

Fei’er nodded, then relayed the orders to the army. Before long, a disturbance happened in the army. The soldiers made way as groups of people bearing bows and arrows came forward. Not only were their attacks far reaching, they were also quick in moving around.

Just as the changes in the Divine Race’s troops finished, the fourth wave of cavalry came in. Seeing them approaching, the Divine Race’s archers immediately established their bow and arrow Domain. Naturally, they wanted to have the initiative and fire attacks towards the Ark Continent’s cavalry.

However, the Ark Continent’s cavalry unit weren’t fools. After seeing the Divine Race’s actions, they immediately turned around and ran, abandoning their plan to attack.

The archer units tried to pursue, but they just weren’t fast enough. When they came back, the same cavalry unit went forward. This caused the archer unit to attack once more, only to find that they really couldn’t catch up.

This exchanged happened several times. Finally, the archer troop soldiers became enraged. This time, after seeing the enemy retreat, they didn’t return to their army. Instead, they went forward and went all out in pursuing the enemy.

Thunder Yun also saw the actions of the cavalry unit, he was quite enraged as well. The Ark Continent’s actions were just too insulting. It was quite obvious that they weren’t intending on fighting full on combat. They seem to be intent on chipping away at the Divine Race Army.

Because of these actions, the archer troop couldn’t help but pursue. Thunder Yun didn’t prevent them. He wanted to see where these cavalry units retreat to.

However, Thunder Yun was quick to regret his decision. Not long after the archer troop decided to pursue, they were suddenly surrounded by huge undead. Although they were huge and skeletal, the undead were fairly quick as well. They didn’t follow the cavalry units, instead, they faced the archer troop. This made the archers stop, then they formed their formations, ready to meet the enemy’s attack. But at this time, a drastic event happened.

Chapter 769: Completely Empty

Just  as the Divine Race was done with their formation, the undead opened their mouths as a sudden burst of blue and red rays came out. These rays were shot directly into the formation of the Divine Race. Upon getting hit, the archers couldn’t help but be scrunched up with each other. One by one, dead bodies started to fall down. But something strange happened, those dead bodies disappeared as they fell down. Before long, the archer troops were being one sidedly slaughtered .

Thunder Yun quietly looked at the battle. The Ark Continent’s move was done beautifully. The ambush was not too far nor was it too close. It was just at the point that the Divine Race was able to see them but not too close for them to catch up. The action was just like a demonstration of the continent’s methods.

Thunder Yun was actually not enraged, he just calmly looked at what happened. To be honest, after the succeeding attacks, Thunder Yun understood what the Ark Continent was doing. They probably wanted to delay their advance as much as possible, thus the constant small attacks on the Divine Race army.

In his past wars, Thunder Yun had also encountered similar situations. But the lethality of the Ark Continent far surpassed those in the past. The attacks of the Ark Continent’s residents can actually cause casualties numbering from a hundred to over a thousand.

These scattered attacks might not look eye-catching. But it was actually a huge blow to the power and efficiency of the Divine Race army.

Thunder Yun might be calm, but his internal thoughts weren’t. The Ark Continent’s poking was truly different than the ones he encountered before. Although they were only attacked four times, they had already lost more than 10 thousand people. This might look small, but in the long run, this number would continually increase.

Moreover, those attacking them made Thunder Yun worry. Most importantly, Thunder Yun and the others weren’t actually aware of the true strength of the Ark Continent. There were two points of interest in what Thunder Yun just witnessed.

First was their mounts. Thunder Yun was a veteran in the battlefield, so he was clear about how strong 9th ranks were. It would be impossible for 9th rank experts to be that quick. The only explanation was their mount. Moreover, it seems like these mounts were something that had never been seen in the Ark Continent before.

The second were their cannons. Thunder Yun had already heard about the continent’s magic cannons. At that time, he didn’t really take it to heart. He knew how strong the magic cannons could be. Not to mention, the magic cannons of the Divine Race, even if they were meticulously made, were still quite weak in Thunder Yun’s eyes. Because of this, he really didn’t think too much about them.

But in this war, Thunder Yun’s knowledge had actually been overturned. He didn’t think that a common magic cannon in the Ark Continent would have this much might. This actually made him surprised.

Thunder Yun cannot just leave his people be slaughtered in front of him. He immediately sent people out to assist. But when they arrived at the site, the cavalry and undead had already retreated. Nobody was left.

Thunder Yun wasn’t very happy with this battle. He had just sent out 10 thousand troops, but when they returned, only about four thousand returned. This meant that the people of the Ark Continent had killed more than 5,000 people. This casualty wasn’t very small.

Thunder Yun frowned as he massaged his head. If they couldn’t deal with these attacks, then the 20 million man army wouldn’t be able to survive. They haven’t even gone far into the Buddha Empire, but they already lost 20 thousand people. Although it wasn’t relatively significant compared to the 20 million, one shouldn’ forget that all of these losses were incurred in just one day.

After some time, Thunder Yun turned to Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, what do you think we need to do?”

Fei’er’s deep voice answered, “Master, we truly haven’t encountered this situation before. Although the Ark Continent’s people have powerful weapons, this is the extent of what they can do.”

Thunder Yun smiled and said, “Good. Give the order to march. If they want to play around, then we’ll just hammer on. Swiftly take their homes. And once they decide to go all out, we’ll wipe them out in one go.”

Fei’er nodded and then spread the order as the army sped up their advance. However, it was a pity that their advance couldn’t become so fast. After all, this was a 20 million man army. If they wanted to speed up, it would be very hard for them to keep their formation.

If they want to maintain their formation, then they would have to carefully advance. But if they don’t, they will become separated groups, making it easy for the Ark Continent’s forces to poke them.

This was hard to deal with, and Thunder Yun knew that there was no solution. He only hoped then they would find the Ark Continent’s camp soon, then they would take their revenge.

The Radiant Empire wasn’t very far from Upper Bank City. If one were to fly fast, they would reach it in half a day. However, since Thunder Yun’s army was advancing, their march was slow. When they came to the city, it was already the afternoon two days later.

Thunder Yun knew that they cannot camp outside for too long. They weren’t in the Radiant Empire, where there were magic cannons protecting them. Here, in the Buddha Empire, they had nothing in terms of defense. If they decide to make camp, they would certainly be under attack by the Ark Continent’s cavalry units, and their casualties would only increase.

Because of this, they needed to reach Upper Bank city as soon as possible. When the army saw the city, their advance became quicker, they wanted to be behind the walls of a city as soon as possible.

However, Upper Bank city actually gave them a scare. Nobody was actually in it, it was completely empty, not even one mouse can be seen.

When Thunder Yun saw this, his expression couldn’t help but sink. He was already aware of Zhao Hai’s plan. Zhao Hai wanted to use the entire Buddha Empire to hamper the advancing armies in every step they take. From the moment they left up until now, the Divine Race army had already suffered 24 different attacks from the Ark Continent’s cavalry units. By now, the Divine Race’s losses has reached more than 30 thousand.

They had already lost 30 thousand troops but they were yet to touch even the hair of the enemy. This fact made Thunder Yun’s face ugly. Originally, he thought that the enemy would be in Upper Bank City and would fight with them when the army arrive. This way, the Divine Race would be able to let out a breath of relief.

Who would’ve thought that the enemy would never give them the opportunity to blow off steam. Thunder Yun looked at the empty city and breathed out a cold air. Just by seeing how swift the other party was, Thunder Yun could understand that they were formidable enemies.

Naturally, the Divine Race also had divine sense. Thunder Yun had repeatedly scanned the surrounding area, looking for something. Not only was the layout of the city good, even the area outside had criss crossing tunnels. This showed how important Zhao Hai regarded this city.

However, as soon as the Divine Race army came, they actually abandoned it. Such a move was something that ordinary people wouldn’t be able to do.

Actually, Thunder Yun was misinformed about the situation with the Ark Continent’s commoners. Except for the army, there were no commoners left in the Buddha Empire. This way, Zhao Hai had more flexibility in making his plans, just like abandoning a city. Since there were no civilians inside, then why would he go and defend it?

Thunder Yun didn’t know about this, so he was quite surprised when he saw the empty city. But after his initial surprise, his expression turned ugly. He knew that if he cannot eradicate the enemy camp, the sneak attacks wouldn’t stop. Whether it be day or night, the army wouldn’t have a single moment of peace.

Everyone looked at the city and didn’t know what to do next. All of them were very eager to rush into the city and kill all those cavalry units that were poking them. However, they found nobody, increasing the frustration that they currently felt.

After looking at the state of the city, Thunder Yun said with clenched teeth, “Enter the city and take a rest. Tomorrow we’ll charge through to the Ark Continent. I don’t believe those cavalry units would abandon the entire Buddha Empire. Also, arrange for night guards and patrols.”

Those who heard him gave a nod before arranging everything. However, the people that Thunder Yun had brought over were too many, they simply were unable to fit inside the city. Because of this, some of them can only stay outside. They made some houses with earth element magic and settled inside.

What made the Divine Race feel strange was the fact that since they entered the city, the attacks actually stopped.

But since the prior attacks gave them a headache, they still chose to continue being on alert. The army had sent forth 1 million troops in order to patrol the surrounding areas.

Bit by bit, the skies turned dark. Most of the Divine Race soldiers had already taken their rest. Although it wouldn’t be a problem for them to stay awake for several days, Thunder Yun was also aware of the effects towards their performance if they didn’t rest. When facing a sly enemy like the Ark Continent’s people, the Divine Race army would need as much rest as possible. Otherwise, they would just be courting death and humiliation.

Chapter 770: Zhao Wen Returns

Although it was already dark, the Divine Race were yet to experience an attack. However, Thunder Yun’s heart was still restless. He didn’t believe that the enemy would just do nothing. Seeing how they acted, it would be foolish for them to let go of this opportunity.

However, it was already dark, and the alarms outside were yet to sound out. Nothing came. What was the enemy doing?

If Zhao Hai was still harassing Thunder Yun’s army during the day, then Thunder Yun might not have been worried. After all, there was nothing notable about Zhao Hai’s tactics.

Now that Zhao Hai stopped, Thunder Yun couldn’t help but worry. Not understanding what the other party would do, plunging yourself in doubt was something that was dangerous to do.

Then suddenly, Thunder Yun became startled, he could hear a faint humming sound. In this silent night, the noise was quite distinct. Thunder Yun sat upright and concentrated on his ears. From what he can deduce, it was a sound of a mosquito. Mosquitoes, in majority of planes that he’d been in, were not very terrifying creatures, one could just kill them without even thinking about it. After being certain that it was a mosquito, Thunder Yun stopped caring about it and just continued sleeping.

However, this humming noise got louder and louder. Thunder Yun couldn’t help but sit still once more. He stood and loudly shouted, “Fei’er, what’s going on? Why are there so many mosquitoes in this city. Go and take a look.”

Fei’er, who was resting just outside Thunder Yun’s room, immediately stood up upon hearing his superior. Then he promptly went outside to take a look.

And just as Fei’er opened the door, he couldn’t help but breath in cold air. He was a God rank expert, but this was the first time that he witnessed the current situation.

In the skies above the city were large clumps of dark clouds. These groups of clouds were massive. Moreover, their shapes kept changing. What made him surprised was the fact that the sounds of humming were actually coming from these clouds.

Fei’er’s body immediately flew up towards the dark clouds. But when he was a hundred meters away, he stopped. He felt the hairs on his back stand up, the dark clouds were actually groups of mosquitoes, countless amounts of mosquitoes.

This was the first time that Fei’er had seen this many mosquitoes. And the most fearful thing about these mosquitoes was their size, they were too big. Each of these mosquitoes were the size of a human palm. Their bloody red color made those looking at them feel numb.

Most important of all, Fei’er recognized these mosquitoes. They were blood devouring mosquitoes, Divine Realm’s blood devouring mosquitoes. Even in the Divine Realm, these mosquitoes were fearful creatures. Naturally, a couple of mosquitoes weren’t a threat. But large clumps of them were a definite disaster in the Divine Realm.

Fei’er slowly retreated, afraid that he would agitate the mosquitoes. Because he was too scared of the mosquitoes, Fei’er wasn’t able to spot the spatial rift right in the middle of the clumps. The blood devouring mosquitoes were going out of this spatial rift in large quantities, further increasing the dark clumps in the skies.

When Fei’er was about a kilometer away from the mosquitoes, he immediately flew towards the city lord’s mansion. Thunder Yun was currently using the mansion as his personal quarters.

Thunder Yun was already up by now, standing outside looking at the sky. His face was drained of color as Fei’er gave his report, “Master, its the disaster mosquitoes. Everyone, wake up! Dangerous mosquitoes are coming!”

After hearing the two words, disaster mosquito, Thunder Yun’s face paled. He immediately turned to the sentries and bellowed, “Sound the alarm, quick!” Fei’er and the others immediately went towards the walls where the alarms were and sounded it with anxiety.

Dang, dang, dang. The sound permeated all throughout the Divine Race army. The soldiers immediately woke up and wore their armors as they went out of their residences. At this time, light mages simultaneously illuminated the skies of the city.

It didn’t take long before the army witnessed the large clump of blood devouring mosquitoes. All of the blood on their faces quickly receded.

Blood devouring mosquitoes were completely troublesome magic beasts in the Divine Realm. They didn’t expect that they would see these creatures in the Ark Continent, they couldn’t help but get scared.

At this moment, as though under command, the clump of blood devouring mosquitoes dispersed. Then all of the mosquitoes started to flood the city and its surroundings. The Divine Race couldn’t help but change their expressions upon seeing the incoming attack. They immediately established their Domains, hoping to block the attack of the blood devouring mosquitoes.

However, there were just too many mosquitoes, nobody can estimate how much. Just as the first wave were eliminated, the second wave replaced them and continued the attack.

These blood devouring mosquitoes seem to target certain people. There were some who only had few mosquitoes going after them while some were completely flooded. After some time, the overwhelmed soldiers found their Domains slowly crumbling.

As large amounts of mosquitoes hammer the Domains, the Divine Race soldiers couldn’t help but go pale. They immediately sent more energy to their Domains. They knew that once their Domains crumbled, the only fate waiting for them would be death!

Thunder Yun’s expression was quite ugly after seeing the mosquitoes. This quantity of blood devouring mosquitoes couldn’t be seen even in the Divine Realm. If these were to appear there, then they would surely be classified as a disaster.

Whether inside the city or outside, everybody was doing their best to kill the mosquitoes. The war between insect and people continued to wage on.

At this time, Zhao Hai was calmly sitting inside the Space while spectating the situation. Naturally, these mosquitoes were released by him. He had actually forgotten about the Space’s mosquitoes. Only when Zhao Wen returned after reaching God rank did Zhao Hai remember.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t expect Zhao Wen to get promoted this early. She was one of the bottom in terms of power among the carrions swamp’s beasts. The other 9th rank beasts have been cultivating for much longer than she did.

When Cai’er informed him that Zhao Wen had become 9th rank, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised.

As Zhao Hai summoned Zhao Wen back to the Space, he saw that nothing changed too much from Zhao Wen’s appearance. However, her strength had indeed reached God rank. This made Zhao Hai puzzled, as for Zhao Wen, she also said that she wasn’t very clear about it.

In the end, Zhao Hai reckoned that it might be because of the drop of blood that Zhao Wen drank. In the past, he deduced that the blood that Zhao Wen had drank might have come from the Divine Race. And since the blood contained great energy, Zhao Wen managed to reach 9th rank.

At the same time, upon taking Zhao Wen into the Space, she also gained benefits from its environment. Zhao Wen was the one who stayed in the Space the longest among the carrion swamp’s magic beasts.

With the Space’s environment and the blood of a God rank expert, not only could Zhao Wen reach 9th rank, she would only need time in order to get promoted to God rank.

Among the magic beasts of the carrion swamp, Zhao Wen was the closest one to Zhao Hai. She didn’t want to leave the Space, but for Zhao Hai, she decided to settle her heart and leave along with the other beasts. She wanted to return to Zhao Hai’s side as soon as possible. She wasn’t stupid, and she knew that as long as one becomes God rank, they would be able to go and stay by Zhao Hai. Therefore, she eagerly cultivated outside. Because of her persistence, she succeeded and became the first God rank among the magic beasts in the Carrion Swamp.

Sure enough, as soon as she broke through God rank, Cai’er immediately invited her back to the Space. If others were to be promoted, they might not have been able to do this. However, Zhao Wen wasn’t the same as the others, because of her relationship with Zhao Hai, she was immediately picked up and sent to the Space.

As Zhao Wen came back, Zhao Hai suddenly remembered a weapon that he had not used, the blood devouring mosquitoes. The Space can release an uncountable amount of them, it was a pity that they haven’t been used lately.

In the past, Zhao Hai was not able to use the blood devouring mosquitoes because he was fighting with the people in the Ark Continent. There really wasn’t any need, the undead were enough. After using them in the Prairie, the blood devouring mosquitoes haven’t been used later on.

However, they were now fighting the Divine Race, and the undead were proving to be insufficient against them. So when Zhao Hai saw Zhao Wen he immediately thought about the blood devouring mosquitoes. But he didn’t immediately make a move, he waited until night before launching an attack.

Zhao Hai was also unaware about how much mosquitoes he had sent out. He just knew that they were several times more than the Divine Race army. These blood devouring mosquitoes weren’t high ranked, and their attacks were weak. So even if they outnumber the Divine Race, they were still unable to completely wipe them out.

However, what confused Zhao Hai was the fact that when he released the blood devouring mosquitoes, the Divine Race actually identified them.

In Zhao Hai’s mind, the Divine Race shouldn’t be familiar with these mosquitoes. But after seeing their expressions, it seems like they were quite afraid of them.

Chapter 771: Blood Devouring Mosquitoes Levels Up

Zhao Wen was currently lying on Zhao Hai’s head, her small eyes looking at the monitor. Her body had changed after becoming God rank, her skin were now like crystals. As long as she lied motionless, it wouldn’t be strange if one were to assume that she was just a sculpture.

As Zhao Hai looked at the nervous Divine Race soldiers, he asked, “Little Wen, why are these soldiers very afraid of the blood devouring mosquitoes? Does you family have any connection to the Divine Realm?”

Zhao Wen shook her head and said, “Young Master, I had been in the Ark Continent the moment I was born. I don’t know anything about the Divine Realm.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The attacks of the blood devouring mosquitoes aren’t that weak, but most of the Divine Race soldiers should be able to endure. At the same time, the mosquitoes would disappear after getting killed 30 times. It seems like they won’t be a huge threat to the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai also learned just recently that there are also other ways to control the pests or mosquitoes aside from giving them a timed life. In this case, in future battles, the same mosquitoes will proceed to attack again and again until they are killed 30 times. The pests would be the same as well.

However, it was already astonishing. Thirty times, if each mosquito needed to be killed 30 times, what would that mean if there were 10 thousand? Ten thousand mosquitoes needed to be killed 300 thousand times. Then how about 100 thousand? A million? And the amount that Zhao Hai released today far surpassed a million. Remember, the Divine Race army numbered 20 million. If 20 million faced 1 million mosquitoes, then would they be afraid? No, Zhao Hai released more than 20 million blood devouring mosquitoes.

At this point, the blood devouring mosquitoes were flooding the skies in and around Upper Bank City. The Divine Race soldiers were also starting to get tired of keeping the mosquitoes off. Although nobody has yet to be injured, the mosquitoes were starting to get on their nerves.

Zhao Hai wasn’t idling right now. He was still in the Space ready to unleash another round of mosquitoes. After the current batch gets eliminated, he will release another.

Fantastic, Zhao Hai thought. He could only release mosquitoes once a Day. After using them, he wouldn’t be able to do so for another 24 hours. Moreover, the time to produce mosquitoes would only happen for six hours. Therefore, the attack can only happen before the daylight comes.

Although there were many limitations, Zhao Hai still thought that the mosquitoes were powerful weapons. Zhao Hai didn’t know how many mosquitoes the Space can release in six hours, but he knew that it would be very astonishing. During that time, the Divine Race would be in constant headache while dealing with the unending stream of blood devouring mosquitoes.

At this time, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but praise the strength of the Divine Race. Although a lot of mosquitoes were already killed, nobody from the Divine Race side had yet to die.

One must know that the mosquitoes needed to be killed thirty times before they disappear. Since casualties happened, then it meant that there were mosquitoes that have been killed for 30 times. It seems like the Divine Race really had skills.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t disappointed, he knew that casualties among the Divine Race were soon to pile up. Finally, a Divine Race soldier had their Domain broken through. Once the defense collapse, the blood devouring mosquitoes immediately threw themselves towards the vulnerable target. The Divine Race soldier went behind a protective shield, but it was useless. The mosquitoes broke through the shield and latched themselves to the soldier’s body. It didn’t take too long before a pitiful yell came from the soldier.

Zhao Hai stopped the mosquitoes from sucking the soldier dry. He was afraid that the lack of blood would stop him from turning the dead soldier into undead.

After being killed by the mosquitoes, Zhao Hai would immediately take the soldier’s corpse into the Space, then turn him into an undead.

It was at this point that Zhao Hai became surprised, just as the mosquitoes bit into the Divine Race soldier, the Space suddenly issued a prompt, “Space’s mosquito pests has absorbed blood of a powerful being. Blood devouring mosquito shall evolve. Mosquitoes promoted to 6th ranks. Every 24 hours, Host can release mosquitoes for seven hours. Mosquitoes can stay outside for ten days or after dying 40 times.”

Zhao Hai stared, then happiness immediately burst out from inside him. He didn’t think that the mosquitoes would level up like this. In other words, once the mosquitoes suck the blood of a powerful being, then they would level up. This was an extremely priceless piece of information.

Although the mosquitoes were only promoted to 6th rank, one shouldn’t forget that their might came from their absurd numbers. Moreover, the life force of the mosquitoes was very strong. Killing them wouldn’t be so easy.

A God rank expert might be fierce, but if they were flooded by tens of thousands of 6th rank beasts, then even they would fall eventually.

While the Divine Race were dealing with the mosquitoes, Zhao Hai was starting to turn his attention to another thing. After the mosquitoes get used up, he would have the cavalry units take over, launching attacks towards Upper Bank City as well as its surroundings.

At this time, Lizzy and Megan were actually handling another matter. They were going to attack the second group of Divine Race soldiers.

The Divine Race’s attack was divided into two parts. The first part was Thunder Yun’s center army, in charge of charging right through the city. Although they couldn’t eliminate Zhao Hai, they would make sure that he wouldn’t be able to help the other places. The second part of the attack were the heavy and light cavalry units, who were supposed to sweep the other Buddha Empire cities.

The heavy and light cavalries took of two hours after the center army left. This was done so that Zhao Hai would focus on Thunder Yun and his army.

However, they didn’t know that Zhao Hai was already aware of their movements. When the light and heavy cavalry units set out, Zhao Hai’s side was already prepared.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the capacity to deal with the two cavalries while he was dealing with Thunder Yun. Because of this, Zhao Hai handed the undead over in order to deal with the light and heavy cavalries. This way, he would be able to gain more undead while crippling two arms of the Divine Race army.

Lizzy and Megan were in charge of this matter. Since the light and heavy cavalries weren’t working together, they divided into two armies, one on the left and one on the right, as they went on and charge towards the heart of the Buddha Empire.

It would be impossible for Zhao Hai to take advantage of this opportunity. Although the heavy and light cavalries weren’t members of the Divine Race, their combat prowess wasn’t weak. Also, since they have been enslaved for too long, it would be impossible to turn them against the Divine Race. At this point, Zhao Hai’s only choice was to make them into his undead.

Once the heavy cavalry units become undead, all of them would reach 9th rank. When that time comes, their innate strength shouldn’t be any less than a God-rank expert.

The winged pegasus cavalry couldn’t be underestimated as well. Because of this, Zhao hai prepared to deal with the heavy cavalry first before going to attack the light cavalry units. After these two sides were dealt with, then Zhao Hai would proceed to slowly grind down Thunder Yun’s army.

At this point, Zhao Hai was tied up with Thunder Yun. So Megan and Lizzy were the ones preparing to deal with the heavy cavalry unit.

Although the heavy cavalry units were strong, they were still inferior to the Zhao Hai’s undead. One shouldn’t forget that Zhao Hai had undead beastmen cavalries. And since all of them were at least 9th rank, they weren’t very weak. They should be able to easily deal with the heavy cavalry units.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about Lizzy and Megan. With their talent and experience, they shouldn’t have any problems in defeating the two enemy cavalry armies. What Zhao Hai needed to do right now was cause as much headache to Thunder Yun as possible.

Besides these matters, Zhao Hai also needed to consider the Demon Race. Since Zhao Hai had changed his strategy, holding Rising Sun City wasn’t as important as in the past. However, there were still a large amount of people in Rising Sun City, preparing to delay the Demon Race’s advance by making them think that Zhao Hai wasn’t entangled with the Divine Race.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that they couldn’t hide this matter for several days. The Demons would certainly get news about the state of the Divine Race. When that time comes, they will immediately join the stage.

It was ideal for Zhao Hai if the Demons stayed put. This way, he would have sufficient manpower to use in dealing with the Divine Race. He needed some more time to damage the Divine Race’s army.

What Zhao Hai needed was time. He wasn’t afraid of fighting two battles at the same time. After adjusting their tactic, it didn’t matter whether the enemy was from the Divine Race or the Demons, it would work on both side. However, Zhao Hai would still need time in order to deal some damage on one side before the other started to move.

In the current Upper Bank City, the fight between the Divine Race soldiers and blood devouring mosquitoes was still going on. However, the Ark Continent’s cavalry had already arrived. They should have been attacking the Divine Race the whole afternoon and into the evening. But since the blood devouring mosquitoes were present, Zhao Hai gave them an order to take a rest. After they rested, they immediately came over to the city and prepare for another wave of attacks.

This time, Zhao Hai prepared a lot of troops to annoy the Divine Race. There were two million people including Humans, Elves, Beastmen, and Dwarves.

Although these 2 million couldn’t compare to the 20 million Divine Race soldiers, they were already quite large for an army who would be doing guerilla tactics. Once this army attacks the Divine Race from day to night, and then have the blood devouring mosquitoes take over, the Divine Race would soon lose their hair in frustration.

Chapter 772: Dealing with the Divine Race

Thunder Yun had lost count of the number of blood devouring mosquitoes that he’d killed. These mosquitoes seemed to be unkillable. After killing a batch, another batch would come, then another, then another.

In Thunder Yun’s mind, these blood devouring mosquitoes were more repugnant than the Ark Continent’s cavalry units. The cavalry unit would attack them while the Divine Race can do nothing. However, only those who were in the periphery of the army were attacked, those in the middle parts were completely unaffected.

On the other hand, the mosquitoes were different. There were just too many mosquitoes, almost everyone was under attack, completely hindering them from taking a proper rest. This situation would surely affect the Divine Race army’s fighting capabilities in the coming days.

There were already casualties among the Divine Race army. Although Thunder Yun didn’t know how much, he still couldn’t help but frown.

The attacks of the mosquitoes were different compared to those made by people. When people attack, you can counter them with proper group tactics. But the mosquitoes don’t care about formations. Their bodies were too small that once they attack, the battle would end up as individual fights.

Thunder Yun looked at the blood devouring mosquitoes. The insects were still attacking the army, however, it was evident that their numbers had dwindled. Compared to before, the pressure that they brought had become much lighter.

After seeing this development, Thunder Yun couldn’t help but let out a sigh of relief. But at this time, a huge explosion was suddenly heard. Thunder Yun became startled, he looked towards the explosion and spotted a group of Ark Continent cavalry. They had just thrown their javelins and were about to retreat.

Thunder Yun’s expression couldn’t help but sink. He didn’t think that the Ark Continent would actually use this opportunity to take a shot. This situation was too irritating.

Although he was completely infuriated, Thunder Yun didn’t have anything to say about it. This was war, and although the Ark Continent has been annoying, he still couldn’t help but recognize their ability to grasp at the opportunity to attack the Divine Race.

After thinking up to here, Thunder Yun couldn’t help but sigh deeply. He came out this time in order to face Zhao Hai, but he didn’t think that it would be very difficult. With how much he lost, his expression was uglier than Silver Shuke and Cloud Ying who were before him. The situation had completely left him with no face to return with.

However, this situation was still expected. Thunder Yun just didn’t think that the Ark Continent would have such methods. At the same time, he also suspected that the blood devouring mosquitoes were products made by someone in the Ark Continent.

The timing of the mosquito attack was very good. They didn’t encounter any attacks in the afternoon and into the night. And just as they lowered their guards, the mosquitoes suddenly appeared. It can be said that if the Ark Continent and the blood devouring mosquitoes weren’t related, then Thunder Yun was willing to cut his own head off.

After the group of Ark Continent cavalry left, another one came. They did the same as the one before them, threw their javelins before retreating. Afterward, a third team came, then a fourth, then a fifth…

While they were dealing with the remaining mosquitoes, the Divine Race army were faced with the attacks of the Ark Continent’s cavalry.

After about more than an hour, the amount of attacks that they had received have reached the same number as the attacks that they had suffered in the past few days. It can be said that the Ark Continent was waiting for this opportunity, and Thunder Yun can’t do anything about it.

Thunder Yun wouldn’t dare to send a detachment to attack the Ark Continent’s troops. This was because he knew that once he sends these detachment armies, they would immediately be slaughtered by ambushes coming from the enemy. They were truly in a dilemma right now.

Thunder Yun loudly commanded, “Troops in the periphery stand guard. The others, proceed to deal with the mosquitoes!” As he said that, the troops in the outskirts of the army focused on the Ark Continent’s cavalry while those in the middle went on and continued to attack the mosquitoes.

After two hours, the attacks that they received had surpassed those they encountered before. Moreover, their casualties were starting to mount up. In the 30 waves of attacks, nearly 40 thousand people were killed. Adding the damage caused by the residual mosquitoes, the casualties would number to 50 thousand. Moreover, it was clear that as they move through the Ark Continent, this number would continue to increase.

When the skies turn bright, the Ark Continent stopped their attacks. This made the Divine Race army relax and count their total casualties. In the evening, they lost 100 thousand people, when they add the casualties during the cavalry attack it would number to 150 thousand. In just one night, the Divine Race lost 150 thousand troops!

After hearing this number, Thunder Yun felt that he was in a dream. He was also hoping that he was in a dream, that all of these was just an illusion. But after he looked at his side and saw the weary look on Fei’er, he knew that it was real.

Thunder Yun rubbed his temples, then he turned to Fei’er and said, “Beat the drums, have the leaders gather.” Fei’er nodded, then he turned around and beat the big drum outside the city lord’s mansion.

Before long, several white robes people arrived. In the Divine Race army, only General rank people can wear white robes. It was a kind of status symbol for the army.

However, Thunder Yun liked to wear his battle armor, this made him different from the other generals. Generals in the Divine Race army took command of about five hundred thousand people, so 40 white robed people arrived at the city lord’s mansion.

Thunder Yun was sat down inside the mansion, there were also some chairs in front of him. All of these furniture were brought by the Divine Race. Zhao Hai already took everything before leaving the place.

After the Generals entered the door, they immediately gave Thunder Yun a salute before promptly taking a seat. Cloud Ying was among those who sat on the first row while Silver Shuke sat on the second.

After everyone arrived, Thunder Yun looked at them and said, “We’ve just begun, but we’re already stumbling. We underestimated the Ark Continent’s people, causing us to lose more than a hundred thousand people. For the Divine Race, this has never happened before. Everyone, tell me about your thoughts on the matter.”

Silence spread out inside the room, nobody knew what to say. After some time Cloud Ying opened his mouth and said, “General, I have something to report. We just fought with those blood devouring mosquitoes, and their numbers are surely large. But although they had been killed, nobody can spot a single mosquito corpse inside or outside the city. Everyone is puzzled by this.”

Upon hearing Cloud Ying, the other generals were giving nods. It was true, yesterday, they had fought with a storm’s worth of blood devouring mosquitoes. Although some of them were incinerated to ashes by fire element magic, there should still be corpses that remained. However, no corpse can be seen. This matter was too strange.

Thunder Yun nodded, “Right, I saw that as well. I’m also quite sure that the mosquitoes are on the side of the Ark Continent. Otherwise, the cavalry attacks would be too much of a coincidence. It seems like the Ark Continent still had a lot of methods they had yet to use.”

The expressions of those present couldn’t help but turn serious. They were generals, and they were no fools, they can accept almost any outcome. In yesterday’s war, not only were mosquito corpses not found, dead Divine Race soldiers were nowhere to be seen as well. Naturally, large part of that was due to being vaporized by the blood lightning beads, but there were also quite a number of those that were taken by Zhao Hai.

Cloud Ying frowns and said, “If those blood devouring mosquitoes are really on the side of the Ark Continent, then we have trouble. If they can make blood devouring mosquitoes, we need to think about ways to deal with it.”

Thunder Yun knit his brows and said, “Blood devouring mosquitoes aren’t easy to breed. Otherwise, the Ark Continent would have already used them a long time ago. However, we still need to be on guard. If we encounter more mosquitoes in the future, every soldier will group up into three man teams. One will support a Domain, one will kill the mosquitoes, and one rests. They will cycle through to minimize exhaustion. That way, the mosquitoes wouldn’t be too much of a threat. What we need to pay attention to are the Ark Continent’s cavalry units. Does anyone have any ideas in dealing their attacks?”

The group frowned, they went quiet for a while before one of them stood up and gave a bow to Thunder Yun and said, “General, I think we are too reliant on our Domains. Domains are indeed powerful, but their range is just too short, not enough to reach the range of thrown javelins. Because of this, we can only receive attacks and not retaliate. Therefore, I think that we should do the same as the Ark Continent’s cavalry. We cut some trees and make them into our own wooden javelins. Although we cannot place blood lightning beads inside them, at the very least, we can counter attack. With our God rank strengths, our throwing distance should be much further compared to the 9th rank cavalry. This will give us a means of counter-attack, and a way to threaten the other side.”

Upon hearing this person’s words, Thunder Yun’s eyes turned bright, he looked at the person and said, “Good Good, Cloud Yi, your idea is good. Although javelins wouldn’t be able to cope with the mosquitoes, they would be a threat to the cavalry units. Moreover, making them is very simple. Good, when everyone heads back, inform the soldiers to cut trees down and make them into javelins. If there are no trees to cut, get some stones and keep them. In any case, we can’t let them continue attacking us like this.”[1]

The people gathered in the room also thought that the idea was good. The disparity between God ranks and 9th ranks is very big. The javelins and stones that God-ranks throw would definitely be more powerful compared to those thrown by 9th ranks. When the time comes, the enemy cavalry would have no way to approach them. Even if the cavalry units doesn’t die, the Divine Race army could at least drive them away.

They weren’t thinking of eliminating all cavalry units with this method, it was impossible. The cavalry units were just too quick, such a method was completely useless. However, this will minimize their losses. As long as they aren’t afraid of the harassment of the other party, then they can continue on and charge towards the heart of the Ark Continent. When the time comes, the Ark Continent’s residents will have no other choice but to fight the Divine Race army head on!

* * *

Cloud Ying is Yun Ying. This guy was named Yun Yi.

Chapter 773: A Good Plan

Zhao Hai didn’t know about the contents of the Divine Race army’s meeting. The Divine Race used a formation in order to isolate the space surrounding them. This magic was quite effective against the Space.

Zhao Hai was currently looking into the Demons. He was afraid that the Demon Race would get any news and proceed to attack. He already had the troops in Rising Sun City show themselves regularly on top of the walls, hoping that the Demons would not suspect anything. But if the Demons did attack, these troops will immediately turn into cavalry units and proceed to harass the Demon army.

The current Demon army was no less than the Divine Race. They also numbered around 20 million troops. Moreover, more people were still coming from the Demon Realm.

At the same time, the continent’s armies were also quite numerous. Although there weren’t a lot of elite troops, the local armies were still collectively large . The local armies have now been promoted to 9th rank, their abilities shouldn’t be too far from the elite troops.

Besides the Human army, there was also the Elves, Dwarves, Beastman, and Fishman armies. All in all, the Ark Continent had about several tens of millions of usable troops. This was especially true for the Fishman race. Nobody knew how large the endless sea was, but one could be certain that the amount of Fishman tribes were a lot. The entire Fishman army, once they left the seas, will become huge war machines. Even the Mermaid Clan was unclear about their total battle prowess.

There were still many others who hadn’t taken the spatial water and were yet to be promoted. But Zhao Hai couldn’t do anything about it. Although he said that everyone can drink the spatial water, there will come a time when it would lose its effectiveness and just turn into normal water.

What Zhao Hai needed to do right now was to unveil the maximum warring potential of the Ark Continent and use it against the Demons and the Divine Race. It can be said that this was part of the Ark Continent’s evolution.

Right, the Ark Continent needed to evolve. Zhao Hai thought about it because of the recent changes to the continent. In the past, the Ark Continent was just a lower realm compared to the Divine Realm. But now, the Divine Race just removed that division. This meant that the Ark Continent and the Divine Race now had similar laws. Under this situation, if the Ark Continent’s people failed to adapt, then they will certainly be eliminated.

If Zhao Hai didn’t have the Space, then this evolution would certainly be impossible. But Zhao Hai had the Space, providing them with the ability to evolve. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to use this war to improve the entirety of the Ark Continent.

However, the situation with the other races was very different compared to the Humans. The Humans lived in a relatively concentrated manner, and their government had almost reached a perfect state. Take the Rosen Empire, for example, their governance was already first-rate. Their control of the population had even reached the tiniest unit, villages being governed by the village heads. On the other hand, the other races were different. The Elves and the Dwarves had it the best, living close to each other. However, the same cannot be said for the Beastmen.

The Beastmen lived in the Prairie, a place that was too big. Because of this, the Beastmen lived a fairly nomadic lifestyle, moving about in small tribes of several tens to several hundreds of households. In this case, wanting to concentrate them would be very difficult.

The Beastmen were just a tad less problematic compared to the Fishmen. The Fishman race lived in the endless sea, a place much bigger than the prairie, and much more difficult to manage.

In fact, the management of the Fishman Race was very relaxed. But all of them knew that the Mermaid Clan was the ruler of the entire sea. However, since the Mermaid Clan doesn’t care too much about taxes, the management had become too loose and neglected.

This caused Zhao Hai a headache. The Fishman Race was just too dispersed despite being the largest group in terms of population and war potential. Additionally, the Fishman Race weren’t too used to fighting on land.

Because of this, although there were a lot of Fishmen who had become 9th ranks, they were still not suitable for land battle. They were on the rear, training on top of the mounts that Zhao Hai gave.

At this time, the number of troops in the Buddha Empire numbered less than 10 million. But there were still more troops coming from the rear.

In fact, if Zhao Hai’s tactics were used, they really don’t need so many troops. However, Zhao Hai still wanted to see what a full on fight with the Demons and the Divine Race looks like.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation in the Demon Camp. Fortunately, it was still the early days of the Divine Race’s attack. Because of this, the Demons were yet to receive any news. However, Zhao Hai knew that word would soon reach their ears.

Seeing no movements from the Demons, Zhao Hai turned to look at what the Divine Race were doing. Upon seeing the Divine Race, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. The Divine Race army were cutting trees down and gathering stones. He was confused at what these people were doing.

However, he soon found out what this action meant. After cutting trees down, the Divine Race unexpectedly made javelins out of them. Although these javelins were simple, looking just like a sharpened wooden club, they were still quite lethal once thrown by the Divine Race army.

It was quite obvious that the Divine Race wanted to use these javelins to retaliate against the Ark Continent’s attacks.

After thinking up to this point, Zhao Hai’s brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. Although the strength of the Divine Race’s javelins were inferior to the ones with the blood lightning beads. The large number of the Divine Race army alone was something that cannot be underestimated.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shiver after imagining 20 million Divine Race soldiers throwing javelins simultaneously. Zhao Hai couldn’t forget the scene from the movie ‘Hero’ where a rain of arrows was seen going down on a city. He reckoned that the Divine Race’s javelins would be more frightening compared to the Qin army’s arrows. [1]

The Buddha Empire had a lot of trees, and for the Divine Race, they wouldn’t be very hard to cut For them, making javelins should be very simple.

Zhao Hai also understood what the stones were for. Judging by the sheer number of the Divine Race army, the javelins made would surely be insufficient. These stones were not only portable and easy to find, they could also deal significant damage once thrown. If these were thrown by any average person, then they might not be a threat, but in the hands of God ranked experts, they would surely be lethal.

Zhao Hai frowned, the Divine Race were too quick to think. Do they intend to deal with the cavalry attacks with this method?

As Zhao Hai was calmly thinking about it, Laura walked in and sat by his side. After seeing the monitor, she was puzzled so she asked Zhao Hai. “Brother Hai, what’s happening? Why are those soldiers gathering stones and wood? Do they want to build a city?” Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “They’re preparing to counter our cavalry attacks. The wood are made into javelins while the stones are to be thrown.”

When she heard Zhao Hai’s answer, Laura couldn’t help but frown. Zhao Hai’s cavalry units were yet to utilize their full 9th rank strength. Additionally, throwing javelins weren’t their speciality. Zhao Hai didn’t even order them to be accurate, throwing the javelins and then retreating was his only order.

Because of this, the cavalry units weren’t very skillful in their job. If they were attacked by these javelins, the only way they could survive was to abandon their mounts. And if they won’t, they would only be eliminated by the Divine Race.

Moreover, once the Divine Race uses this tactic, the harassment methods that Zhao Hai’s side had thought of would become useless.

Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what do we do now? Under these javelin and stone attacks, our cavalry units would be unable to continue their job. Using shields to block the Divine Race projectiles would not be enough.” Zhao Hai nodded as he sighed and said, “I’m also worried about this matter. God rank experts are much stronger compared to 9th ranks. God ranks are very difficult to deal with, especially those who already have Domains. The javelins thrown by the Divine Race would surely be strong. Only a few armies in the continent are able to block their attack.”

Laura frowned, but then her eyes shone, then she said, “Brother Hai, do you remember the magic formation disks used by the Radiant Church? If we make more of those, I think they can be used.”

Zhao Hai stared, “Formation disks? So what if we make formation disks?” Laura smiled and said, “Defensive formation disks. Major cities of the continent might have defensive formations, but these formations are very complex. If we shrink them down, then they can be used with formation disks. Each squad can carry a set of these disks and use it with crystal stones when they face the Divine Race. This should make the stones and javelins very useless.”

* * *

For those curious, here’s a clip from youtube.

Chapter 774: I Have a Way

When he heard Laura, Zhao Hai’s eyes lit up. He nodded and said, “That method is good. We should have them made as soon as possible. However, we still need to test these magic formations. They can’t be too big nor too small. Too big and they waste too much energy, too small and they become useless.”

Laura smiled and said, “This should be easy to do. At this point, your word is already law in the continent. Moreover, father has been researching magic formations for a very long time. I can hand the task over to him. We should expect results to come up soon.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, then we’ll hand it over to father-in-law. Tell him that we need it and we prefer them to be made as soon as possible.”

Laura nodded, “I’ll take care of it. But Brother Hai, we cannot stay put in the following days. How about we adjust Lizzy and Megan to face the center army. The javelins and stones might be a threat to the cavalry, but to the undead they should be less harmful.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, I’ll tell them after they deal with the heavy cavalry unit.”

Just as Zhao Hai said that, Lizzy’s voice was heard, “It seems like me and Megan came in at the right time. Big Brother Hai, the heavy cavalry unit has been taken care of.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to look and saw Lizzy and Megan’s excited faces. Zhao Hai immediately smiled at them and said, “You already took care of the heavy cavalry? How many people did they have?”

Although the majority of the reinforcements were composed of the Divine Race, the winged pegasus cavalry, and the rhinoceros heavy cavalry, there were also other races included in the mix. This time, these extra races weren’t included in the Divine Race’s center army. Instead, they were used to supplement the heavy cavalry army in attacking the other cities of the Buddha Empire. What Zhao Hai was asking about was the total number of people included in the heavy cavalry army, including those supplemental races.

Megan smiled and said, “There were a lot of them. You couldn’t even imagine. There were 5 million of them, 5 million.”

Zhao Hai immediately became ecstatic when he heard Megan, he said, “That’s fantastic. Then this means that we have 5 million additional undead. That is a huge harvest. Hahaha. And since the light cavalry unit have more people in comparison, our numbers will be greatly strengthened. Good, good. You two have a good rest before you deal with the light cavalry. Right, hand some of those undead over to me. I’ll use them to deal with the Divine Race’s center army.”

Lizzy and Megan nodded. Then they thought back to how difficult it was to deal with the heavy cavalry unit. The opponent wasn’t weak at all. Moreover, with their numbers, dealing with them in such a short time was very hard.

However, Lizzy and Megan had thought of a way. They would have Dwarves would dig some holes on the ground, making the heavy cavalry stop their advance.

The heavy cavalry’s greatest asset was their charge. Once their charge gets stopped, then they’re overall power would drop. The Dwarves’ traps were precisely used to stop them.

Once the heavy cavalry unit saw the traps, they quickly knew that it was set up by the Dwarves. It didn’t take too long for them to shoot out earth magic towards the ground. This magic had the effect of hardening the ground. It would last for an hour or so, making them unafraid of any attacks coming from the Dwarves.

However, their decision this time was very mistaken. Lizzy and Megan didn’t plan to attack them from the ground. Instead, they used the time where the enemy was using earth magic to surround them with undead. Then the undead began to attack the heavy cavalry.

These undead were quite strong, they were 9th ranks after all. Because of this, even before the heavy cavalry can respond, they were already eliminated.

This method can only be used because Zhao Hai’s side had the Space. They have the method of making the undead appear wherever they want. Lizzy and Megan used this feature to surround the heavy cavalry with undead. Catching them off guard and making the operation easier than it should be.

The plan might look simple, but it wasn’t. Fortunately, not a lot of people were aware of this capability.

Some of the undead were handed over to Zhao Hai while some remained in the control of Lizzy and Megan. The winged pegasus army were fast, and could fly, so they would need a much better plan to deal with them. This needed to be thoroughly thought out.

While Lizzy and Megan rested, Laura went out to discuss the formation disks with Karen. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai stayed in the villa in order to monitor the Divine Race.

Besides monitoring the Divine Race, Zhao Hai also busied himself with resupplying the cavalry units with more javelins..

There were currently a lot of places in the Ark Continent that took on the job of making javelins. In addition to wooden ones, there were also a lot of bamboo-made javelins. Those javelins made of bamboo were found out to be more powerful and convenient to use.

At this point, Zhao Hai planted a lot of bamboos in the Space, specifically for the manufacturing of javelins. Making bamboo javelins was simple. A single person would be able to make a lot of javelins in a single day.

Supplying the cavalry units was also a unique matter. Zhao Hai placed the supplies somewhere on the continent, then he would just lead the cavalry units there in order to take their javelins. At the same time, the cavalry could also eat and rest there.

These places varied, some were in cities of the Buddha Empire while some were in rural areas. The areas weren’t too complicated and the supplies present there were only enough for one or two batches.

Zhao Hai had also given the captains of these units a spatial bag each. Each bag can carry about a thousand cubic meters. In addition to the messenger fish, the bags also stored things to eat and drink. Zhao Hai didn’t want them to be starved during times where he was unable to teleport them from place to place.

Now that the cavalry units had received their supplies, they proceeded to take a rest. At the same time, the Divine Race army were also taking a rest. The blood devouring mosquitoes had made them suffer heavily.

Although the mosquitoes were upgraded, they still needed 24 hours in order to be re-released. But when the time comes, those new mosquitoes would be stronger than the ones before.

After being upgraded, the strength of the mosquitoes had doubled compared to before. Zhao Hai believed that the mosquitoes would deal a much heavier damage to the Divine Race the next time they attack.

Although the Divine Race army were composed of God-rank experts, Zhao Hai can still see weary looks on their faces. Those who had acquired their javelins and stones immediately took a rest. It seems like they were very tired.

However, there were still some of them who stood guard in the surroundings. Therefore, attacking them at this time wouldn’t be so easy. Still, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. If he really wanted to deal with the Divine Race army, he could just send some undead into the middle of the army. That would certainly catch them off guard.

But Zhao Hai didn’t want to do that right now. The Divine Race was different compared to the light and heavy cavalries. The Divine Race army have God-rank strength, making them much stronger than the two other armies. Even if the undead appeared in the middle of the army, their only choice would be to self destruct using blood lightning beads. Dealing with the Divine Race army using the methods used on the heavy cavalry would be a foolish decision, the strength disparity was just too much.

For Zhao Hai to not use it doesn’t meant that it was useless. On the contrary, this trick would be very useful. However, this trick can only be used once. The next time, the Divine Race would be prepared for it. Because of this, Zhao Hai planned to use it only when it is crucial.

Since that was his plan, Zhao Hai didn’t send people to harass the Divine Race right now, allowing them time to rest. But Zhao Hai also believed that even if they were resting, they would still keep one of their eyes open, fearing that an attack would come at any time.

After seeing that nothing was happening in the Divine Race’s camp, Zhao Hai felt relief. He took some time to head back to the Black Wasteland. At this time, many people who specialized in magic formations had been sent over. Karen was present there as well. Zhao Hai had a laboratory made for them so that they can research weapons and formations much easier.

After the plan for making formation disks were passed on to Karen’s group, they immediately started on their research. They were quite familiar with defensive formations. In fact, they already have ideas on how to proceed.

Ever since the Demons and the Divine Race started to invade the Ark Continent, these people were already thinking about these types of formations. Because of this, after Zhao Hai’s word was sent, they didn’t fumble around and just proceeded to shift their research towards Zhao Hai’s needs.

In the past, they have been researching ways to make more defensive and energy saving formations. This time, they only needed to make the formations small enough to carry around. Their research were focused on huge formations, so they had a certain understanding when it came to areas and their energy consumption. What they needed to do now was to make formation plates that have ample defensive strength for the cavalry units.

When he saw how smooth the research was going, Zhao Hai felt relief. It seems like it would only take a few days before the formation plates to be made.

Chapter 775: The Demon Race Moves, War On Two Fronts

Zhao Hai had also changed his methods from before. He now reported everything that happened in the frontlines. He would have Cai’er manufacture written documents to be given to the various powers, detailing what happened. This will give them a more direct understanding about the situation in the frontlines.

This would also make the various powers feel more involved in the fight and not too distant to what was happening.

While the Divine Race and Zhao Hai’s army were resting, the Demons were doing the contrary. The Demon Dragon King had received word that the Divine Race had already made their move. Upon receiving this information, the Demon Dragon King immediately convened his officers and notified them about the Divine Race’s action.

When they heard that the Divine Race had made their move, the various officers couldn’t help but be excited. One of them said, “Good, the Divine Race finally attacked! Your Highness, when do we advance?”

The Demon Dragon King was also smiling, he replied, “It has already been a few days since the Divine Race advanced. We might not know what happened, but there was no movement in Rising Sun City. I suspect that those left there are only the human army. Zhao Hai shouldn’t have the time to block our advance. Our opportunity has arrived!”

The group cheered. The Demon Dragon King looked at the group and said, “The sooner we dispatch the troops, the greater the advantage we can gain. At the same time, we must prepare to deal with the Divine Race. Just as Zhao Hai said, they might not agree to divine the Continent. We don’t agree to divide it as well. The strength of the Divine Race is no less than ours. Everybody should prepare well.”

The group simultaneously made a shout. However, each one of them still had their happy expression. The Demon Dragon King faintly smiled and said, “Go back to your armies. After one hour, we depart. Our target, Rising Sun City!” The group gave another loud shout before they turned around and left.

There was no Demon who came to the Ark Continent that didnt’ want to attack. This was because all of them wanted to make the Ark Continent their territory as soon as possible. After staying here for one day, nobody wanted to return to the Demon Realm.

After one hour, the Demon Army was fully prepared. And with the command from the Demon Dragon King, close to 30 million Demons left the Demonic Abyss, heading straight towards Rising Sun City.

However, the moment the Demons moved, Zhao Hai already ordered everyone inside Rising Sun City to leave. Nobody was left inside as they transitioned into doing guerilla tactics.

Using their harassment methods on the Demons should be more convenient compared to the Divine Race. This was because the Demon army didn’t have as much God-rank experts, so not a lot can support a Domain to block the blood lightning beads. Because of this, Zhao Hai held more confidence in dealing with the Demon Race.

Before long, the first round of harassment came. The Demons were not like the Divine Race, they don’t have as much God ranks. However, the abundance of God ranks and their Domains made the Divine Race think that long ranged weapons weren’t that important. On the other hand, since the Demons had 8th to 9th ranks, they equipped themselves with bows, javelins, and other throwable weapons. After losing more than ten thousand people in the first attack, the Demon Dragon King immediately made an adjustment. Those with ranged weapons would be placed on the outskirts of the Demon Army. Moreover, as soon as they saw the Humans, they immediately threw their weapons. This arrangement actually caused some casualties among the Human Race’s cavalry.

This caused Zhao Hai a headache. He didn’t expect the Demon Race’s archery to be this strong. Moreover, their firing distance was quite far. Because of this, Zhao Hai was very dissatisfied. Although they were still causing trouble for the Demons, Zhao Hai was still not happy.

This move by the Demons further pushed the importance of the formation plates. Zhao Hai discussed the matter with Karen, making them produce a working prototype as soon as possible. And with the Dwarves’ help, they need to make one at the quickest time possible.

Shortly after the Demons moved, the Divine Race had finished their rest and continued to charge towards the heart of the Ark Continent.

This time, Zhao Hai has to face enemies on two fronts. However, he was already prepared for this outcome. He immediately sent the undead that was handed over to him and harassed the Divine Race. On the other hand, there was no substitution for the Demons. The cavalry units still attacked them. Even if the damage made was low, at least the Demons weren’t advancing smoothly.

At this time, Lizzy and Megan led the undead and the other armies of the continent to deal with the light cavalry army.

The number of people assigned to the winged pegasus cavalry was about 7 million. Because of how fast the light cavalry units were and the fact that almost nobody can catch up to them, there were no other race that was placed in this army.

Zhao Hai actually wanted to use the winged pegasus as a mount for the cavalry. This was because they were very mobile.

However, Zhao Hai’s Space had just acquired some winged pegasus. It would be impossible to fit every cavalry unit with one. Although the Space can speed up the breeding of these winged pegasus, to reach a proper number was still far off.

Thunder Yun noticed that Zhao Hai had changed his way of attack. Before, their attackers were composed of Human soldiers, but now they were replaced by undead. These undead were also very fast, and their usage of javelins was actually more proficient and lethal compared to the Human soldiers.

Naturally, Thunder Yun wasn’t aware that the armies of the continent had just been promoted to 9th-rank, so they weren’t too proficient with their strength. On the other hand, the undead had already underwent battles in their current state, so they were more used to their bodies compared to the recently promoted soldiers. It was no wonder that the undead were more proficient in using the javelins.

But what worried Thunder Yun the most was how quick Zhao Hai was able to adjust. Zhao Hai was just too fast, it was as though he immediately figured out that the Divine Race had a way to deal with the Human cavalry. Just as Laura said, the javelins and the stones might be effective against living cavalry, but were less useful against the undead. Unless the javelin or stones hit exact places, the undead would remain unscatherd. The projectiles would just go through their bones as they continued to fight.

Moreover, Zhao Hai’s undead had self regeneration and pseudo-vitality. As long as their souls weren’t extinguished, these undead would stay immortal. In this case, the javelins and stones were rendered close to useless.

Thundery Yun didn’t know whether Zhao Hai was aware of their actions or this arrangement was just done in pure coincidence.

If Zhao Hai knew that the Divine Race planned to use javelins and stones, and promptly used his undead, then this meant that Zhao Hai had means to constantly look into the state of the Divine Race army.

While thinking about this possibility, Thunder Yun couldn’t help but be startled. He immediately scouted the surroundings, looking for places where people could hide.

However, they found nothing. This action only made their march slower, which allowed Zhao Hai more time. What Zhao Hai needed is time, time to eliminate the winged pegasus army, to research magic formations, to finish constructing the defensive line at Accra Mountain, and to promote more people to God-rank.

Naturally, Zhao Hai will not let the Divine Race go just because they slowed their advance. The undead cavalry remained and continued to harass the Divine Race army. Because the undead were never tired and didn’t need to eat nor drink, they attacked non-stop. And as soon as they reached the Divine Race’s line of fire, Zhao Hai would immediately take them into the Space. He would release them once more when their turn to attack comes.

Thunder Yun’s army was now advancing at the speed of a turtle. It would only need about three to four hours if one were to fly from city to city. However, it has already been five hours since Thunder Yun’s army left Upper Bank City, yet they were still halfway to the next city.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with this result. He was currently making every effort he could in order to delay the Demon and the Divine Race. After Lizzy and Megan eliminates the light cavalry army, Zhao Hai would then be able to allocate more resources into crippling the advance of the two enemy parties. At the same time, Zhao Hai had a more sinister idea in his mind. He would go and attack their rear!

As long as manpower gets available, Zhao Hai will have the undead winged pegasus army attack the cities in the Radiant Empire in the guise of zombies. When that time comes, Zhao Hai wanted to see whether the Divine Race would retreat or not.

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t think about driving the Divine Race back to the Divine Realm, that was just impossible to do. After seeing the giants, the winged pegasus, and the heavy armor cavalry, Zhao Hai knew that the Divine Race had already conquered several smaller planes. And in their operation in the Ark Continent, it was certain that they had made the proper preparations. To drive them back to the Divine Realm in such a short time was just not possible.

However, attacking the Radiant Empire still had its own advantages. First, they could compel the Divine Race army to retreat. Second, they would be able to acquire those large magic cannons and have them researched. And third, they would be able to get some green skinned creatures and ask them about the matters of the Divine Race.

But all of these relied on time. As long as Zhao Hai had time, he can make sure that the Divine Race never reached Accra Mountains.

The construction in Accra Mountain had increased a lot. It will become a permanent defensive line, so Zhao Hai’s requirements for it were very strict. Not only does it need magical formations, the materials needed to be selected properly as well. In addition to being resistant to physical damage, the materials needed to resist magic attacks as well as have magical effects. That is to say, using magic to break these materials was just plainly impossible.

Take Upper Bank City, for example. The city had a very good defensive formation, providing the walls with defense against magic. However, after the formation was broken, the walls were susceptible to being turned into golems by using earth magic. The walls will become weapons to attack the city’s defenders.

This situation needs to be prevented in Accra Mountains. Instead of stones, Zhao Hai asked for concrete to be used in making the walls. This concrete was different to the concrete back on Earth. The materials used for Ark Continent’s concrete comprised of things like gravel, rice milk, and some other things. Naturally, combining these things would need magic.

In the Ark Continent, magic-mage materials weren’t rare. There were a lot of materials that can be made using magic, but they weren’t used much in the past years. Only in making Imperial Palaces did these materials appear. Making concrete using magic was an idea that Zhao Hai had proposed.

Moreover, Zhao Hai had another requirement for the Accra Mountains. The defense lines must be done outward. This meant that the defense will be focused on the Buddha Empire. As for the Lyon Empire’s side, no defense shall be made.

The reason that Zhao Hai made this decision was because he was afraid that if Accra Mountain fell, then its defense would be turned against the Ark Continent. If Zhao Hai made both sides of the mountain defensive, then the Divine Race or the Demon Race might use it as a forward base against the Ark Continent. When that time comes, reclaiming the land would become much more difficult.

This method had its advantages and disadvantages, but Zhao Hai can only do it. Before doing so, he also discussed this matter with the Buddha Emperor. He wanted to make it clear that this arrangement wasn’t against the Buddha Empire, but to the invaders instead.

Chapter 776: Skill

In the past, Zhao Hai didn’t consider the people of the Ark Continent in his decisions. The only things in his mind was the Buda Clan, everything is for the betterment of the clan.

But in his current position, he found out that there were more things to consider. Just take the matter with the Accra Mountains, for example. If it wasn’t properly taken care of, then it might result in the dissatisfaction of the Buddha Empire.

Although the Buddha Empire had moved to the Lyon Empire, Zhao Hai had to hand a city over to the Buddha Emperor. This was done in order for the Emperor to be able to rule his people. One could see how sensitive matters like these were to the Buddha Empire’s people.

Even if they were forced to leave their country, this only intensified their feelings about it. By making a demarcation in the Accra Mountains, Zhao Hai just cut the continent into two. The internal part would start from the Lyon Empire and then moving forward. The outer part would be the Buddha Empire and the Radiant Empire. Those people in the internal part naturally wouldn’t have any issues with this. After all, this was done in order to combat the Demons and the Divine Race.

On the other hand, this decision would make the people of the Buddha Empire feel bitter. Cultivating the Accra Mountains as a wall made the people of the Buddha Empire think that Zhao Hai had already abandoned their home. This was akin to handing the Buddha Empire over to the Demons and the Divine Race.

This didn’t even include what the Buddha Emperor would think. If Zhao Hai were to repel the Demons and the Divine Race one day, then the Accra Mountain defense could be seen as a protective guard against the Buddha Empire.

Because he was afraid of the Buddha Emperor having this idea, Zhao Hai talked this matter with him when the construction started. He even promised the Buddha Emperor that once the Demons and the Divine Race were expelled, the Lyon Empire would not place any garrison troops inside Accra Mountains.

All of this was made in the name of stability. Only when everything was stable would the fight in the frontlines be smooth.

Although the Buddha Empire’s people were living under refuge right now, their influence was still quite significant. This was because they had given up their country for the sake of the Ark Continent. Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to give them preferential treatment. Otherwise, the other nations would feel that Zhao Hai had been unfair.

The various Emperors were on the side of the Buddha Emperor. How Zhao Hai treated the Buddha Emperor right now would be how he would treat them in the future. These Emperors knew how strong the Demons and the Divine Race were, so they were aware that repelling them wouldn’t take a short time, it was just impossible.

They were afraid that a day would come where the invaders would rush over Accra Mountain’s defensive line. They were afraid that they would have the same fate as the Buddha Emperor. If Zhao Hai didn’t treat the Buddha Emperor well, then they wouldn’t be expecting Zhao Hai to treat them well in the future. Maybe they would even think that Zhao Hai would just eliminate them and consolidate control over the entire Ark Continent.

Although Zhao Hai’s present strength allows him to dethrone the Emperors and control the continent, he didn’t want to do this. The Emperors and Great Nobles had been ruling their respective subjects for several thousand years. It can be said that their influence in the continent had already been ingrained in the hearts of the people. Wanting to abolish their rule wouldn’t be very easy.

The reason why Zhao Hai was able to quickly control the Lyon Empire was because their Royal Family was killed by the Dragons. The strength of the Dragons had also left a huge impression on the commoners. So after Zhao Hai eliminated the Dragons, the Great Clans of the Lyon Empire had no choice but to become his subjects, otherwise they would face ruin in the hands of the commoners.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to tell the people of the continent about his arrangements. He had no choice, otherwise the aristocrats of the continent would unite against him. When that time comes, the whole continent would be plunged into chaos. Not to say about the Demons and the Divine Race, the continent might even disperse because of infighting. Zhao Hai had no choice but to consider all of these whenever he made a major action.

The reason why Zhao Hai can say that there would be no Lyon Empire garrison on Accra Mountains in the future was because he was still the Emperor of the Lyon Empire. One shouldn’t forget that the Buddha Empire and the Lyon Empire were divided by the Accra Mountain.

Not having garrison on the Accra Mountains might also mean that the defense would be handed over to the Buddha Empire. Naturally, the Buddha Emperor have no problems about this.

Actually, Zhao Hai didn’t want to hand the Accra Mountain over to the Buddha Empire nor would it be under the hands of the Lyon Empire. After they repel the Demons and the Divine Race, Zhao Hai plans to hand the defensive line over to the Dwarves and the Elves.

The passage between the Dwarf Mountain and Elven forest passes below the Mountains. If either the Buddha Empire or the Lyon Empire takes control of the mountains, then this would mean that they would have a certain influence over the Elves and the Dwarves.

Naturally, he wouldn’t tell this plan. He just told the Buddha Emperor that there would be no Lyon Empire soldiers stationed on the mountain after the war. However, he didn’t explicitly say that the mountain would be handed over to the Buddha Empire. If the Buddha Emperor thinks so, then that won’t be Zhao Hai’s problem anymore.

This was a type of deception, a deception that must be used since it was necessary. After all, the Buddha Empire wasn’t loyal to Zhao Hai. Therefore, some small deceptions needed to be made in order to achieve certain goals.

Besides the frontline and backline matters, Zhao Hai also took care of the reports that Cai’er would send. In addition to the heads of the powers, these reports would also be read aloud in various cities. This would allow the commoners to know about the situation in the frontline.

Zhao Hai still continued to stabilize the spirit of the people. Just like how he needed to appease the heads of states, he also needed to make sure that there weren’t wrong rumors going about among the populace. Rumors like ‘the frontlines couldn’t defend, ‘Zhao Hai is heavily injured’, and ‘The Demons and the Divine Race have come’ needed to be quelled.

Nonsense rumors like these would only cause anxiety to the people. Moreover, there were also a lot of soldiers in the continent that were originally commoners. Therefore, these people needed to be made aware of the war’s progress.

The reason why Zhao Hai didn’t bother doing this before was because he was yet to transfer troops from the continent into the Buddha Empire at a large scale. At that time, the people involved in the war were only those who were from the Buddha Empire, some armies from the three Empires, and groups from the other races.

However, now was different, Zhao Hai was mobilizing the entire Ark Continent. Although he had improved the strength of the soldiers, it was still impossible for them to not be worried about the frontlines. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to read out the reports to the civilians, informing them about the war.

Zhao Hai was not afraid that his plans would be exposed to the Demons and the Divine Race. After all, what he was doing was just stalling the enemies. It was a kind of information that nobody can make use of. The enemies might know about his plan, however, what can they do about it?

Whether it be the Demons or the Divine Race, both of them were subjected to Zhao Hai’s delaying tactics. Zhao Hai used his undead for the Divine Race while the cavalries were used against the Demons. This arrangement was right. Although the strength of the Demon army wasn’t that great, they were beings completely unafraid of death. With their powerful life force, even general 9th ranks from the continent would be unable to play around with them.

Although using the cavalry against the Demons caused some lives to be lost, it was still better than facing the Divine Race. Zhao Hai can imagine the large losses that would be met if he continued to use the cavalry units against the Divine Race.

The javelins and stones from the Divine Race were very lethal. Even undead fell to them, much less actual living people.

Actually, the heavy cavalry unit can be said to be the most appropriate enemy against the Divine Race. Their inborn strength would bring them more throwing distance compared to the others. They might even compare to the Divine Race’s projectiles.

However, Zhao Hai cannot send them right now because he needed to deal with the winged pegasus cavalry. Once Zhao Hai sends the heavy cavalry, the Divine Race would know that Zhao Hai was planning on dealing with the winged pegasus cavalry next. This would allow the Divine Race to adjust their strategy, making the situation unfavorable for Zhao Hai. Therefore, Zhao Hai could only use the undead to deal with the Divine Race. Fortunately, the undead were already enough to slow the advance of Thunder Yun’s center army.

The Demons and the Divine Race were still advancing, but their rate of advancement was horribly slow. The Divine Race wasn’t expecting this move from Zhao Hai, they didn’t bring too much supplies when they left the Radiant Empire. Although their supplies can lest them for another one or two days, it was already clear that their supplies wouldn’t last for too long. When they decided to get supplies from the Radiant Empire, then that would be the time where Zhao Hai’s undead cavalry would make their attack.

Zhao Hai has been paying attention to the moves of the two armies. Now, 24 hours had almost passed by, Zhao Hai was preparing to unleash the blood devouring mosquitoes once more. When the time is up, the mosquitoes would be released immediately. This time, the blood devouring mosquitoes wouldn’t only assault the Divine Race, they would go for the Demons as well.

Chapter 777: Thunder Yun’s Thoughts

It was more advantageous to use the mosquitoes during the night. Since it was still daytime, Zhao Hai only gathered them in the Space. When night comes, he would unleash them to deal with the Demons and the Divine Race.

Honestly, the time of day didn’t really affect the Demons and the Divine Race too much. However, even a small advantage needed to be used, so Zhao Hai chose to wait.

This time, he wouldn’t have the blood devouring mosquitoes attack on their own. Instead, Zhao Hai planned to have his cavalry carry on attacking as well. It was necessary to exhaust the Demons and the Divine Race as much as possible. When Lizzy and Megan eliminates the  winged pegasus cavalry, then Zhao Hai would have more chess pieces to move on the board.

Eliminating the winged pegasus army would provide Zhao Hai with millions more undead. Once that gets accomplished, Zhao Hai would have more things to do with the cavalry. For example, he could completely disrupt the supply line of the Divine Race, he could even go and harass the Radiant Empire. On the other hand, there was no need to be afraid of the Demons. Although they were strong, they weren’t much stronger compared to the undead. If an undead dies, it would definitely take another Demon along with it. This trade of losses wasn’t something that the Demon Race can withstand.

Zhao Hai looked at the monitor while making orders towards the cavalry units from time to time. At the same time, he would also lead the undead in making their attacks.

Zhao Hai currently felt like he was playing a computer game back on Earth. On the screen were green and red dots. The red dots would be his people while the green ones represented the enemy. At this time, groups of red dots were advancing and retreating on the monitor.

There was also a huge mass of green dots. The smaller group of red dots would come in contact with these green dots once in a while, some green and red dots would vanish at each encounter.

Zhao Hai didn’t feel too much after seeing the red and green lights vanish. Although he knew that each dot that disappeared meant a life was ended, he understood that this was war. Loss of life was inevitable in these situations.

Aside from the Demons and the Divine Race’s camps, Zhao Hai was also paying attention to Lizzy and Megan. This didn’t mean that he was worried about their success, he knew that the two of them would succeed in this operation. What he was paying attention to was how long it would take to eliminate the winged pegasus army. The sooner they get killed, the more advantageous it would be for Zhao Hai.

But he didn’t urge Megan and Lizzy to go faster, he knew that the two were already doing their best. There was no benefit in making them anxious about their success.

The skies slowly turned dark, and Zhao Hai knew that the time to dish out huge damages had come. He immediately had his cavalry units withdraw for some time so that they would be in their best condition when night came.

Actually, these cavalry units weren’t very tired at all. After a group attacks the Demons, they would just retreat and resupply while at the same time taking a rest.

Zhao Hai’s arrangement was to keep them in the best condition. And now that casualties were happening, Zhao Hai took their corpses and kept them, not turning them into undead. On the other hand, the dead ferghana horses were turned into undead. Not only would they keep their strength, their endurance would also be improved by a lot.

As the skies turned dark, the Divine Race were also beginning to get their guards up. First was because undead creatures can display 120% of their strength during the night. Second, because the Divine Race were expecting the blood devouring mosquitoes.

They were terrified by yesterday’s attack. Although they had thought about means to deal with the mosquitoes, the mere idea of the attack made them extremely uneasy.

After seeing the wave of undead retreat, Thunder Yun turned to Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, how many attacks did we receive today?”

Fei’er turned to Thunder Yun and smiled bitterly, “Forgive me master, I lost count.”

Thunder Yun smiled bitterly as well, he couldn’t blame Fei’er. The undead attacks that they received was just too much. Just as one ten thousand troop retreated, another would come. In this case, it would be strange if they had kept count.

After watching the sky, Thunder Yun immediately said, “Spread this order, immediately find a place to rest and arrange sentries. Have everyone be extra careful. If the blood devouring mosquitoes are indeed under the enemy’s control, then they would come back this evening.”

Fei’er nodded and then went to arrange it. Thunder Yun looked at the horizon with a worried look. Since their advance was slowed, Thunder Yun took the chance and observed the undead.

After looking at the teams of undead that Zhao Hai sent, Thunder Yun had discovered that there weren’t a lot of them, probably about a few million. Thunder Yun was assured of this conclusion because he can see the same faces among the undead from time to time. After his calculations, Thunder Yun reckoned that there shouldn’t be more than 5 million undead.

However, from the information that he acquired from Cloud Ying, Zhao Hai had a minimum of 20 million undead. He only used 5 million this time, where did the others go?

More than 10 million undead wasn’t small, but they haven’t appeared yet. Thunder Yun thought of the various implications of this information.

After the Divine Race army stopped, they immediately built rooms with earth magic. Thunder Yun also had a command center made. Once inside the hall, Thunder Yun had Fei’er sound the drums.

When all the generals arrived, Thunder Yun glanced at Cloud Yi and said, “Cloud Yi, sit on the third row.”

Don’t underestimate this change of seating, this was essentially a promotion. When Cloud Yi heard Thunder Yun, he immediately stood up and sat on the third row. Everyone in the hall looked at Cloud Yi, but nobody said anything. Cloud Yi came up with the method to restrict the harassment. Although it wasn’t completely useful, it still played a big role. Getting a promotion at this time was normal.

Seeing that nobody opposed to it, Thunder Yun moved on, “Everyone should have noticed, the Ark Continent had changed from cavalry soldiers into undead. Does everybody know why?” The people in the room all frowned. Then Cloud Ying said, “There are two possibilities for this. One was coincidence, and the other is Zhao Hai knowing our plan. If it is the former, than we’ll be fine. But if it is the latter, then this means that every move we make would be known to the other party. And that isn’t good for our future plans.”

When the generals heard this, their brows couldn’t help but wrinkle. They were experienced war veterans, but since they were too preoccupied with thinking about the undead, they had missed this point. After hearing Cloud Ying, all of them immediately understood.

Although they can understand what this meant, this was still very bad news. Knowing all of their actions wouldn’t bode too well for this conquest.

Thunder Yun nodded and said, “Right, and I suspect that the second possibility is true. Our moved are under Zhao Hai’s surveillance. As for his methods, I have absolutely no idea. But there is one thing worries me more.” After saying that, Thunder Yun scanned the group. All of them had unclear expressions aside from three people. They were Silver Shuke, Cloud Ying, and Cloud Yi.

Thunder Yun couldn’t help but nod after seeing the expression of the three. And among these three, the one who he favored the most was Cloud Yi.

Cloud Ying and Silver Shuke had fought with Zhao Hai before, so they were very clear about his strength. For them to discover the strangeness of the undead was quite normal. But Cloud Yi was different, he had not fought with Zhao Hai. In addition to his understanding now, he also managed to formulate a way to deal with the cavalry harassment. This meant that Cloud Yi had a powerful gift of observation.

However, Thunder Yun kept himself from asking Cloud Yi. He knew that if he asked Cloud Yi about this matter, then the others would think that he favored Cloud Yi and was planning to promote him even more. This wasn’t good for troop morale.

Cloud Yi’s promotion was because of his advice, so nobody would oppose this point. But if Thunder Yun were to blatantly give a promotion, then it would attract the envy of other people. When the time comes, Cloud Yi might even be bullied in the future, hindering his talent from growing any further.”

Therefore, Thunder Yun turned to Silver Shuke and said, “Silver Shuke, tell me, did you notice anything strange about Zhao Hai’s action?”

Chapter 778: Thunder Yun’s Plan

Thunder Yun decided to ask Silver Shuke and not Cloud Yi. This was because in the first fight with Zhao Hai, Silver Shuke was the first to fail, and he had been feeling bad about it.

In the beginning, Thunder Yun didn’t look too highly on Silver Shuke. But after these few days, Thunder Yun changed his mind. Zhao Hai really did have the strength to cause them losses. In this case, it wasn’t surprising for Silver Shuke to fail.

Because of this, Thunder Yun decided to help Silver Shuke out. He used this opportunity to ask him the question, giving him some credit and making it known that Thunder Yun wanted to use him in the future.

Silver Shuke didn’t expect Thunder Yun to say his name. He was stunned for a moment before a flash ran by his eyes, he immediately replied, “Yes, General. I noticed something strange.”

After seeing Thunder Yun choose Silver Shuke, Cloud Ying and Cloud Yi couldn’t help but have a momentary look of disappointment in their eyes. Although their faces were serious, the change didn’t escape the eyes of Thunder Yun.

Thunder Yun didn’t say anything, he just looked at Silver Shuke and said, “Tell me.”

Silver Shuke immediately replied, “General, from what I can see, the number of undead this time isn’t right. Zhao Hai has more than ten million undead, but the ones attacking us right now seem to number in the few millions. The number was just too small, and the others were nowhere to be seen. I think there are only two possibilities for this, the first one being the undead attacking our headquarters. Now that our army has departed, the forces back in the Radiant Empire wouldn’t be as good compared to before. Even if they couldn’t break the camp, they could at the very least cause some damage. However, we haven’t had any rescue letters in the past couple of days. This might be because the base hasn’t been attacked, or they couldn’t send a rescue letter. I think the former is more plausible. We still have a lot of strong soldiers in the camp, and it would be impossible for them to be unable to send a letter in case of the attack. Therefore, the base is still safe.”

“The other possibility for the undead’s disappearance might be because they are dealing with the barbarians and the winged pegasus people. If they could indeed see our actions, then it is possible that they are already aware of the two armies. If that is really the case, then we might be in even more trouble.”

Thunder Yun nodded, Silver Shuke’s analysis coincides with his own. But Thunder Yun discovered that Cloud Ying was still frowning, he probably had some words to say.

Thunder Yun looked at Cloud Ying and said, “Cloud Ying, do you have any other ideas? Say it.”

Cloud Ying looked at Thunder Yun and nodded, “General, I have thought of another possibility. We know that the Demons have also come to the continent, and their fighting strength is also quite good. It’s certain that the Demons would dispatch their troops once they discover that we have made out more. Zhao Hai might have brought his undead to deal with the Demons.”

Thunder Yun looked at Cloud Ying, then he smiled faintly and said, “That is correct as well. However, you have missed something. Zhao Hai replaced those cavalry units with the undead. And where are those cavalry units now? It would be impossible for Zhao Hai to just have them lying around. If he can harass us, then why can’t he do the same with the Demons? It’s more plausible that he had the cavalry deal with the Demons while his undead goes on and attacks the barbarians and the winged pegasus people. Zhao Hai’s only enemies are us and the Demons. And this time, I’m sure the Demons didn’t split their army like us. They arrived in the Ark Continent much earlier than us, so they should be more experienced when it came to Zhao Hai’s capabilities. And I also heard that the Demons aren’t as strong as us, therefore they couldn’t afford to split up their army. At this moment, in the Buddha Empire, Zhao Hai has four groups of enemies. The strongest two of those four are us and the Demon Army, the weaker ones are the barbarians and the winged pegasus army. Zhao Hai would surely eat the weaker ones first before going to deal with us. This is his safest and most beneficial method right now.”

Everyone who listened to Thunder Yun’s breakdown started to believe his words. After all, Thunder Yun already had the qualifications to make speculations like these. Although he had eaten a loss lately, his status remained unchanged in the hearts of these people.

Therefore, everybody nodded at Thunder Yun’s analysis, nobody voiced opposition. Cloud Ying said, “The General is right, forgive me for being wrong.”

Thunder Yun just waved his hand. Although he just said that the barbarians and the winged pegasus people were going to eliminated, he still had a calm look on his face. This made everyone confused.

Cloud Ying looked puzzled at Thunder Yun’s expression, so he asked, “Isn’t General worried about the barbarians and the winged pegasus army? Is the General confident in them beating Zhao Hai?”

Thunder Yun actually laughed before he answered, “How is that possible? Although I haven’t we haven’t had a true clash with Zhao Hai, his recent actions are already proof enough to how strong he is. How could the barbarians and winged pegasus armies be able to beat a person like him? If I haven’t guessed wrong, then the barbarians should have already been eliminated while the winged pegasus army shouldn’t last for long. However, this is exactly what I want.”

Thunder Yun’s words made everyone present stare. Some of the more intelligent among them immediately understood what Thunder Yun meant.

Thunder Yun smiled faintly and said, “Does everyone understand? Cloud Yi, tell them. You look like your ass is on fire, you tell them what I mean.” As soon as they heard Thunder Yun, the group couldn’t help but chuckle. The heavy emotions that they carried all this time seemed to slowly vanish.

Cloud Yi stood up and bowed to Thunder Yun before saying, “The general is talking about how vengeful both the barbarians and the winged pegasus people are. After the Divine Race subjugated them, they were still quite resistive to our rule. Therefore, when we asked them for troops this time, they initially refused. Although they gave us some troops, they only gave us two of their ordinary armies, no elites were included. But now that Zhao Hai had killed their people, these two would surely bear a grudge and send their elites over. When that time comes, we would be more relaxed in dealing with the Ark Continent.”

Thunder Yun laughed and said “Good, correct. Just as Cloud Yi said, both the barbarians and winged pegasus clans bear deep grudges. They will surely retaliate against Zhao Hai now that he has killed their people. Once they send their forces, then we would have more powerful cannon fodder for our army.”

The people in the hall smiled, their low morale had surged up. On the other hand, both Cloud Ying and Cloud Yi were looking at Thunder Yun with admiration. They knew that Thunder Yun’s purpose today was to raise morale.

Cloud Ying also understood Thunder Yun’s idea, he looked at Thunder Yun and said, “General, what do we do next?’

Thunder Yun’s voice turned serious as he said, “In the last two days, the Ark Continent showed that they don’t intend to go directly against us, just resorting to harassment tactics and forcing us to be on the defense. Because of this, I plan to withdraw the troops tomorrow and see if the barbarians and winged pegasus people are indeed killed. If they are, then I will immediately send word to the two races, making them dispatch their troops. The winged pegasus mounts are insanely fast, there would be no way the mounts of the Ark Continent’s cavalry would catch up to them. Moreover, the barbarian elites are vastly stronger than the people in the Ark Continent. As long as the elites come, then we can deal with the Ark Continent in one go!”

If Thunder Yun hadn’t said his plan, then the morale might’ve drop when he suggested retreat. But since he made a cushion for himself, the situation became different. Now, instead of dropping, the moral actually increased. Those present were thinking that their retreat this time was done in order for them to mount an even stronger attack. They had been feeling suffocated from the attacks coming from the Ark Continent. Now, they couldn’t wait to go all out, this was the result that Thunder Yun wanted.

Being a good General doesn’t only depend on how many wins one can get, it also depends on how one deals with their adversary. Cloud Ying and Cloud Yin knew that if they were in Thunder Yun’s shoes, then they wouldn’t have a spectacular result as this. There were some times where a strategic defeat meant losing. But their retreat this time was different, they would retreat only because they were preparing to launch a better attack.

An example of this happened in the civil war after the Sino-Japanese war. It was when the party had to give up the headquarters at Yan’an. This might look like a big defeat. But this retreat had conserved the party’s strength. Moreover, it didn’t affect their morale at all. In the end, this move was marked as the party sacrificing Yan’an in order to acquire the whole of China.

Chapter 779: Thunder Yun’s Discovery

Naturally, Zhao Hai didn’t know about Thunder Yun’s plan to withdraw their troops. But even if he did know, he still wouldn’t let Thunder Yun off. After all, his hatred for the Divine Race was too deep, as long as he gets to kill them, then he would do it.

Therefore, after darkness comes, he would immediately release the blood devouring mosquitoes; half to the Divine Race and half to the Demons. At the same time, he also had the cavalry and undead prepared for another wave of attacks

.Zhao Hai looked at the sky, the Divine Race have pitched camp and their officers met up. It was time, Zhao Hai immediately sent the mosquitoes towards the Divine Race camp.

Thunder Yun and the others were currently discussing about their retreat when suddenly Fei’er came in from the outside. His face was ugly as he reported, “Master, the blood devouring mosquitoes have appeared.”

After hearing Fei’er, Thunder Yun’s expression changed. What he was worried about came true, the blood devouring mosquitoes were indeed under the enemy’s control. Moreover, their numbers are quite large.

However, this wasn’t the time to think about these, he immediately said, “Give the orders, do what I said earlier. Three people will form one group. Tell them not to panic. It’s possible that the enemy would use his undead to attack. Everyone, return to your divisions.”

Although they were just laughing earlier, at this time, orders were orders. Everyone immediately gave a shot before turning around and leaving.

After seeing the group walk out, Thunder Yun stood up as well. He took his wooden pole and then turned around to Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, gather your people. We’ll make the Ark Continent’s people experience how powerful our lightning abilities are.” Fei’er nodded, then he took up his own wooden pole and followed Thunder Yun outward.

When they reached outside, the immediately saw a scene similar to yesterday. The blood devouring mosquitoes were constantly shooting down from the skies and attacking the camp. Thunder Yun snorted as he waved his pole, a flash of light came and a bunch of mosquitoes in front of him disappeared into ash. What Thunder Yun didn’t notice was the same mosquitoes reappearing in the sky above him and continued on their attack.

At this time, Fei’er had also gathered the other giants. All of them had their poles with them as they lined up and muttered incantations. Tiny sparks of lightning started to appear on their bodies, the sparks got stronger and stronger before each giant was covered in lightning. It was at this moment when Fei’er said, “Attack!”

And just as his voice fell, the lightning on each Giant arched towards the mosquitoes, jumping from one mosquito to another. Those who were hit by the attack were instantaneously turned to ash.

With Fei’er and the other giants controlling the lightning, it meandered all throughout the Divine Race camp, killing a large number of mosquitoes with each go. However, just as soon as they died, the mosquitoes reappeared and then continued on with their attack.

Naturally, it was impossible for the giants to control their lightning for a long time. Soon enough, the net of lightning vanished in mid ark. On the other hand, it seemed like the number of mosquitoes remained unaffected.

While Fei’er and the others were doing their attack, Thunder Yun took the time to observe the blood devouring mosquitoes. He always had this strange feeling. He led his 20 million army yesterday and eliminated all of the blood devouring mosquitoes. They worked very hard, and even if they suffered casualties, they removed all of the mosquitoes that came. However, the disappearance of the mosquitoes’ corpses seemed to nag him in the back of his mind.

Because of this, he decided to focus on the blood devouring mosquitoes, he wanted to see some clues. Just as the giants’ lightning net eliminated a swathe of mosquitoes, another large clump appeared in the air.

Thunder Yun couldn’t help but be surprised when he saw this. In order to make sure that he wasn’t seeing things, he concentrated on the lightning net. After the net eradicated the mosquitoes, a blood devouring mosquito suddenly appeared from where it vanished. It looks as if they weren’t killed at all.

This startled Thunder Yun, his forehead dropping a cold sweat. He knew that this situation would only happen in two occasions; First, when a mosquito has a spatial teleportation ability. However, Thunder Yun couldn’t detect any spatial fluctuations, so this possibility is void.

Another possibility was that these blood devouring mosquitoes can actually resurrect!

Resurrection! This isn’t a strange name in the Divine Realm. There were several magic beasts with this ability. If one wanted to kill these creatures, then one needed to ensure that every single part of it was gone, including each drop of blood. Otherwise, any of their parts would be able to attach to another magic beast, absorbing their life force before completely resurrecting themselves. Although their strengths would be affected, nobody in the Divine Realm would want to offend any beast that had this ability. With no way to completely eliminate them, stirring trouble with these creatures would be a very bad idea.

But from the looks of it, these blood devouring mosquitoes seem to have more than just resurrection. Thunder Yun can see that the blood devouring mosquitoes today were stronger than those yesterday, at least twice as strong. And if they can regenerate, then it meant that these weren’t blood devouring mosquitoes.

After thinking about it,, Thunder Yun observed the mosquitoes more carefully. He wanted to see if the attacks of these mosquitoes were the same as those he had seen in the Divine Realm.

However, after looking for a long time, he couldn’t find any differences on these blood devouring mosquitoes. Therefore, there is only one explanation for this, these mosquitoes were a variant species of the blood devouring mosquitoes.

At the thought of this, Thunder Yun let out a sigh of relief. He wasn’t afraid of these regenerating mosquitoes. Since these mosquitoes can regenerate, then it meant that those yesterday could regenerate as well. No wonder those mosquitoes were very hard to deal with, they actually had the ability to regenerate.

But in the end, the mosquitoes yesterday were still eliminated. This means that the number of times these mosquitoes gets resurrected was not endless.

Thunder Yun felt relieved, however, he didn’t spread the information about the resurrecting abilities of the mosquitoes. One must know that the mere thought of a resurrecting beast would cause anxiety on any Divine Realm resident. If he spread the word out, then he would be causing unnecessary decrease in troop morale.

After Fei’er and the other Giants ran out of energy to do their attacks, Fei’er returned to Thunder Yun’s side. Fei’er didn’t follow Thunder Yun for a day or two, so when he saw Thunder Yun standing there, he knew that his Master was observing the blood devouring mosquitoes. Naturally, he wouldn’t disturb Thunder Yun and so he gave him time to analyze their enemy.

At this time, an explosion was suddenly heard in the distance. This sound sobered Thunder Yun, he looked at the direction of the sound as he said, “As I expected, this Zhao Hai is really difficult to deal with.”

Fei’er naturally understood Thunder Yun. Not only was Zhao Hai using the blood devouring mosquitoes, he also took the time to add the undead as well.

Fei’er turned to Thunder Yun and said, “Master, what do we do now?”

Thunder Yun sighed and said, “We endure, we have no other ways to deal with them right now. This is also the reason why I decided to make a retreat. The enemy just has too many things to use against us, way more than I expected. We have to go back and rethink about how to deal with them.”

Fei’er turned silent. After being with Thunder Yun for all these years, this was the first time that he heard Thunder Yun say this. From Thunder Yun’s tone was a hint of helplessness. This aspect had always been absent on Thunder Yun,before, yet it appeared right now.

This made Fei’er even more curious about Zhao Hai. He wanted to know what kind of person this Zhao Hai really was. How could he be this consistent that he even had Thunder Yun retreat? This person was just too strong, can one man really do all of these?

Although Fei’er was thinking about these, he didn’t stop and stare. If Thunder Yun were to see Fei’er’s face right now, he would be surprised. Fei’er’s eyes were so bright that he must have been thinking about great things. The first time Fei’er was like this was when he was going all out against the invading Divine Race army.

The attacks from the mosquitoes and undead kept coming. Although they had already thought about ways to deal with the mosquitoes, they were yet to think about how to deal with the undead. The attacks of the undead were really fast. Moreover, with the attacks from the mosquitoes, those in the outskirts of the army had their consciousness split into two. They were keeping eyes on the mosquitoes while also taking note of the constant wave of javelin attacks coming towards them.

Because of the method that Thunder Yun made yesterday, the lethality of the mosquitoes has been greatly reduced. Although the blood devouring mosquitoes were promoted, the casualties that they caused had become smaller. While the mosquitoes were attacking, one Divine Race soldier would support his Domain, one would focus on killing the mosquitoes, and one would rest and get ready to rotate.

But even so, casualties couldn’t be avoided. The coordination between the javelins of the undead and the mosquitoes caused more deaths compared to last night.

Chapter 780: Demon Dragon King’s Worry

The Demon Dragon King looked at Rising Sun City and thought of all the Demons that had died. After seeing Zhao Hai’s move, the Demon Dragon King already knew about its purpose. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s harassment tactics really gave the Demon Dragon King a headache.

Although Zhao Hai’s harassment didn’t take too much off of their numbers, he did greatly slow their advance. When the Demon Dragon King arrived at Rising Sun City, it was already late afternoon, the skies were proceeding to turn dark. However, nobody was in Rising Sun City.

The most troublesome thing for the Demon Dragon King right now was that he was afraid of splitting his troops. From what he had counted, Zhao Hai had sent a couple million cavalry units to harass them today. If the Demon Dragon King split his troops, then the only outcome that would happen is them being dominated by Zhao Hai.

Because of this, the Demon Dragon King decided to stay in a single clump. And since Zhao Hai only used his undead in their previous battle, the Demon Dragon King didn’t know about the general strength of the Ark Continent’s troops. The information that they had collected in the past stated that the people of the Ark Continent were quite weak, they were not an opponent for the Demon Race.

But in the recent time, the Demon Dragon King received information that Zhao Hai had potions that can make anyone into a 9th rank expert in short time. The Demon Dragon King was quite doubtful of this report. But after seeing the cavalry units, the Demon Dragon King finally believed that Zhao Hai really did have a way to drastically improve one’s strength.

This made the Demon Dragon King worried. The reason why the Demons were confident in conquering the Ark Continent was because their soldiers were far stronger compared to those in the continent. Additionally, the Demons also had large amounts of God rank experts. But now that the Ark Continent can promote their strength, the advantage of the Demon Army has been nullified. Additionally, Zhao Hai had items that can injure God-rank experts. Because of these reasons, it would be difficult for the Demon Race to conquer the Ark Continent in a short period of time. Being in competition with the Divine Race didn’t help either.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but feel his confidence drop after being faced with the cavalry attacks. He didn’t know how Zhao Hai managed to make his potions. After all, these potions weren’t only good for the Ark Continent, it was good for the Demon Race as well.

The Demon Dragon King even had Demon researchers study the two potions. However, the answers that they gave him was disappointing. The researchers told him that the 8th rank potion was just a bottle of water while the 9th rank potion was the blood of an unknown magic beast. The 9th rank potion wasn’t a potion at all!

Upon receiving the result, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but frown. He hadn’t heard of a water that can make someone 8th rank, even the Elves’ life liquid couldn’t do this. The blood that can make people 9th rank was even more mysterious. If a magic beast who had blood like that existed, there would be no way for Zhao Hai to tame it. More importantly, it would be impossible for that creature to have enough blood to feed the Ark Continent’s army.

As the matter stands, the Demon Dragon King gained nothing in this study. He was still stuck in looking for ways to deal with Zhao Hai.

After looking at Rising Sun City, the Demon Dragon King sighed and said, “We rest here tonight. Inform everyone to set up camp.” Those around him gave a nod and proceeded to spread the order.

The efficiency of the Demon Race wasn’t any slower than the Divine Race. Additionally, they were using the same methods as the Divine Race. Because of this, it didn’t take too long before the Demons had finished making their camp.

After the camps were set up, the Demon Dragon King went to his own room and met with other God rank experts from different clans. The Demon Dragon King looked at those present and said, “We have finally arrived at Rising Sun City. However, Zhao Hai’s methods are giving us huge problems. Moreover, their soldiers had underwent a huge promotion of strength. Conquering the Ark Continent in a short time is proving to be difficult. I have already reported this matter to the Great Demon King. What we need to do right now is to wait for some clashes between Zhao Hai and the Divine Race, when that happens, we’ll go out and capture some important places for ourselves. Then we’ll hold those places and wait for the Great Demon King’s arrival.”

The group didn’t have anything to say, they were also annoyed by the constant attacks that they went through today. They couldn’t’ do anything, their cavalry units weren’t as quick as the enemy. Even God-rank experts couldn’t catch up. In this case, the Demon Dragon King’s method was the best plan for them.

Seeing that nobody gave their own ideas, the Demon Dragon King continued, “Zhao Hai has changed his tactics, and their strength is no weaker than us. The only thing we could do is to steadily advance while capturing more cities. However, I expect Zhao Hai to make it harder for us to advance. Make sure to have your men be alert at all times, we can’t be careless at this time.”

The group loudly accepted the Demon Dragon King’s command before then turned around to leave. However, what the Demon Dragon King didn’t expect was the cavalry attacks stopping when evening came.

The Demon Dragon King became more relieved as the skies turned darker. This was because the skies of the Demon Realm were darker than the Ark Continent. The Demons were more suited to fight in the dark, so the Demon Dragon King wasn’t afraid of anything.

After establishing their defense, the Demon Dragon King went on to take a rest. Him and Thunder Yun had similar methods. At the same time, the Demon Dragon King also came to encounter the same scenario that Thunder Yun had.

A humming sound awakened the Demon Dragon King. He stared for a moment before he quickly sat up. This was because he felt that this sound was quite familiar. However, even though he felt it familiar, he still couldn’t remember what it was.

The Demon Dragon King was a very cautious person, he immediately gave an order, “What is that humming noise? Go and check!” The guard outside immediately responded, footsteps were heard as the guard went away.

Before long, that same guard came running back, and with a panicked voice he said, “Your Highness, large quantities of devil mosquitoes are outside. It looks like an enormous swarm!”

The Demon Dragon King’s expression completely melted. He finally remembered where he heard this humming noise. It was an experience he didn’t want to remember. Before the Demon Dragon King became God-rank, he was just an ordinary person among the Vile Demon Race. He wandered all throughout the Demon Realm, wanting to quickly improve his strength. At that time, he had several friends travelling with him. They entered a famed dangerous area in the Demon Realm, wanting to explore it. However, they didn’t expect to see a mosquito swarm living there. The Demon Dragon King only escaped because of his luck, all of his friends weren’t as fortunate.

He could clearly remember the clump of mosquitoes that was enough to blot out the entire sky. At that time, he was extremely terrified as he ran for his pitiful life. All those friends that he had tried to fight their way out, but in the end, they were swallowed by the mosquito swarm. The Demon Dragon King still had nightmares about that event up to this day.

The Demon Dragon King immediately ran out of the door before he shouted loudly. “How can there be devil mosquitoes here? How can those mosquitoes appear in the Ark Continent? Quick, ring the alarm!!” With his order, the alarm quickly rang out. The melodious ring of the bell seemed very alarming in this dark night. The entire Demon Army immediately sprang out, ready to take action.

The Demon Dragon King looked at the blood devouring mosquitoes in the sky. His expression was very difficult to describe, he didn’t expect devil mosquitoes to appear in the Ark Continent.

At this time, experts from different clans arrived by the Demon Dragon King’s side. Their expression were quite ugly as well, they didn’t know what to say. After a short while, a Demon opened his mouth, “How can devil mosquitoes appear here? If they existed, how can the Ark Continent still survive?”

The Demon Dragon King had already calmed himself, he replied, “I recall reading something from our information of the Ark Continent. There is a record about mosquitoes called blood devouring mosquitoes. At that time, there was a small flock of them in the Ark Continent. In order to suppress them, a lot of 9th rank experts went on to drive them away from the mainland. But I didn’t think that those blood devouring mosquitoes would be the Devil Mosquitoes that we now of. Let everyone be extra careful. Everyone should know about devil mosquitoes and how terrifying they are.”

The group nodded before they turned and left. Just as the meeting was finished, the blood devouring mosquitoes started their attack, plunging the whole Demon Army into chaos.

However, this was also the time where the Demons have shown how relsolute they were. The Demons went on and killed the mosquitoes wave by wave. And once a Demon knew that he would not survive, he would fly up to the distance and blow himself up, taking a huge clump of mosquitoes from the surroundings.

The Demon Dragon King looked at these explosions in pain. As the first explosion sounded out, more and more Demons started to blow themselves up.

At this time, a different kind of explosion was heard. The Demon Dragon King stared for a moment before his expression turned ugly. He knew what this explosion was, this was from the Ark Continent’s javelins.

After hearing the explosions, the Demon Dragon King knew that the Ark Continent’s people had used this opportunity to attack. What made the Demon Dragon King worried wasn’t this attack, but instead the fact that the people  from the Ark Continent weren’t worried about the mosquitoes.

If they weren’t scared, then this only meant one thing, the devil mosquitoes wouldn’t attack them. And the reason for this was because the mosquitoes were under their control.

The Demon Dragon King knew about how terrifying these devil mosquitoes were, if the Ark Continent can indeed control them, then this wouldn’t be good news for the Demon Race.

Another thing that worried the Demon Dragon King was the strength of the devil mosquitoes. They weren’t weaker than the ones he encountered in the Demon Realm. The Demon Army was in a very dangerous position!

Chapter 781: A Night of Loss, Two Choices

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the Space looking at the state of the Demons and the Divine Race. He didn’t know whether the Demons or the Divine Race would retreat or not.

Zhao Hai knew that tonight’s attack would be regarded as the largest attack he’d made to both the Demons and the Divine Race. With the mosquitoes and the cavalry attacking together, Zhao Hai believed that the damages caused this evening wouldn’t be small.

However, Zhao Hai’s work was actually much easier this time. He just had the javelins and other supplies dropped off on a single place not far from the camps of both the Demons and the Divine Race. The amount that he took out was more than enough. Even if the cavalry and the undead attack non-stop, the supply wouldn’t run out.

What Zhao Hai wanted to see was the reactions of the two parties when it came to the blood devouring mosquitoes. What he saw was interesting, both Demons and Divine Race knew about the mosquitoes, this confused him.

Originally, Zhao Hai thought that the blood devouring mosquitoes were native to the Ark Continent. But when he saw the Divine Race say the name of the blood devouring mosquitoes, he knew that they also existed in the Divine Realm. Moreover, they even had the same name.

More surprisingly, the Demons also knew about the mosquitoes. However, their name was different, they called the mosquitoes devil mosquitoes. This made Zhao Hai curious. He knew that the Demon Realm had an environment completely different compared to the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm. Moreover, even though the Demon Realm had variant versions of the Ark Continent’s magic beasts, Zhao Hai can tell from the Demon Dragon King’s words that the blood devouring mosquitoes and the devil mosquitoes were the same.

The blood devouring mosquitoes existed in three realms, what does this mean? Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown, he planned to study it when there is time.

Zhao Hai didn’t want any more trouble. At this time, Zhao Hai had a constant sense of crisis. Not to talk about the Demons and the Divine Race, the appearance of the immortal cultivator made Zhao Hai look seriously into his current state.

The strange circumstance circulating the blood devouring mosquitoes made Zhao Hai think of his problems. He wanted to see if the mosquitoes also had a connection in the immortal cultivation realm.

As Zhao Hai was juggling his thoughts, the Demons and the Divine Race were continuing their heated war against the blood devouring mosquitoes. The Demons had a bigger loss this time. The Demon army had 8th ranks among their numbers. After being subjected to hundreds of mosquito attacks, these 8th ranks simply didn’t have any chance to escape. In the end, most of them chose to blow themselves up.

When faced with ordinary blood devouring mosquitoes, this move might be very useful. However, the mosquitoes that they faced belonged to Zhao Hai’s Space. When these mosquitoes die, they just be resurrected. The sacrifice made by the Demons were made utterly useless.

Majority of the Demon deaths were 8th ranks, but this still satisfied Zhao Hai. The 8th rank Demons were still quite a threat. Although they might not be a match against the Ark Continent’s 9th rank soldiers, their self-explosions were still very lethal.

But even then, the undead and the cavalry units were still able to bring damages to the two parties. Although the javelins would kill some mosquitoes, the consequence was not that heavy. After all, the mosquitoes can be released once more after 24 hours, so Zhao Hai wasn’t hurt too much about the collateral damage.

The battle lasted the entire night. The Divine Race’s losses had reached an astonishing 300 thousand. Meanwhile, the Demons lost more than 500 thousand troops. It can be said that the damages were quite heavy. When dawn came, the number of mosquitoes have been reduced by a certain degree, only stragglers here and there remained. At the same time, Zhao Hai also ordered the undead and the cavalry units to retreat.

After the Demons and the Divine Race counted their losses, their expressions weren’t too good. Thunder Yun immediately convened the generals inside his room, he looked at them and said, “It seems like Zhao Hai has yet to eradicate the barbarians and the winged pegasus armies. Otherwise, he would have sent them last night, causing us even more losses. This is the second batch of mosquitoes that Zhao Hai had sent in two days. It has become obvious that the mosquitoes are under the Ark Continent’s control. Zhao Hai might not be the one controlling them, but we can be sure that someone from the continent can. We’ll return to the Radiant Empire for now. We need to ask for ways to repel those mosquitoes. Otherwise, we will have even more casualties.”

The group naturally wouldn’t oppose to this, but Cloud Ying couldn’t help but say, “I think we need to send word towards the Barbarian and Winged Pegasus clans. Make it known to them that their kin has been killed. Even if Zhao Hai didn’t completely wipe them out, he still managed to kill some number of them, the two clans would still send some elites over. At the same time, when the repellants for the mosquitoes arrive, we can resume our attack on the Ark Continent. At that time, I will personally shred Zhao Hai.”

Cloud Ying shared this sentiment with the other Divine Race generals. In the many conquests that the Divine Race had in the lower realms, this was the first time that they had lost this much. Although they had lost a lot back in the God of Thunder’s Realm, the losses to the other party was much more. But this time, the Ark Continent barely lost anyone. To the arrogant Divine Race, this was a completely unacceptable situation.

Thunder Yun looked at the group and said, “Send this order. Rest for two hours, after that, we return to the Radiant Empire. We don’t want to get entangled with the undead any longer.”

The group all nodded before they turned and left.

After the others walked out, Thunder Yun relaxed. He turned his head to Fei’er and said, “Fei;er, have you noticed something strange with those blood devouring mosquitoes?”

Fei’er’ had a confused expression as he said, “Strange? Aren’t they just the normal blood devouring mosquitoes? Although they are stronger than the ones in the Divine Realm, they aren’t very numerous.”

Thunder Yun smiled and said, “You don’t think that those mosquitoes aren’t a lot? The blood devouring mosquitoes that we met last time are obviously not the same as the ones we met today. Why is this?”

Fei’er looked puzzled at Thunder Yun, “Master, to be honest, I didn’t notice it.”

Thunder Yun smiled bitterly and said, “I can’t blame you, not everyone noticed it. The Ark Continent’s blood devouring mosquitoes can regenerate. Moreover, it seems like instant regeneration. The number of times seem to surpass 25!”

When Fei’er heard Thunder Yun, he couldn’t help but stare. His complexion changed as she said, “Regeneration? Master, those mosquitoes can regenerate? How is that possible? If those mosquitoes are that terrifying, then the Ark Continent would have been completely eradicated by now.”

Thunder Yun smiled faintly and said, “It’s true. I observed those mosquitoes closely and reached this conclusion. It doesn’t matter matter how the Ark Continent managed to control them, the important thing is that those mosquitoes aren’t good news. We must be more careful from now on.”

Fei’er nodded and didn’t say anything. At this time, the camp outside had regained its peace. Thunder Yun gave out a sigh and said, “Alright, you go and take a rest. Don’t forget, we need to retreat in two hours.”

Fei’er nodded, then he walked out. But after he walked out, Fei’er looked back at Thunder Yun’s room before a flash of light appeared on his eyes. It seems like he was thinking about something that Thunder Yun didn’t know about.

The Demons had a fairly similar situation as the Divine Race. They had lost almost twice as much as the Divine Race. For an army of several tens of millions, this number might not be strong. However, the circumstance of the deaths made the difference. In just one night, the Demons had lost seven hundred thousand troops. This was something unfathomable even to the Demon Dragon King.

The Demon Dragon King was currently inside his room, thinking about whether he would make a retreat or not. They had lost too many people just this evening. Although majority of the deaths were 8th ranks, the number was just too much. If the Demons weren’t hardened fighters, then some Demons might have deserted the army.

The Demon Dragon King was frowning as he sat there. This loss was something that he couldn’t ignore. The more worrying matter was the possibility that the Ark Continent’s people were controlling the devil mosquitoes.

After pondering about it for some time, the Demon Dragon King decided to hold the retreat for now. They would advance in steady steps. He knew that even if they were to retreat, the Ark Continent’s people would still go on and harass them. When the time comes, not only would they gain nothing, they would even be forced to be in a passive situation.

However, this didn’t mean that they didn’t need support. The Demon Dragon King already sent people back to the Demon Realm to report on the Demon Army’s state. At the same time, he asked the troops back at their base to make some repellents against the mosquitoes.

In the Divine Realm and the Demon Realm, their description of the mosquitoes was different from the Ark Continent. In the continent, the mosquitoes were just a one-time disaster. After they were eliminated, they didn’t pop out once more. Therefore, the mosquitoes only existed in the Ark Continent’s writings.

However, mosquitoes were a constant disaster in the Demon and the Divine Realm. Therefore, research had been made in order to deal with them. It was only because they didn’t expect to see mosquitoes in the Ark Continent that the Demons and the Divine Race didn’t bring any repellents.

Chapter 782: What Zhao Hai Doesn’t Know

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the monitor. He didn’t think that the Divine Race would retreat, it was actually out of his expectations. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when he saw the Divine Rest pack their things and heading the opposite direction after their two hour rest. Seeing them retreat, Zhao Hai decided to not send the undead after them. It was best to give more time to Lizzy and Megan. As long as the two women had time, they can completely eliminate the winged pegasus cavalry. When that time comes, Zhao Hai’s strength would dramatically increase. Also, after seeing the Divine Race retreat, Zhao Hai can now focus solely on the Demons.

Zhao Hai needed time, he wanted the Demons to retreat as well. If the Demons retreat, then Zhao Hai would gain even more time. The first batch of God ranked undead have already finished and the pagoda had started with the second batch. At the same time, another God-rank potion was on the way. As long as there was time, Zhao Hai’s side would become much better.

But to Zhao Hai’s disappointment, the Demons didn’t retreat. Unlike the Divine Race who retreated after resting for two hours, the Demons rested for 5 hours before leaving Rising Sun City, pushing forward into the Buddha Empire.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. His expectation for the Demon Army’s retreat was even more than the Divine Race seeing how cautious they had been lately. But who would’ve thought that the opposite happened, the Divine Race retreated while the Demons pushed on.

While looking at the Demon Army, Zhao Hai coldly snorted. He was still monitoring the Divine Race, however, he didn’t send more attacks. He wanted the Divine Race to retreat, and he didn’t want to enrage them even more. He was afraid that the Divine Race would get angry and reverse their decision. After all, when enough time passes, Zhao Hai would be able to clean them up in one fell swoop.

On the other hand, the Demons actually went forward. In two days, they would meet with Lizzy and Megan’s group, and that wouldn’t be good.

Now that the Divine Race was gone, Zhao Hai can reallocated his undead to deal with the Demons. These undead made the Demon advance even more difficult. They needed to delay the Demons and make time for Lizzy and Megan to eliminate the winged pegasus cavalry.

After the Demons left Rising Sun City, Zhao Hai noticed that they had left some people behind. Zhao Hai immediately knew that the Demon advance this time was meant to occupy the Buddha Empire’s cities.

Altogether, the Demons have left 1 million troops inside Rising Sun City, a thousand of them being God-rank experts. At the same time, a constant stream of Demons can be seen going from Demon City to Rising Sun City.

Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but change. With his current resources, he wouldn’t be able to reclaim Rising Sun City. If he decided to attack the city, the Demons from Demon City will go forward as support. When that time comes, a clash would happen, this wasn’t something that Zhao Hai wanted.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t too worried. After all, he didn’t have much power in his hands. As soon as Lizzy and Megan finishes their action, the majority of the undead would be available once more.

The Demon Dragon King had discovered that their current assailants didn’t comprise of only cavalry units, there were undead mixed in as well. These undead were very difficult to deal with. The bows and throwing weapons that the Demons had were less lethal to the undead. On the other hand, the javelins thrown by the undead were a huge threat to the Demon Army.

To be honest, the Demon Dragon King was quite curious about Zhao Hai’s javelins. In their previous battles, Zhao Hai didn’t use it. Now that Zhao Hai had changed his tactics, these javelin were used. The Demon Dragon King wondered why.

This wooden javelin wasn’t simple. One could see that they were crudely made, however, their lethality couldn’t be underestimated.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but rub his temples. Although he planned to grab some land while Zhao Hai battles it out with the Divine Race, his current losses was something he didn’t hope for.

And after they left the city, they were attacked by javelins once more. All of these gave the Demon Dragon King a headache.

While Zhao Hai was busy dealing with the Demons, he wasn’t aware of the changes in another place. In the Northern Icefield, there was a huge spatial rift that was constantly releasing undead. When they came out of the rift, the undead went about and explored the icefield. They only remained undetected because the icefield was just too big.

However, the undead quickly found the volcano as well as the stone city. Soon, more and more undead went towards that direction as even more undead came out of the rift.

At this point, a large sea of undead was starting to head towards the Beastman Prairie. These undead were tirelessly going forward. The ice and winds were completely useless against them. In a few day’s time, they would be setting foot on the prairie.

Naturally, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t know about this. At the same time, they were also unaware about another small rift appearing in an island not too far from the Radiant Empire. This rift was smaller and there were no creatures going out of it. However, this rift would surely have an impact on the Ark Continent in the future.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about any of these, his thoughts were currently on the enemies in front of him, the Demons and the Divine Race. Now that the Divine Race was heading back to the Radiant Empire, Zhao Hai only had the Demons to worry about.

Lizzy and Megan had prepared for three days in order to deal with the winged pegasus army. However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry too much. He knew that they would take action quite soon. At the same time, the God rank potion would be completed in one day.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was very surprised at the Demon Army. He didn’t stop harassing the Demons both day and night. Moreover, with the use of the mosquitoes, the losses to the Demon Army had reached an additional 1 million. But even with this, the Demons didn’t retreat. Conversely, even with their slow pace, they continued on. This action made Zhao Hai admire the Demon Race. Zhao Hai sent forces to attack them all the time, however, they kept going forward even if they knew that every step they make would cause them to bleed out.

Zhao Hai didn’t understand why the Demons continued on. After the days of being attacked, the Demons were looking very exhausted. They didn’t have a good time to rest and eat. However, they still kept on moving forward.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that the reason for this was simple. The Demons didn’t retreat because Zhao Hai has yet to use his main army. This made the Demons think that he was still in battle with the Divine Race. If they don’t use this opportunity to occupy land, then they won’t be able to do it in the future.

Although the Demons had sent some scouts, those people didn’t dare to get too close to the Divine Race. Moreover, after Thunder Yun saw that Zhao Hai didn’t harass them, he decided to slow their retreat, allowing more time to rest. At the same time, he also used this time to get familiar with the surroundings.

The Demons had more information coming from their scouts near the Radiant Empire. Seeing that the main army was still absent, they were unaware of the retreat. If they knew that the Divine Race had turned back, the Demon Dragon King would surely stop the army from going forward.

A day passed and another God-rank potion has been made. However, Zhao Hai didn’t use it. He was waiting for one more potion to be made before handing them over to Blockhead and Rockhead.

Blockhead and Rockhead were twins that had a mysterious way of coordinating with one another. If Zhao Hai decided to promote one before the other, then he may risk disrupting this coordination. Because of this, Zhao Hai chose to promote them at the same time.

It can be said that some of Zhao Hai’s fears were unwarranted, but he wasn’t in a hurry about this matter. After all, Blockhead and Rockhead would be Demigods after promotion, so they wouldn’t be a great help anyway. Waiting for a few days wouldn’t affect anything too much.

Time passed by and another day came. This was the fifth day after the Demons decided to dispatch their troops. They were still advancing but their losses had now surpassed 3 million, a tenth of their original number. Additionally, after passing by another two cities, more than 2 million troops were left behind. It can be said that the Demon Army was now cut down by a fifth.

Zhao Hai had to recognize the tenacity of the Demon Race. However, he knew that the Demon army’s luck was soon to run out. This was because Lizzy and Megan had already taken care of the winged pegasus cavalry. With this, Zhao Hai was back to using his full strength.

Chapter 783: The Divine Realm’s Situation

Lizzy and Megan were both sitting and talking inside the living room. However, Zhao Hai was nowhere in sight. He was currently busying himself with the Demon Race. Zhao Hai had Megan and Lizzy rest well after they eliminated the winged pegasus army. Now that the two were resting, Zhao Hai took the job and commanded the undead and the cavalry in the meantime.

Lizzy looked at the weary Demons in the monitor and couldn’t help but smile, “It looks like Brother Hai really made them suffer in the past few days. Look at how exhausted every one of them looked.” Laura gave out a hmph, “You haven’t seen Brother Hai. He was monitoring the Demons non-stop, he’s quite tired as well. If you dealt with the winged pegasus sooner, he would have more time to rest.”

Megan smiled and said, “Sister Laura, we already did our best. After all, we need to take care of every single winged pegasus soldier.” Laura snoted and said, “Alright. Go call people from those two races, let’s ask them about the Divine Race’s situation.”

Since Laura had been managing Zhao Hai’s affairs for the longest time, she had the highest status among the women. Lizzy didn’t hesitate and immediately called a heavy cavalry soldier and a winged pegasus soldier. This was also done according to Zhao Hai’s instruction. When the two races were turned into undead, some of them were made into advanced ones so that they could ask them questions.

The barbarian soldier was tall and big, they were even taller compared to average Beastmen. On the other hand, the winged pegasus person was not that huge. Moreover, they look quite slender, resembling the Elves. However, instead of long ears, the winged pegasus people had two wings as ears, with long feathers on each tip.

Lizzy and the others curiously looked at the two people. After some time, Lizzy looked at the barbarian soldier and said, “What is your race? Are you from the Divine Race?”

The heavy cavalry soldier replied, “Answering the madam.We are called the Barbarians. We aren’t from the Divine Race, instead, our plane was invaded with the Divine Race. Whenever the Divine Race goes into war, they would send us.”

Lizzy nodded, then she asked once more, “Are the other people in your race as powerful as you? How many of you are there?” Barbarian Ding shook his head and said, “Back at home, we are only considered to be second-rate soldiers. The real elite of our race has yet to set out. Our race’s elites are all 9th ranks. We also have our Golden Horn division made up of God ranked experts. However, their numbers aren’t large, only about 50 thousand people. All in all, our race has about 10 million elite troops. As for second-rate soldiers like us, I don’t know how many there are.” Lizzy and the others couldn’t help but inhale cold air. They didn’t expect the barbarians to be this strong. If they didn’t have a few God-ranks, then the Divine Race might not have been able to conquer their plane.

After thinking about it for some time, Lizzy said, “Will your people send more troops? You lost too many people this time. Will your people help the Divine Race? Is your relationship with the Divine Race good?” Barbarian Ding replied, “Replying to the madam. Our relationship with the Divine Race isn’t very good. We might send our troops, but the most we can send out are our elites. The Golden Horn division rarely sets out. Since the madame have killed us, the clan would surely send some people for revenge.”

Lizzy and the to others frowned. They didn’t expect this thing to happen. At this time, Megan couldn’t wait as she turned to the winged pegasus soldier and said, “How about you? What is your race? And how is your race’s relationship with the Divine Race?”

The winged pegasus soldier replied, “Answering the madam. We are the winged pegasus race. Our relationship with the Divine Race is roughly the same as the Barbarians. We also listen to them but we don’t worship their existence. At the same time, our clan would also be sending troops in order to avenge us.”

Lizzy and Megan smiled bitterly, they didn’t think that there would be more enemies coming over. Laura didn’t think about it too much as he looked at the winged pegasus soldier and said, “What is your name? And how many people does your race have? How strong are you?” The winged pegasus person answered, “Replying to the madam. My name is Zhan. My troops are in the middle of our race’s strength. Above us are the elite army with 10 million troops. We also have the Silverwing Division composed of 100 thousand God-ranks.”

Everybody smiled bitterly upon hearing this. The Divine Race already had a lot of God-ranks. Now, there are also 100 thousand God-rank winged pegasus soldiers. If the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus clan decided to send their best troops, then the Ark Continent would be in trouble.

Lizzy forced a smile and said, “How about those giants, do you know what race they belong to?”

Winged Pegasus Zhan nodded, “I do. They are people from the Thunder clan. Their faith lied on the Thunder Beast. Their wooden poles are totems used to worship the thunder beast. However, nobody has seen an actual thunder beast. Their totems can summon incarnations of the thunder beast. Their race is very strong, not only are they physically powerful, their totems also allowed them to cast multiple spells. I heard that when the Divine Race went on to conquer the Thunder Realm, they lost a lot of men doing so. Later on, they carried on a massacre in the Thunder Realm, shocking the entire Thunder Clan. In the end, the plane was given to the God of Thunder, General Thunder Yun. Thunder Yun is the commander of the Divine Race army, the Thunder Clan had become his personal bodyguards.”

Lizzy gave a faint smile. Megan immediately followed up, “I saw green skinned creatures in the Radiant Empire. What are they? Why do they look like slaves?”

Barbarian Ding replied, “Replying to the madame. They are indeed slaves. They are called the Goblin Race. They are creatures native to the Divine Realm. Their fighting strength is low, however, they are very interested in tinkering. It was said that magic formations made by them are very strong. I’ve also heard that they were able to produce flying machines in the past. However, since their race isn’t interested in making weapons, the Divine Race managed to subdue them. In the end, their entire race was reduced to becoming labor slaves.”

Laura asked, “Did the Divine Race conquer any other race? If so, what other races are there?’

Barbarian Ding shook his head and said, “I don’t know.”

However, Winged Pegasus Zhan replied, “Answering to the madam, there are no other races in the Divine Race army. The Divine Race army that is attacking the Ark Continent right now are the Divines from the Taurus Continent. The Taurus Divines had only conquered our four races. As for the other Divines on the other continents, I don’t know much about the planes that they conquered.”

Laura stared, then her expression underwent a huge change, “Will the other continents send troops here? Aren’t the Divine Race in a war against the foreign races? Did the war subside?”

Winged Pegasus Zhan shook his head and said, “Replying to the madam. I don’t know whether the other continents would send their troops or not. However, I have heard about the war with the foreign races. It seems like the foreign races had inferior strength compared to the Divine Race, they had been pushed into a passive state.”

Laura frowned, “I heard that the Divine Realm has 13 continents. How are they divided between the Divine Race and the foreign races?”

Winged Pegasus Zhan nodded and said, “Of the 13 continents, ten of them are under the control of the Divine Race while three are controlled by the foreign races; the Aries Continent, the Libra Continent, and the Virgo Continent. Other than those three, the remaining ten are under the Divine Race.”

Laura let out a long breath, then she asked once more, “Do you know which foreign race controls each continent?

Winged Pegasus Zhan nodded, “The Ares Continent is where the Beastmen Gods reside. The Libra Continent is under the Dwarves, and the Virgo Continent is under the Elves. Beside those three huge races, there are also some other races that live in the three continents. All these years they had continued to resist the Divine Race.”

Laura and the others nodded. To be honest, they didn’t know what to think right now. They didn’t think that the Divine Race would have this much scope in their power. They were already having problems dealing with the Taurus Divines. If the other continents send troops, then the Ark Continent would surely be eliminated.

However, Laura and the others were also thinking that it was highly improbable. The Taurus continent surely wasn’t that smaller than the Ark Continent. In this case, if the other continents sent their troops, there won’t be much they could gain. They might even lose more than what they receive.

Additionally, the Divine Race also needed to deal with the foreign races. It was impossible for the entire Divine Race to focus on the Ark Continent. Perhaps this is an opportunity for Zhao Hai.

They had already proven that the foreign races are still surviving. This meant that a potential ally existed!

Chapter 784: Make Them Know How Terrifying We Are

Zhao Hai woke up. He found himself very tired in the past few days as he continually harassed both the Demons and the Divine Race.

Additionally, when Lizzy and Megan were done dealing with the winged pegasus cavalry, Zhao Hai saw that the two of them were very tired. So instead of having them work again, he decided to have them take a rest. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai went on and continued to harass the Demons.

After cleaning his room, Zhao Hai pushed the door open. Upon going out, he couldn’t help but knit his brows. He knew that Laura and the others were in the living room, however, there wasn’t any sound right now.

Zhao Hai immediately knew that something must have happened. Otherwise, the women wouldn’t have been this silent. After thinking about it, Zhao Hai immediately hastened his steps as he went to the living room.

After arriving, Zhao Hai saw Laura and the others frowning, nobody made any noise.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be curious, so he asked, “What’s wrong? Why are you all frowning?”

When the women saw Zhao Hai arrive, they immediately made space for him to sit down. Meg stood up and offered Zhao Hai a cup of tea while Laura and the others told Zhao Hai about what they had found out.

After hearing the story, Zhao Hai frowned as well. If this was really the case, then he had gained more annoying enemies.

Seeing that Zhao Hai stayed silent, Laura and the others didn’t make a noise. After all, the final decision about this matter lied on Zhao Hai.

After some time, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “Alright, worrying about this is useless. If the elites of those two races come, then let them come. We aren’t afraid of them. Moreover, when it comes to revenge, their hatred for the Divine Race is certainly stronger. Yet, they still submitted, therefore, they should submit to us as well. The important thing to us right now is the existence of the foreign races in the Divine Realm. As long as they survive, then the Divine Race couldn’t go all out in fighting us. Also, the other Divine Realm continents might not be interested in the Ark Continent. Moreover, with how serious the Taurus Divines have become, their actions have certainly been spread to the Divine Realm. At the very least, the foreign races should be able to hear the news. They might even take the opportunity to contact us, seeing how they aren’t doing too good.”

Laura nodded, “However, it wouldn’t be too easy for us to deal with the Taurus Divines. After all, we’ve already been having problems with Thunder Yun, the power of his Giants is very strong.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “That’s correct. But although the Giants have great strength, I’m certain that they aren’t that numerous. After all, if they had enough numbers, then they wouldn’t have been destroyed by the Divine Race.” Laura and the other nodded. They were just worried, they weren’t afraid. After all, they had the Space. They could just evacuate the Ark Continent whenever things get out of hand. When that time comes, they would just wait until their overall strength gets improved. Then they can expel the Divine Race form the continent.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and the others as he smiled and said, “Actually, among these information, the one I think the most useful is the Goblins. I have underestimated them before, I didn’t think that they would have this much skill.”

Laura looked confused at Zhao Hai’s words, she asked, “Why is Brother Hai so interested in those Goblins? I can’t see anything special about them.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Didn’t Zhan say that those goblins are very skilled when it comes to machines? Moreover, they have certain talents when it comes to using magic formations for machines, their skills would surely be good for us.”

Laura was still confused, “Good? What’s the difference between machines with magic formations and just magic formations?’

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Of course its good. If those goblins are really experts in the application of magic formations, then they can help improve the strength of our magic cannons. Also, they might be able to make different uses for the crystals. Using the crystals just for ammunition would be wasteful.”

Laura stared for a moment before she nodded, “Alright. If we can save more crystals, then we could make more magic cannons and other items.”

Laura finally understood what Zhao Hai meant. Karen had been researching ways of using magic formations to change the lives of the average person. He wanted to make their lives more convenient and safe. After seeing the things in the Space like the monitor, the kitchen and other Earth items, Karen suddenly had an inspiration.

Laura didn’t oppose to Karen’s new obsession. However, she didn’t like how Karen would exhaust himself and even forget to eat and sleep.

Therefore, when Zhao Hai raised the idea of the Goblins, she immediately agreed. If these Goblins were to find ways to make use of the crystals, then it would be a good thing for them.

However, Lizzy was still frowning as she said, “Big Brother Hai, but in the past, the Goblins seems to have no interest in weapons. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have fallen easily to the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “In the past, the Goblins did indeed have no interest in weapons. However, now should be different. They had been slaves of the Divine Race for so long that they should have understood the importance of having weapons. I think they should be looking into making their own all this time.” Megan also frowned, “Will this work? Those goblins have been under the Divine Race for so long. I’m afraid their inheritance had already vanished with time. Will they really be useful to us?”

Zhao Hai gave a faint  smile and said, “Their inheritance might have vanished, but as long as they are goblins, their skills for tinkering should be ingrained to their bones. Just like how the Elves are innately close to nature and the Dwarves gravitating towards blacksmithing, those goblins should still be able to make machines.”

The woman nodded, then didn’t say anything more. Zhao Hai let out a long breath as he said, “The Divine Race are truly fools. If they had the goblins research weapons, then they might have already conquered the Ark Continent.”

Zhao Hai said this as he shifted his gaze towards the monitor, showing the Demon Race’s situation. At this time, the Demons were resting. The Demons looked less tired now compared to two days before.

This didn’t mean that Zhao Hai had reduced his harassment, it just meant that the Demons have adapted. In the past, whenever they meet Zhao Hai’s troops, the Demons would become anxious. But now, except for those in the outskirts of the army, the others went on to sleep and eat, acting as if nothing was happening.

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, the Demons were truly worthy of being mighty warriors. Their adaptiveness to war was very good. Not only did they adapt to Zhao Hai’s harassment, they also got used to the attacks made by the blood devouring mosquitoes.

Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and Megan and said, “Are we ready? I think it’s time to attack the Demons. Let them be aware that the Divine Race has retreated, and that we are now focused on dealing with them.”

Lizzy looked at the screen and then smiled, “It is indeed time to inform them, otherwise they would think that we’re being bullies.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Go, make them know how terrifying we are.” Lizzy nodded and then took out her messenger fish as she and Megan began to issue orders.

First, they had the cavalry units take a rest. Then they immediately released a large number of undead, ready to attack the Demon Army.

In the beginning, Zhao Hai wanted the undead army to attack Rising Sun City, cutting the retreat of the Demons. Then he would encircle the Demon Army and kill them in one go.

However, he discovered that this plan was too unrealistic. First, the Demons had a large number of reinforcement from Demon City. Secondly, the Demon Dragon King’s army had 20 million troops, trapping them was completely impossible.

If 20 million troops were to make a move, then their threat would be too big. Zhao Hai had painstakingly been acquiring undead, and he didn’t want the to be blown up by the Demons. Because of this, Zhao Hai quickly trashed his plan. Instead, he would hand the matter over to Lizzy while he would charge towards the enemy troops.

After seeing Lizzy and Megan prepare, Zhao Hai took Berry, Shue, and Shun, as well as some undead creatures with him. The other undead were given to Lizzy and Megan.

Four people stood on top of a Bone Dragon. They appeared on the place where the Divine Race decided to stop. Then, a large army of undead followed them outside. Zhao Hai, along with the undead army, were ready to charge towards the Demon Army!

Chapter 785: Drill

The Demon Dragon King felt strange. The constant attacks from the Ark Continent suddenly stopped. All the cavalry units and undead have retreated. What happened? Did the Divine Race break their defenses? Were they forced to retreat?

The Demon Race’s information network wasn’t quick. Although they had already discovered the retreat of the Divine Race army, reaching the Demon Dragon King wasn’t easy. The Demon Army was already deep into the Buddha Empire. And the Ark Continent’s forces were often patrolling the surrounding area. Because of this, word of the Divine Race’s retreat had failed to reach the Demon Dragon King.

However, word from the scouts was now unneeded. This was because the Demon Dragon King can already guess what happened from what he saw in front of him. An undead army was approaching from the distance with Zhao Hai standing at the front. The Demon Dragon King’s face changed, he gave a bitter smile as he muttered, “I didn’t expect the Divine Race to be so soft. It seems like Zhao Hai hasn’t been damaged at all, instead, he had gained more undead.”

The Demon Dragon King was talking to himself, naturally, these words didn’t reach the ears of the other military commanders. Seeing the approaching undead army, these commanders were in shock. It can be said that they hadn’t battled with Zhao Hai before, so this was the first time that they experienced Zhao Hai’s might. Even those who fought with Zhao Hai discovered that Zhao Hai’s power was more than what they had thought.

In the past, Zhao Hai brought about more than 10 million undead to fight with the Demons. But now, Zhao Hai brought nearly 30 million. At the same time, human cavalry soldiers were patrolling around the Demon Army. This caused the tension to increase among the Demons present.

In fact, aside from the Demons, the cavalry units were also startled. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this much undead. However, their surprise turned into glee. The stronger Zhao Hai was, the better it would be for their future. Although they don’t fear death, they still didn’t want to die. The more undead Zhao Hai had, the need for the cavalry to break through the enemy lines decreased. This would reduce the probability of them being killed in battle.

As the undead army got closer, the Demon Dragon King slowly gave command, “Army Formation!”

As the Demon Dragon King’s voice dropped, the drums behind him began to sound out. The flustered Demons immediately recovered. Before long, a large formation was already set.

At this point, most of the warriors in the Demon Army were 9th ranks. Their 8th rank experts were almost killed during Zhao Hai’s constant harassment.

The Demons were unable to form a giant cube just like the undead. Aside from the Fishmen, only Zhao Hai used this kind of formation.

The intricacies to the cube formation was too much. Except for the Fishmen who trained in it for so many years, only Zhao Hai who had a completely obedient undead army can use it. It was impossible for other armies to use it with little to no practice.

The battle formation that the Demons used was different to the cube. It was a half moon formation with the curve’s inside facing Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Army and couldn’t help but acknowledge the Demon Dragon King’s ability. They had been constantly attacked in the past few days, causing them to lose several million people. However, not only did the Demons refrain from retreating, they were also able to adapt to their situation. This was naturally largely in part to the Demon Dragon King’s plans.

Since it was the Demon Dragon King who was controlling the army, the Demons still trusted him despite their heavy losses. Also, not even one Demon deserted the army, showing how resolute the entire race was.

Zhao Hai didn’t plan to have a talk with the Demon Dragon King. Instead, he was waiting for Lizzy and Megan to get ready. As soon as they give the signal, the attack would begin.

Just as Zhao Hai’s group reached about a kilometer away from the Demon Army, Lizzy’s voice came through, “Big Brother Hai, we’ll change to a cone formation, you’ll be in the head.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned his head to the three other people and said, “You don’t need to be with me. You go out of the formation and attack the Demons.” The three nodded before they flew from the bone dragon and out of the cube formation.

At roughly the same time, the cube formation changed and became an extremely huge cone. Zhao Hai was on the very tip of the cone, establishing his Domain. Since his Domain can transform into anything that he can think about, Zhao Hai made his Domain into a huge cone with ridges along its side. The Domain looked just like a huge drill bit.

Behind Zhao Hai were the undead, all of them were in perfect place along the cone formation, ready to attack the Demon Race.

After Zhao Hai transformed his Domain, it slowly turned. Going along the Domain’s rotation were the undead behind, making a huge drill out of the massive cone formation.

While the formation rotated, Zhao Hai led the charge towards the Demons army, intending to barrel through the Demon Army.

The Demon Dragon King didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s move. A kilometer distance wasn’t far, but Zhao Hai managed to change a cube formation into this rotating drill before it clashed with the Demon Army.

It was too late for the Demon Dragon King to change the position of his army. He knew that if this drill formation hit their army, then the entire formation would be finished. The Demon Dragon King immediately commanded, “God-ranks, go forward and block the attack!”

After the Demon Dragon King’s order, the God-rank Demons immediately went forward. However, Zhao Hai’s advance was too quick. Just as the God-ranks arrived, they were immediately attacked. Even if their Domains weren’t broken, they were slowly turned back by Zhao Hai.

The God-rank Demons met Zhao Hai’s drill, however, they were unable to prevent it from advancing. After Zhao Hai killed some God-rank Demons, his formation was already nearing the Demon Army’s half moon formation. When the Demon Dragon King saw Zhao Hai’s approach, he knew that he needed to break it. However, he knew that he wasn’t Zhao Hai’s opponent.

The Demon Dragon King discovered that Zhao Hai’s drill formation was creating strong energy disturbance around it. These disturbances weren’t something that ordinary people can stop, it was even impossible for people to come close.

At this time, Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking about this. His only focus right now was to control his speed. He didn’t want the undead to be too spread out.

When the undead reached their speed limit, they immediately began to take their weapons out. Then one by one, they sprang out of the formation. Zhao Hai’s formation wasn’t just an ordinary drill, it was a drill with protruding thorns, dealing massive damage to all it ran through.

Because of this, all the Demons who dared to approach this drill was torn to pieces, they didn’t even have the time to blow themselves up. If they don’t go near this massive drill, then they would be safe. However, in a big battle such as this, one couldn’t just easily reposition himself. It wasn’t long before the Demon discovered that they had very little ways to deal with Zhao Hai.

Although there were a lot of Demons, all of them were in a formation, and Zhao Hai used this opportunity. It didn’t take a long time before Zhao Hai’s drill was already into the Demon Race’s formation.

When Zhao Hai’s drill ran through the Demon Army, it immediately disintegrated, turning into innumerable undead that went on and slaughtered the surrounding Demons.

The Demon Army’s formation was in chaos, Zhao Hai’s drill completely destroyed it. And just as they were about to make a move, the drill suddenly dispersed.

This caught the Demons off guard. In a blink of an eyes, the Demon Army has been divided by the undead.

Zhao Hai immediately understood what Lizzy and Megan wanted to do. He immediately turned his head and killed his way towards the Demon Dragon King. The Demon Dragon King was the centerpiece of the Demon Army. His flag was easily spotted in the battlefield, allowing the Demons to know where he was. Because of this, the Demons would have a sense of direction and wouldn’t immediately turn to chaos when dispersed.

What Zhao Hai needed to do right now was to deal with the Demon Dragon King. As long as the Demon Dragon King is gone, then the Demons would certainly turn chaotic. This would ensure Zhao Hai’s victory in this battle.

The Demon Dragon King naturally saw Zhao Hai’s move. When he saw their formation crumbling, the Demon Dragon King immediately knew that it was impossible for them to defeat Zhao Hai today.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t accept this outcome. He didn’t think that he had just been defeated by Zhao Hai in such a quick manner.

However, he also knew that lamenting on this matter was useless. He needed to find a way to conserve their strength. At the same time, the Demon Dragon King also noticed that some of Zhao Hai’s undead, although they had an appearance of a skeleton, were wearing very good armor. Their armor was something the Divine Race would equip themselves with.

Additionally, he can also recognize these winged horses. Several days ago, his scouts had informed him of the Divine Race’s cavalry. It seems like Zhao Hai’s new undead came from the Divine Race army!

Chapter 786: A Brave Soldier Breaks His Arm

After thinking up to here, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but force a smile. He can now feel pressure from Zhao Hai’s strength. Demons who couldn’t withstand the attacks would blow themselves up, unwilling to be turned into undead.

However, Zhao Hai actually managed to massacre a large number of Divine Race soldiers and turn them into undead. One must know that the Divine Race were generally stronger compared to the Demons. In this case, for Zhao Hai to turn a large number of them into undead wasn’t a good idea for the Demon Race.

But the Demon Dragon King doesn’t have the time to think about this right now. Zhao Hai had already started his killing, and the Demon Dragon King knew how strong he was. Although the Demons still had a lot of experts, as long as Zhao Hai can grasp an opportunity, then he could surely eradicate every single Demon here.

Zhao Hai’s Domain was still in its drill form as it went about its killing spree. There were some God-rank Demons who wanted to stop Zhao Hai. However, upon meeting the Domain, they were immediately shredded to death.

The Demon Dragon King shouted, “Retreat!” Just as he said that, his Dragon Domain appeared as he slowly drew back. At the same time, his flag kept waving back and forth. It was a signal known to all Demons, informing them to retreat.

Although the Demons were fighting against Zhao Hai’s undead army, they were also keeping attention to the Demon Dragon King’s flag. Upon seeing the Demon Dragon King’s flag, the Demons immediately fought while going in the direction of Demon City.

However, this feat wouldn’t be very easy. The small drills formed by the undead were like slippery fishes, retreating from such conditions was very difficult.

This scene also made Zhao Hai understand how the Demons can survive in a place such as the Demon Realm. And at this time, some Demons had stayed behind.

These Demons didn’t proceed to retreat, instead, they blew themselves up. This caused resounding explosions from all directions, causing massive casualties among the undead.

After Lizzy and Megan saw this, they knew that the Demons had went all out. They didn’t want to fight with the Demons in this situation. Because of this, Lizzy immediately ordered the undead to clump up while pursuing, allowing the Demons more time to withdraw.

But just as the undead drew back, various cavalry units appeared beside the Demon Army before throwing javelins towards the retreating army. Zhao Hai was still using his harassment tactics against the undead, causing more chaos to appear.

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but feel a pain on his heart. He turned his head and looked at Zhao Hai, who had finished reorganizing his army. Also, the Demon Dragon King can also see undead Demons among Zhao Hai’s undead army,

During the battle, there were still Demons who weren’t able to blow themselves up. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t let their deaths be a waste, he turned them into undead immediately.

When he saw this, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but clench his jaws. His hate for Zhao Hai had reached an all-time high. However, he discovered something that made him frustrated. The speed of his army wasn’t as fast as Zhao Hai’s. Before they had regrouped, the undead were already finished. At the same time, the cavalry units were already on the sides of the Demon Army. It seems like they were boxed in with one side missing.

While the Demon Dragon King was looking at Zhao Hai’s army in a daze, two pitiful yells woke him up. The Demon Dragon King immediately turned his head to see a God-ranked expert’s separated head and then another God-ranked expert with a hold in their neck. But even then, nothing was seen beside them.

The God-ranked Demon with a hole on his neck was still alive when the Demon Dragon King saw him. However, he didn’t dare to blow himself up since he was still in the middle of the Demon Race’s formation. If he exploded, then he might take his allies along with him. Because of this, he can only swallow his hatred and normally die.

As soon as the two Demons dies, two spatial rifts appeared right beside them, swallowing them in the process. Then at Zhao Hai’s side were another two spatial rifts where two undead Demons appeared. At the same time, an additional two people appeared. One was Berry while the other was someone the Demon Dragon King haven’t seen before. This person looked like an assassin, he also had a rapier strapped on his back.

Naturally, this person was Shun. He hasn’t been idle after becoming God-rank. Although he had been sparring with Shue, no positive results ever came forth. He was yet to acquire his own Domain.

Shue told him about his experience on how he managed to comprehend a Domain. Because of this, Shun went and looked for a God-rank Demon during the battle and attacked him, hoping to gain insight into his Domain.

In the end, he succeeded. And unexpectedly, his Domain was actually the same stealth type Domain as Berry’s. Berry’s Domain was a huge hook while Shun’s Domain was a rapier.

While the Demons were yet to reorganize, Berry and Shun used this opportunity to kill God-rank Demons. And in order to ensure their safety, Lizzy quickly took them back to the Space before sending them to Zhao Hai’s side.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at their eyes and nodded, “Good, nice job. But don’t take such huge risks next time.” Then he turned his head back to the Demon Dragon King.

At this time, Lizzy’s voice sounded in Zhao Hai’s ear, “Big Brother Hai, demon scorpion. Pay attention since the undead are using their javelins.”

ZHao Hai nodded, then his figure moved and returned inside the formation. After that, the undead formed the demon scorpion formation, the one they also used back against the Fishmen. Since Zhao Hai wasn’t needed at the front, he was repositioned to be at the tail end of the scorpion.

It didn’t take a long time before the cube formation changed into the demon scorpion. After seeing this change, the Demon Dragon King’s expression couldn’t help but turn ugly. He was yet to put his men in order, and now they were clashing again?

The Demon Dragon King couldn’t’ do anything but wave his flag, urging the Demons to retreat. Both the elites and average soldiers continued to draw back. And as they were retreating, they were also rearranging themselves.

The Demon Dragon King had small time to think about new formations. This demon scorpion looked more menacing compared to the drill. Some of the troops on the left and right of the Demon Army went forward and clashed with the two claws of the scorpion.

Despite their current situation, the Demon Dragon King was still confident about the strength of the Demons. He believes that even Zhao Hai’s undead army wouldn’t be able to face the might of the Demons.

However, he was mistaken this time. Zhao Hai simply didn’t give them time to reorganize. When the Demons reached the firing distance, the undead immediately peppered them with javelins.

The Demon Dragon King’s expression couldn’t help but change after seeing the rain of javelins. Zhao Hai didn’t use javelins before, but they already lost too much. Now that javelins were back in the fray, the Demon army’s losses would surely pile up.

But this wasn’t the end. Just as the Demon Dragon King was feeling regret, the skies above him suddenly darkened. A drill formation had appeared from above, and their target was him.

The Demon Dragon King calmed himself down. At this time, changing his position was too late. Just as he was about to be killed, two people suddenly flew up from the side of the Demon Dragon King. The two greeted Zhao Hai’s drill and when they were in a sufficient distance away, they blew themselves up.

These two people were God-rank Demons, so their explosions weren’t weak. Zhao Hai felt the tremendous impact from the explosion on his Domain. His whole figure shook, his face drained of color. Before long, his advance slowed down before he ultimately led his undead to draw back.

The explosions of the God-rank Demons also caused huge damage to the Demon Army. Aside from the Demon King and others who could support a Domain, nearly 10 thousand 9th ranked Demon were killed from the impact.

However, this didn’t mean that the Demon Dragon King remained unscathed, he was also quite injured. But this was the only way to deal with Zhao Hai. If the Demon Dragon King dies, then the whole Demon Army would be finished.

A brave soldier wouldn’t hesitate to sacrifice his arm, and the Demon Army didn’t lack these brave soldiers. Blood dripped on the corners of the Demon Dragon King’s mouth. He knew that fighting would only bring more casualties to the Demons. Because of this, he immediately shouted, “All armies draw back. Return to Demon City!”

This order was quickly passed down to each Demon. The entire Demon Army immediately formed groups before they slowly retreated. On the other hand, there was no way for Zhao Hai to let this opportunity go. Batches upon batches of javelins rained one after another, peppering the entire Demon Army. One could say that every step the Demon Army made, people died. However, they still didn’t dare to turn their heads and fight with Zhao Hai. The Demon Dragon King knew that even more deaths would occur if they do so.

Chapter 787: Drastic Changes In The Icefield

It was a road of death. Every minute, Demons would die. Zhao Hai’s javelins were like a weapon of the Grim Reaper. Each volley caused deaths to mount up.

At this time, the Demon Dragon King deeply regretted his decision to continue their advance. Under such attacks, he wasn’t sure how many people would survive upon returning to Demon City.

The Demons left on the other cities were completely vulnerable in front of Zhao Hai’s army. They were completely unable to stop the attacks.

There was no other way for the Demon Dragon King other than retreat. They were pursued by Zhao Hai up until they reached Demon City. After the Demons arrived, Zhao Hai stopped. He didn’t say a single word as he led his undead and promptly turned back. The Demons had a lot of troops in Demon City. It wouldn’t be good if they were compelled to desperate methods.

After seeing Zhao Hai retreat, the Demon Dragon King let out a long breath. This time, he had led 30 million troops to battle. But now, the number hardly reached 20 million. In this fight, he had lost a third of his troops.

A lot of Demons died in the last battle. They were very heroic, and if they weren’t faced with undead, then they might have already won.

Most armies wouldn’t be able to keep their composure if they lost a third of their numbers. Only the strong willed Demons were able to achieve this feat. But even then, they weren’t proud of this achievement. It was because they lost, they were completely defeated. Moreover, this wasn’t their first defeat in the hands of the same person.

After the Demon Dragon King returned to Demon City, he immediately arranged for those who came with him to take a rest. He also returned to his room to heal himself while also sending a letter to the Great Demon King.

In just one battle, they had lost more than 10 million people. This was something that the Demon Dragon King didn’t imagine. In the past, even the Divine Race wouldn’t think that a battle in the Ark Continent would take so many lives. There were many wars where the Demon Dragon King lost the same number of men, however, he didn’t think that he would do so in the hands of one person.

After Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he immediately arranged people to reoccupy the vacated cities. At this time, the Buddha Empire regained its calm.

Zhao Hai’s two battles between the Demons and the Divine Race had spread to the entire Ark Continent. It didn’t matter if they were Humans or other races, when they received this news, a scene of jubilation erupted.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t idle. He was preparing for another matter, carrying his attack on the Radiant Empire. Zhao Hai was tired of being the receiving end of the attack, he wanted to take shot at the enemy.

Now that the Demons were heavily damaged, Zhao Hai believed that they would stay put for some time. On the other hand, although the Divine Race had lost some people, their major losses were the barbarians and the winged pegasus armies. Because of this, their losses weren’t that great, they may send their troops again at any time.

To be honest, Zhao Hai’s action was mainly in order to get some goblins. At the same time, he also wanted to see whether he can grab one or two magic cannons from the Divine Race.

When Zhao Hai told his plans to Lizzy, she immediately agreed. Although they had lost some undead in the battle against the Demons, their losses of about a million was still smaller compared to the 10 million from the Demons. The battle was completely their victory.

Since they had lost a little, their overall strength wasn’t affected. If they want to attack, they can attack, if they want to defend then they can defend. They still had many tactics that they could use.

Additionally, acquiring goblins for their abilities as well as the magic cannons was something that would benefit their army. Nobody would certainly oppose to this decision.

However, before they could go and deal with the Divine Race, they would still need ample understanding about their structure. They need to think about where to attack from and which place to attack. They wouldn’t want a long term battle against the Divine Race.

As Zhao Hai planned his actions inside the Space, various troops had arrived in the Buddha Empire. Zhao Hai had already left orders for the veteran troops to teach the newcomers. Although these people weren’t really newcomers when it came to battles, they were still greenhorns when it came to fighting the Demons and the Divine Race. They still need those with experience to guide them.

This matter didn’t need Zhao Hai’s direct supervision. He just gave some orders and left it all to the other troops. At the same time, he also gave them sufficient supplies while emphasizing that the troops needed to take a rest.

….

One day, while Zhao Hai was studying the composition of the Divine Race army, Cai’er’s voice was suddenly heard, “Young Master, the God-rank potion is finished.”

When he heard this, Zhao Hai immediately stood up. With a smile on his face he told Laura, “Call Blockhead and Rockhead over to the Space.”

Laura nodded before calling Blockhead and Rockhead over. The two of them already knew about Zhao Hai’s plan, therefore they used the past few days to hand their current tasks over as they waited for Zhao Hai’s call.

When the two entered the Space, Zhao Hai didn’t waste any time and immediately gave them the potions. Then he pushed them to a room and forbade people from disturbing their cultivation.

During the early times when Shue was using the God-rank potion, Zhao Hai was still very anxious. But now, he was already calm. He knew that the God rank potions would work. Unless they forced the potion on a dead person, then they won’t have anything to worry about.

Shortly after Blockhead and Rockhead entered the Space and when Zhao Hai was about to resume his study, the Beast King’s voice was suddenly transmitted from a messenger fish, “Little Hai, are you there? Little Hai? If you hear me, please talk. It’s an urgent matter!” Anxiety was clearly heard from the Beast King’s voice. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare as he immediately took the messenger fish and replied, “Your Majesty, what’s the problem?”

The Beast King’s voice was heard, “Little Hai, bad news. Large quantities of undead from the northern icefield are killing their way into the Prairie. The Polar Bear Tribe, White Tiger Tribe, and the Blue Hawk Tribe are already fighting them. In addition to undead, there are also plenty of Darkness lifeforms. They are all very strong. If you haven’t provided your potions, then these creatures might have already broken through.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, his head couldn’t help but turn dizzy. But he recovered himself as he said, “What are the losses between the three tribes?” At the same time, the image of the northern icefield appeared on the Space’s monitor.

Just as the icefield was shown, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but gasp. The everpresent white color of the icefield had completely changed, it had all been turned into black!

It seems like the entire northern icefield has been covered by a dark mist, it was extremely hard to see a thing. And inside this dark mist were large quantities of undead and creatures of the dark. Their activities seem to be absent of reason, but they had completely filled the entire icefield.

At this time, the Beast King replied, “Their losses aren’t huge, but the undead are very hard to deal with. They have poison in their bodies. Even the dark mist is poisonous. Although it wouldn’t kill people immediately, the poison would impede a person’s fighting strength. The tribes had no choice but to return to the Beastman Prairie.”

Zhao Hai stared at the screen. He can understand the situation more than the Beast King. These undead and dark creatures were indeed numerous. At the same time, wherever these creatures go, the dark mist would follow them. Both of these influences slowly crept towards the center of the Beastman Prairie.

Zhao Hai immediately replied to the Beast King, “Your Majesty, don’t dispatch troops to the frontlines. Instead, have them form a defense in the Prairie. The undead and dark creatures are indeed too many. It is also clear that they aren’t under the control of the Demons. Get ready and have the tribes migrate towards the Aksu Empire. I will inform the people of the Empire. I’ll be keeping attention to the icefield, I’ll report whatever I find.”

The Beast King agreed and didn’t say anything more. Zhao Hai placed the messenger fish down and slowly stood up. He looked at the screen with enraged eyes. He stopped himself from yelling out, he turned his head to Laura and said, “Inform the Aksu Empire that the Beastman are coming. We don’t want any misunderstanding to occur.. I’ll be heading to the icefield to take a look and see what is in there.”

Laura and the others were also shaken by the news. The group absentmindedly nodded, for a moment they didn’t know what to say.

Zhao Hai’s figure moved and vanished from the Space as he appeared inside the northern icefield. As he appeared, he was immediately engulfed by the dark mist. Not far away from him was a skeleton. It had a silver white body that looked quite beautiful.

However, Zhao Hai was not in the mood to appreciate things right now. Just as he came out of the Space, a prompt was suddenly heard, “Huge amount of dark energy toxins entering the Host’s body. Activating detoxification measures. Toxins have been neutralized. Spatial water can now cure the toxin. Toxin added to the Space’s insecticide.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the poison would be so strong that it could actually affect his body. One must know that the spatial water was a powerful antidote against poisons. For the Space to actually proceed to clear the poison meant that the dark mist was very strong.

Just as Zhao Hai was thinking about the announcement, the silvery white skeleton took notice of him. The skeleton immediately charged towards Zhao Hai. At this time, Zhao Hai paid attention to the skeleton. It was very fast and should have a strength not lower than 8th rank. Moreover, there was a silvery white blade on its hand, a type that was probably made from its own body.

Zhao Hai didn’t move, he just stood there and stared at the skeleton. Before long, the skeleton was already near Zhao Hai. It raised its sword up, intending to divide Zhao Hai in two. At this time, Zhao Hai raised his blood ghost staff, repelling the incoming attack. However, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but wrinkle his brow.

Chapter 788: Fuck, This Is Bullshit!

Zhao Hai frowned. Naturally, this wasn’t because he was injured. The skeleton was just about 8th rank, so how could it injure him? Zhao Hai frowned because of the raw strength of the undead. Although it was only 8th rank, it’s power was surprisingly great. The skeleton was actually as strong as a similarly ranked barbarian.

The barbarians were very strong, they were even stronger than most Beastmen. Although the Beastmen were much stronger than the Humans, they were evenly powered with barbarians. And now, this skeleton was as strong as them? Zhao Hai didn’t expect this.

After the silver white skeleton saw that Zhao Hai had repelled its attack, it actually didn’t stop. Instead, it moved and went on to kick Zhao Hai.

Once again, this made Zhao Hai stare. Not only was the skeleton strong, it was actually quick as well. Its movement was much nimbler compared to the other undead.

Naturally, compared to the undead from the Space, this skeleton was nothing. However, it was still an extraordinary event that an uncontrolled undead could exhibit these kinds of movements.

Zhao Hai moved his body and blocked the skeleton’s attack once more. At this time, the skeleton opened its mouth and let out a very loud roar. As the sound resonated, Zhao Hai scanned the surroundings with his divine sense. All the skeletons around them were unexpectedly rushing towards Zhao Hai. This caused another surprise from Zhao Hai, he didn’t think that the skeleton was able to call the other skeletons over. They actually had some sort of communication with each other.

Besides the skeletons in the Space, this was the first time that Zhao Hai saw an intelligent skeleton like this. But he wasn’t afraid. He was planning on capturing these skeletons to see how special they were.

Zhao Hai was certain that these undead weren’t from the Demon Realm. Although there were also wild undead from the Demon Realm, these undead weren’t intelligent. Moreover, the undead in the Demon realm didn’t have this poisonous mist going along with them.

Zhao Hai waved his blood ghost staff and turned it into a large net. He covered the silver skeleton with the net before he flung it into the Space.

As the skeleton entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Virally positive robot detected. Eliminating the virus, virus eliminated. Discovered robot to be hostile towards the Space. Subduing the robot, robot has surrendered.”

“Evolution class robot has been detected. Extracting advantages. All robots in the space can now evolve.”

Zhao Hai stared at this announcement before he smiled. He turned his head and looked at the surrounding skeletons who were coming towards  him. Zhao Hai waved his blood ghost staff continuously as he threw skeletons to the Space one after another. However, no further prompts were heard from the Space. Moreover, Zhao Hai saw that these skeletons were silvery white like the ones before. They were much darker wood in color, seemingly like bronze.

Seeing that nothing remained in the surroundings, Zhao Hai’s body flashed and returned to the Space. Then he turned the silver skeleton into a zombie. After turning the silver skeleton into a zombie, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare, the zombie was very handsome.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t in the mood to pay attention to its face. He immediately asked, “What is your name? And where did you come from?”

The skeleton quickly bowed and answered, “Answering the Master. I am called Ginko, the place the I was born in is called the Underworld, initially as a low-level undead.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then his complexion changed as he said, “Did you just say that you came from the Underworld? Does the Underworld really exist?”

Ginko nodded and said, “Yes Master. I am from the Underworld. I don’t know when I woke up, but at that time, I was a low level grey skeleton. But after killing other skeletons and absorbing their soul fire, I turned into a white skeleton. After that, I became a black skeleton and then a bronze skeleton. At the moment, I am a silver skeleton.” Zhao Hai looked blankly at the skeleton named Ginko. He didn’t think that the underworld really exists. The Underworld was just a plane found in legends. It was even more mysterious compared to the Demon and the Divine Race. And now, there was this skeleton saying that he was from that same Underworld.

The expressions of Laura and the others were also quite ugly. At this time, Zhao Hai looked at Ginko and said, “Just call me Young Master. Since you said that you’re from the Underworld, how did you appear here?”

Ginko replied, “Answering to the Young Master, I also don’t know. Just one day, a large hole appeared not far away from my territory. I walked into that hole and then arrived here.” Zhao Hai’s expression turned uglier. He was certain that a spatial rift had appeared in the Underworld, causing Ginko and the others to come here.

Zhao Hai asked once more, “What is the strongest existence in the Underworld? What grade do you belong to?”

Ginko replied, “Answering to the Young Master. The strongest being in the Underworld is the Hell King. However, the Hell King rarely appears, so the true control of the Underworld relies on the God Kings of the various races. I am just one of the lower beings in the Underworld. I am stronger compared to the grey, white, black, and bronze skeletons. Those above me are the gold skeletons, variant skeletons, crystal skeletons, and the skeleton King. There are also the Skeleton Saint, the Skeleton God, and the Skeleton God King above that.’

Zhao Hai nodded. From what he heard, it seems like the skeletons in the Underworld were divided into 12 ranks. Ginko was in the fifth rank and there were seven ranks who were stronger than him. And since Ginko was equivalent to an 8th rank expert, how powerful were those above him?

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai immediately said, “Ginko, how stronger is the rank higher than you?”

Ginko immediately replied, “Young master, gold skeletons are much stronger and faster than me. A single gold skeleton can fight against ten silver skeletons. Variant skeletons are even more powerful than gold skeletons. Aside from having a harder weapon, they also had their own abilities. These abilities are far different than those on the lower ranks. Crystal skeletons are an evolution of the variant skeletons. Aside from having the abilities of the variant skeletons, crystal skeletons are a qualitative improvement to the variant skeletons. Skeleton Kings are the ones above crystal skeletons. Skeleton Kings have the ability to subdue crystal skeletons to be their subordinates.Then there are the stronger skeleton saints who have the ability to control the heaven and the earth around them. The rank higher than skeleton saint is the skeleton god. Their control over the heavens and the earth would become much more formidable. As for the skeleton god king, I’ll have to ask for forgiveness, I haven’t heard about them.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he can somewhat understand how these skeletons were divided. The details of their power was more pronounced compared to the Humans. From what he understood, controlling the heavens and the earth was actually the Domain. That is to say, unless one becomes a skeleton saint, then they would become Demigods on the verge of comprehending a Domain. Skeleton Gods would be the God-ranks who had their own Domains while skeleton god kings should be Saint Gods. As for the Hell King, Zhao Hai believed that it may be a cultivator like Lu Wei. Zhao Hai thought for a moment before asking another question, “Are there a lot of skeleton saints in the Underworld?”

Ginko nodded and said, “There are plenty of them in the Underworld. Not only the Skeleton race, the Zombie race, Lich Race, Magic Beast Race, and other races have saint level or above. As for their number, I don’t know. The Underworld is ust too big. And although the Skeleton race are most numerous creatures, we aren’t actually the strongest. Compared to the other races, the skeletons could be called weaker.”

The frown on Zhao Hai’s face turned tighter. He didn’t expect this development. Silver skeletons were as strong as 8th ranks. Gold skeletons should not be far from being 9th ranks. This would make variant skeletons medium grade beings in the Underworld, and their number should be uncountable.

Now that a spatial rift to the underworld appeared, beings from the underworld would start to flood the Ark Continent. When that time comes, the Ark Continent would gain yet another strong enemy.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get angry. He couldn’t bear it anymore as he cursed, “Fuck, this is bullshit!” After Zhao Hai arrived at the Ark Continent, he had always been a very careful person in maintaining his personal image. He was almost always polite in his speech. Although he didn’t care too much about how the nobles view him, he was now the representative of the Buda Clan, and he needed to preserve his clan’s face. Because of this, he had always chosen the words coming out of his mouth.

However, he couldn’t bear it this time. There were already the Demons and the Divine Race who wanted to take the Ark Continent. But now, there is the legendary Underworld. This development had completely disrupted Zhao Hai’s plans. So how could he not be angry?

Chapter 789: Last Resort! Good Or Bad?

This was also the first time that Laura and the others have heard those words coming out of Zhao Hai’s mouth. Naturally, they were aware about Zhao Hai’s anger, and they understood his mood. Zhao Hai’s tactics already placed them in an advantageous position against the Demons and the Divine Race. But now, the Underworld suddenly appeared, this caused all of Zhao Hai’s preparations to go to waste.

Zhao Hai’s past arrangement was to isolate the Demons and the Divine Race to the south of the continent while the area on the north becomes their rear.

Now that the Underworld appeared, it was like they were just stabbed at the back, with an extremely poisonous blade. Zhao Hai was already having headaches while dealing with the Demons and the Divine Race. Having the Underworld’s presence didn’t help.

Laura was afraid that Zhao Hai would get too angry. She could still remember the time when Zhao Hai vomited blood after seeing what the Divine Race did. So she turned to Zhao Hai and hugged him, “Brother Hai, calm down. Please. If you get injured, the continent would be in grave trouble.”

Lizzy and the others also ran over to appease Zhao Hai. After some time, Zhao Hai calmed down and breathed some air in. He patted Laura’s head and said, “I’m alright, I’m fine.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand and stored Ginko. Then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, I just heard that the undead are now able to evolve. What does that mean?”

Cai’er looked at Zhao Hai with shining eyes as she replied, “Young Master, in the past, the undead can only upgrade their strength because of the Space and nothing to do with themselves. Now that Ginko has arrived, the undead’s natural ability to evolve has been absorbed into the space. Now, the undead can also evolve without the help of Fuwa and the Hell background. However, the speed of this evolution isn’t fast.”

When he heard Cai’er, Zhao Hai gawked, then his two eyes shined as well as he said, “Good, that is good news. Any improvement to the undead is great for us.”

One of Zhao Hai’s greatest worries was the promotion of the undead. Now that the undead can evolve on their own, Zhao Hai was naturally happy. However, when his thoughts went back to the Underworld, his mood couldn’t help but turn sour.

After seeing that Zhao Hai had recovered, Laura let go of Zhao Hai. Then she looked at Zhao Hai and felt sad, “Brother Hai, what do we do next? The Underworld is certainly as strong as the Demons and the Divine Race. This isn’t good for us, we cannot defend the Beastman Prairie.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Do we have any other choice? Aside from our last plan, we don’t have any other way.”

Laura understood what Zhao Hai meant. Their last plan was to evacuate the Ark Continent’s entire population to the Space.

Lizzy knit her brows and said, “Brother Hai, doing that would be very problematic. Moreover, we don’t even know if the people would agree.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “We can only propose this matter to them and hope for the best. However, we still need to discuss this with Grandpa Green. Laura, please call Grandpa Green and the others over to the Space. And Shue, go and see Blockhead and Rockhead, go see why those two are taking so long to come out.”

Laura and Shue nodded. Laura went on to call Green and the others while Shue went on to the room where Blockhead and Rockhead were.

Blockhead and Rockhead had already succeeded in their promotion and were now taking a bath. Shue went to their room and saw what they were doing, but he didn’t call the two. He just turned back and told Zhao Hai, “Young Master, they have been promoted successfully. They are now taking a bath.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he waved his hand and said, “Take a seat. Shue, Shun, what do you think about taking the people of the Ark Continent into the Space?”

Shue looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I agree to taking them to the Space.”

Zhao Hai stared at Shue and said, “Why?”

Shue replied, “Young Master, do you remember what that immortal cultivator is doing in the Divine Realm and the Ark Continent? He is collecting faith power. It is obvious that this faith power is important to him. If Young Master gets promoted in the future, then wouldn’t you need faith power as well? If you have the people in the Ark Continent in the Space, then they would possibly look at you as a god. Maybe you can collect faith power from them.” Zhao Hai stared, he wasn’t expecting Shue to present this reason.

At this time, Shun added, “That’s right. Young Master, before that immortal cultivator disappeared, he said that he will wait for you in the higher realm. If the Young Master gets stronger in the future, then you will certainly ascend to their plane. If the Young Master doesn’t have people to provide you with faith power, then you would be at a disadvantage. Also, the Young Master shouldn’t forget that the immortal cultivator has a huge sect behind him while the Young Master would have no background. Lastly, if the people of the Ark Continent come to the Space, then the Young Master can choose talented people and promote their strength. Maybe we can form our own sect to fight the immortal cultivators.”

Zhao Hai looked blankly at both Shue and Shun. He wasn’t thinking at this angle before. However, it was indeed an advantageous move if the people of the Ark Continent were to come to the Space. But even then, it was a bit unfair to them. Zhao Hai frowned and said, “If that happens, then wouldn’t the people from the Ark Continent be like caged beasts in the Space?”

Shue replied, “Young Master, putting it that way isn’t pleasant to hear, it will cloud your decision. You have been managing the continent for all this time, so you should know that without you, the continent would have already fallen to the Demons and the Divine Race. Although they would indeed provide the Young Master with faith power once they live in the Space, you would also provide them with a safe place to live in. Also, they are prone to believe in god, so why not make them believe in you. At the very least, you wouldn’t enslave them, right?”

Laura and the others are blankly staring at Shue and Shun. To be honest, they haven’t thought of this, but Laura and the others had to recognize that Shue and Shun had a point. Having the people of the continent come to the Space would be very advantageous to Zhao Hai. Laura and the others already knew that the Space could make Zhao Hai favorable to those who were inside it. If the people of the Ark Continent migrates to the Space, then they would provide Zhao Hai with endless faith power. In the future, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be encumbered with the disadvantage of not having faith power.

The group looked at one another, it seems like Shue and Shun was already convinced by the Space. They were loyal to Zhao Hai would want to benefit him as much as possible.

Zhao Hai was frowning as he sat there. To be honest, he didn’t think that having the people of the Ark Continent in the Space would benefit him. He just didn’t want the Space to be known to others. Now that Shue and Shun told him about it, Zhao Hai was somewhat convinced that there wasn’t anything wrong to have the people of the continent migrate to the Space.

Still, he needed to make a decision after consulting Green and the others. After all, this matter was too big. And like Lizzy said, they were not sure if the people would agree.

Chapter 790: Decision

Green and Merine, along with Kun and Karen, were now in the Space. People Zhao Hai thought to be his elders were inside the Space.

They were yet to know what had happened, but just by listening to Laura they knew that something urgent must have occured. Because of this, they immediately left what they were doing and quickly went to the Space. Green and the others understood that Zhao Hai wouldn’t have called them over if it wasn’t important.

Currently, Green and Merine were mainly responsible for running the Black Wasteland. There were many races in the wasteland, dealing with their affairs was quite a chore. Naturally, since Zhao Hai was busy, these things were handed over to Green and Merine.

Kun was still in charge of Golden Island. Although war was happening in the frontline, people still needed supplies. Zhao Hai already took care of transporting supplies in the frontlines, so Kun was overseeing the transactions in the island.

At the same time, Karen had also been very busy. His team was currently busy with researching defensive formations. But when he heard Zhao Hai’s summons, he immediately entered the Space.

After the group arrived at the villa, they immediately saw Zhao Hai’s unhappy face. Shue and Shun were keeping silent right beside him. Blockhead and Rockhead had just exited their room.

After Green and the others saw Zhao Hai, they knew that he was thinking deeply. Shue and the others didn’t dare to disturb him so Green didn’t hesitate and said, “Young Master, what happened?”

When Zhao Hai heard Green’s voice, he quickly recovered. He looked at the group and hastily got up as he said, “Grandpa Green, Grandma Merine, Grandpa Kun, Father-in-law. Please have a seat. I have an important matter to discuss.”

After the group sat down, Zhao Hai told them about the northern icefield. He told them that the idea of relocating the Ark Continent’s residents to the Space. As soon as Green and the others heard this, all of them stared blankly. The Divine Race and The Demons were yet to be dealt with, and now the Underworld appeared? Anyone who had heard this would would to shout ‘motherfucker!’

There was only a little improvement to the frontline, but now a huge calamity appeared on their backyard. In this case, aside from relocating to the Space, there was no other way to evade massive losses.

After Zhao Hai saw that the group was silent, he continued on and told them about what Shue and Shun just said. He wanted to hear their opinion. Although Zhao Hai had experience in these matters, he was still a beginner in front of these elders.

Not to say about Green and the others, even Shue was more experienced than him. Otherwise, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have needed Shue and Shun to tell him about faith power.

After they heard Zhao Hai, Green and the others frowned. To be honest, they didn’t think about this before. The Space was the biggest secret of the Buda Clan, so they never thought of making it public. Because of this, they shifted the idea of relocating to the Space to being the last of methods they would use. But now that Green and the others listened to Shue and Shun’s idea, they started to think that revealing the Space wouldn’t be a bad idea.

Green hesitated for some time before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, I don’t expect this thing to go smoothly, but we can try it anyway. But after we do this, the Divine Race and the Demons would surely be aware of your Space. Even if they don’t know what the Space is like, they would still have a general idea about it. And once the Divine Race knows, they would also report this to the immortal cultivator. When we ascend to the immortal cultivation plane, that immortal would surely have this in mind.’

Zhao Hai nodded, he was aware of this point. It would be impossible to hide it when the massive population of the Ark Continent suddenly vanished. Lu Wei would definitely get wind of this and make certain preparations. Zhao Hai needed to be careful with this.

Perhaps the immortal cultivators would think that Zhao Hai had a rare treasure and would have greedy thoughts about it. When that time comes, Zhao Hai would definitely be chased by those cultivators, making Zhao Hai’s troubles even bigger.

To Zhao Hai, this was a very hard decision. On one hand, he could keep his peaceful life but would sacrifice the Ark Continent. On the other, he would be in more trouble but he would provide safety to the people of the continent. Zhao Hai was not a saint, so before he made this decision, he needed to properly weigh the advantages and disadvantages.

After seeing that Zhao Hai stayed silent, Green said, “If we don’t help the people of the Ark Continent, then they would be in danger. Moreover, we would have no way to gain faith power in the future. There are surely advantages and disadvantages to migrating the Ark Continent’s people to the Space, this decision is entirely up to you, Young Master.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I believe we should relocate the people of the Ark Continent into the Space. For us, the benefits outweigh the shortcomings. In the future, it would be impossible to hide the existence of the Space. It would be revealed sooner or later. We might as well save the people of the continent at this point.”

Merine nodded, “If the Young Master has decided, then we can proceed to the next step. Young Master, I believe we should start with talking to the other races. There may be Demon spies among the Humans. Relatively speaking, there would be less traitors among the foreign races.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “My relationship with the other races is pretty good as well. We’ll start with the Dwarves. After all, the Dwarves are at the forefront. If a fight were to happen, then they would be in the most danger.”

Merine nodded and said, “I also think that the Fishmen would agree. There is a sea on the Space’s background. And since the Fishmen doesn’t need to survive, then it would be easier for them to move in immediately.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “I’m actually quite worried about the Fishmen. There are too many people in the sea. Although the Space is huge, I’m afraid it would take a year before relocating all of the Fishman into the Space.”

Laura smiled and said, “I think that the Fishmen can be delayed. Whether it is the Divine Race or the Demons, they don’t seem to be very good at sea battles. The sea should be the safest place right now. We should ask the Dwarves and the Elves. I don’t think there would be any problems with the Elves. The most important thing for them is their tree of life, and we have several of those trees inside the Space. If they decide to settle down, we can plant more trees of life for them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “The Beastmen should be easy to persuade as well. What they value the most is the Prairie, and the Space has a much better grassland in comparison. At the same time, the magic beasts in the Space should be sufficient for them.”

The group discussed even more and decided to approach the Dwarves first. Although the Beastmen were also at the frontlines, the Prairie was just too big. Moreover, the Beastmen weren’t weak. The Underworld had just opened, so powerful creatures should arrive quite later on, the Beastmen could still defend against the advancing underworld creatures.

However, Zhao Hai still wanted to approach Wales, so that he could prepare in advance. After all, Wales was already aware of the Space.

In order for this matter to do good, Zhao Hai would do it himself. Billy was currently inside the mountain along with the other Dwarves. They were building weapons every day in preparation to deal with the Demons and the Divine Race.

Billy was also aware about the positive development in the frontlines, so he was quite happy. Because of this, he took the initiative to head towards Iron Mountain and personally help in making the iron chains for the magic cannons.

Billy was currently hammering a piece of ore when Zhao Hai arrived. After hearing that Billy was working, Zhao Hai immediately went to the cave where Dwarves did their work.

The sound of hammering was quite loud on the ears. Dwarves had covered their ears as they proceeded to use their hammers. Each hammering came with sweat and dedications from the Dwarf Race.

Zhao Hai arrived by Billy’s side and patted him on the shoulder. Billy was also blocking his ears, otherwise, he would turn deaf from the loud noise.

After sensing Zhao Hai’s pat, Billy immediately turned his head. When he saw that it was Zhao Hai, he didn’t speak, instead, he gestured to a door at the side of the mountain before they proceeded to walk out.

When they arrived outside, Billy removed his ear stoppers and then turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Why are you here? Did something happen in the frontlines?”

Zhao Hai looked at Billy and bitterly smiled, “Something did happen, but not in the frontlines. Let’s take a walk, I’ll tell you along the way.” Then they walked towards the Dwarves’ Divine Palace while Zhao Hai told Billy about the spatial rift on the northern icefield, telling the Dwarf Patriarch that the Underworld has been connected to the Ark Continent.

Billy carefully listened, he didn’t believe that Zhao Hai would deceive him. Therefore, after Zhao Hai’s report, Billy calmly looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What do you have in mind?”

Looking at Billy’s calm demeanor, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be curious, “Why aren’t you worried?’

Billy laughed and said, “There’s no use in being worried at this point. It seems like my time to die for the continent has come. I’m a resident of the Ark Continent. I’m not afraid to sacrifice myself.”

Zhao Hai admired Billy’s heroic spirit. Zhao Hai said, “I have a solution. But you need to come to a place with me.” Then he waved his hand as they appeared in the Space.

Chapter 791: Unexpected Decision From the Fishmen and the Lyon Empire

BIlly looked at the Space in a daze, all of it was beyond his comprehension. Zhao Hai looked at Billy and said, “Patriarch, come with me. I’ll discuss with you in detail.” Then he lead Billy to the villa.

Billy was similarly stunned when he arrived at the Villa. This was because he didn’t expect to see Laura and the others there. Zhao Hai introduced Billy to the others before inviting him to sit down. Megan handed Billy a glass of wine before Zhao hai started talking about everything inside the Space.

Fully explaining the Space couldn’t just be done inside the villa. So Zhao Hai took Billy to see the background and introduced it.

Five hours passed since Zhao Hai began to talk to Billy. By the time they returned to the villa, Billy already had a general understanding of the Space.

After they sat down, Zhao Hai gave Billy a glass of wine. Billy drank all of it, and then asked for seconds before placing it down and turning to Zhao Hai, “You want the Ark Continent’s people to migrate to the Space?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Although it can be said that I am a god inside this place, you should also know that I have no plans to oppress you. Moreover, this is the safest way we can go forward, I don’t have any other plans. I won’t force you to come to the Space, everything is up to your choice. I will still participate in the fight against the Demons and the Divine Race. However, to tell you the truth, I can’t find any future in fighting the two. And now that the Underworld has come, my confidence in defending has gotten lower.”

Billy nodded. He was clear about the situation of the Ark Continent. Although he wasn’t in the frontlines, there were Dwarves there to provide reports in addition to Zhao Hai’s news. Although Zhao Hai gained recent victories, discerning people can see that the Demons and the Divine Race were just being harassed by Zhao Hai. Once they find ways to go around Zhao Hai’s antics, then they would attack once again. And now, there was the Underworld.

Billy turned to look at Zhao Hai and said, “I know how you have it hard. However, I cannot take responsibility of this matter alone. You should also be aware of how the Dwarves do things. Any matter needed to be discussed with everyone. I’ll go back and ask for their opinion on this.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright. But I hope to hear your decision as soon as possible. We can’t drag this matter for a long time. The Underworld’s residents are getting closer and closer. And once the Demons and the Divine Race discovers that the Underworld has come, then they would certainly attack. When that time comes, things might be too late.”

Billy nodded, “Rest assured, I will give you an answer as soon as possible. Please lead me back.” Zhao Hai nodded before he lead Billy back to his mountain.

After Billy returned, he immediately convened the elders and the village chiefs. He told the the Ark Continents current state before proposing Zhao Hai’s idea.

While Billy was talking with his people, Zhao Hai went on to visit the Beast King. He also took the Beast King to the Space. And just like Billy, he introduced the Space while proposing his plan.

Naturally, the Beast King didn’t agree immediately. The Beastman Race’s government was much looser than the Dwarves. The influence of the Beast King wasn’t as powerful as the Patriarchs of each tribe. So Zhao Hai lead the Beast King back to the Prairie to discuss the matter with his people. After leading the Beast King out, Zhao Hai didn’t immediately go to the Elves. Instead, he went to the Herculean Bull camp and looked for Wales.

The Herculean Bulls had also sent their cavalry to help Zhao Hai in the Buddha Empire. One can say that Zhao Hai had Wales’ unconditional support.

Wales knew that the changes in the northern icefield wasn’t good news. The powerful northern tribes were already promoted to 9th rank by Zhao Hai, and yet they were still driven pack into the Prairie. This alone fully explained how strong the creatures of the Underworld were. An enemy at the icefield was akin to having a knife at the back of Zhao Hai. Therefore, Wales was very anxious in the past few days.

When he heard that Zhao Hai came, Wales immediately welcomed him to the tent. As they entered, Wales gave the guards and order, “Guard the tent, don’t let anybody approach.” The guard nodded before walking out.

Yale and Mendez were also inside the tent. Wales looked at Zhao Hai and said, “How come you have time to visit? Do you have any plans?”

Zhao Hai looked at Wales and smiled, “Brother, you should already know about the Space. I want the Cow-headed race to move to the Space. You can still herd there, keeping your present life while being safe.

Wales couldn’t help but stare, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Are you sure about this?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I’ve decided. There is no safer way for the continent other than this. I have already told the Beast King about the Space, and he said it needed to be discussed. Brother, you need to be an example and help the Beast King out. You know how good the Space is better than anyone in the Prairie. What do you think?”

Wales nodded and said, “Give me a few days. I don’t think there’ll be any problems. Rest assured.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he looked at Wales and laughed, “Brother, later on we can drink daily together. Hahaha.”

Wales smiled. He knew that inside the Space, Zhao Hai was a god. He can go wherever he wanted to go and he can do whatever he wants to do. It would be very easy for Zhao Hai to drink with Wales everyday.

Wales laughed and replied, “You better give us some good pastures. Our entire cow-headed race will be depending on you.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Brother, rest assured, the grass in the Space is much better than in the Prairie. As long as you move there, you won’t have any more problems.”

Wales nodded, “Good. I don’t have anything else to ask. Just wait for my news, I will certainly do well in the following days.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said his goodbyes to Wales before returning to the Space. After that, he went to the Elves. Zhao Hai couldn’t forget the Elf Queen’s shocked face when she saw the trees of life inside the Space.

Nobody could blame the Elf Queen, the Elves treasured their tree of life. But in Zhao Hai’s Space, there seem to be one in every direction. There were even two of them beside the door of Zhao Hai’s villa. Moreover, these trees of life looked healthier than the one back in the Elf Forest.

Although she was dumbfounded by what she saw, the Elf Queen didn’t immediately agree to migrating to the Space. After all, she also needed to discuss this matter with the elders.

Zhao Hai didn’t oppose to this decision as he gave an understanding nod. After that, he immediately went to the Fishmen to see the Mermaid Queen. Naturally, he also took the Queen to the Space and introduced her with the surroundings. He also led her to the place in the background he specially prepared for the FIshman Race.[1]

Zhao Hai expected the Queen to delay her decision and discuss the matter with her people. However, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare when the Queen agreed to migrate immediately. She told Zhao Hai that she would organize the move as soon as she gets back from the Space.

This was completely unexpected, but Zhao Hai was still happy. He immediately opened a spatial rift, enabling the Fishmen access to the Space at all times.

Zhao Hai  didn’t think that the first ones to move would be the Fishmen. But Zhao Hai was also glad. The Fishmen were the easiest people to settle in. Unlike the other races, the Fishmen didn’t need houses nor tents. As long as they were in the sea, then they can already take care of themselves.

After having Cai’er manage the Fishmen, Zhao Hai and Green returned to the Black Wasteland. Then the Buda Clan’s people and slaves, along with the Diamond Ape Tribe, moved and settled down in the Space.

These people weren’t with the Buda Clan for a day or two, it could be said that they were completely loyal to Zhao Hai. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to have these people move to the Space first as an example to the other residents of the continent.

After moving his people to the Space, Zhao Hai immediately went to look for the leaders of the various Empires of the continent. He told them about the state of the continent and about the Space. Finally, he proposed the migration of the continent’s residents towards the Space.

The various leaders didn’t agree immediately. They knew that once they entered the Space, then it would akin to being on Zhao Hai’s hands. If Zhao Hai had anly plans for them, then they couldn’t do anything to rebel.

Although there were God-rank experts among the enemies, these experts weren’t invincible. However, in Zhao Hai’s Space, Zhao Hai was a literal god. If Zhao Hai wants them to die, then it would be impossible for them to live. This was why they were reserved about the decision, this was the same case as the other races in the continent.

But out of Zhao Hai’s expectation was the Lyon Empire. Zhao Hai also told the Lyon Empire’s Great Nobles about his plans. Who would’ve known that after Zhao Hai proposed his idea, the Great Nobles of the Empire immediately agreed. All of them quickly moved their families to the Space while also helping Zhao Hai move the Lyon Empire’s residents.

Zhao Hai didn’t know why this was the case. But the true reason was because the Lyon Empire was already convinced of Zhao Hai’s strength. The people of the other Empires might know Zhao Hai’s might from the battle with the Demons, but the Lyon Empire were already aware of it when he extinguished the Dragons. The people of the Lyon Empire believed that since Zhao Hai assured them safety inside the Space, then safety would definitely be provided. Hence they decided to not delay and move immediately.

* * *

From my advance reading, this is the main background of the Space, not those that needed to be purchased.

Chapter 792: Remaking The Ark Continent

There wasn’t much mystery as to why the Lyon Empire agreed to enter the Space. On the other hand, Zhao Hai doesn’t understand why the Mermaid Queen agreed. Although Zhao Hai was glad that they agreed, he still wondered why.

Actually, this was because the Mermaid clan was different compared to the Elves, Beastmen, and Dwarves. The three latter races had members who had ascended to the Divine Realm while the mermaid race had no ascenders. In other words, they don’t have a powerful backer.

Because of this, the Fishmen immediately agreed to enter the Space. The Mermaid Queen knew that Zhao Hai would eventually defeat the Demons and the Divine Race. And although the Fishmen would have it better, their state would still be different compared to the Elves and the other two races. If Zhao Hai succeeded in his counter attack, then the Elves could meet with their people in the Divine Realm. Once they get in contact, their situation would be much safer. The case was similar to the Beastmen and the Dwarves.

But the Fishman Race was different, they didn’t have any people to help them in the Divine Realm. Even if Zhao Hai succeeded in defeating the invaders, the Fishmen still wouldn’t gain any advantage.

The Mermaid Clan had a lot of 9th ranks, but nobody was able to reach God-rank. This worried the Mermaids. Because of this, they saw hope in Zhao Hai and the potion that he had.

Although Zhao Hai’s potions could only promote people to 8th and 9th rank, Zhao Hai told them that he has yet to develop a potion for God-rank. This meant that the potion was on its way to being made. This was too tempting for the Fishmen, so the Mermaid Queen immediately agreed to enter Zhao Hai’s Space. The Mermaid Queen also saw the place that Zhao Hai had arranged for them, and to be honest, it was a much better place than where they were living right now. The Mermaid Queen had no qualms about moving their entire race over.

Although Zhao Hai was shocked at the decisions made by the Mermaid Queen and the Great Nobles, he was happy with their quick response. And even if they had some reservations at this point, they would slowly accept Zhao Hai when they live in the Space.

The Mermaid Clan and the Great Nobles took the lead in entering the Space. With the influence of the Great Nobles as well as Zhao Hai’s appeal as the Emperor, the civilians of the Lyon Empire also agreed. After all, their almighty Emperor would take them to a place devoid of war and was plentiful in food and clothing. Moreover, they also won’t need to worry about the Demons and the Divine Race.

Although the way Zhao Hai became Emperor was quite special, the people of the Lyon Empire were still very respectful towards him. This was because Zhao Hai had essentially rescued them from the Dragons. Moreover, Zhao Hai was taking the lead in resisting the Demons and the Divine Race. Even if they weren’t Beastmen, they would still respect a strong and powerful person. This was because in the Ark Continent, the stronger the person, the more respect he would gain, and Zhao Hai was a very strong man.

With Zhao Hai’s fame as well as the help of the Great Nobles, the Lyon Empire’s people began to move towards the Space. Naturally, they didn’t know about the specifics of the Space. The only thing they knew was that they were going to migrate.

And along with the movement of the Lyon Empire, the Buddha Empire’s people were also affected. It was impossible to hide the Lyon Empire’s migration to the Buddha Empire. After all, the Buddha Empire has taken refuge in the Lyon Empire. Because of this, when the commoners of the Buddha Empire heard that the Lyon Empire was migrating, they also prepared their things for migration.

People were sometimes subjected to blind obedience. And who do these civilians follow? Naturally it was the Nobles. And with Zhao Hai’s call, the commoners will surely follow. These commoners knew that the Nobles might have known something that they don’t. Therefore, once they saw the nobles moving, they suddenly thought that the Lyon Empire might be in danger. If this was true, then they needed to move quickly.

There were a lot of people with the same ideas. It was because of this that the entire population of the Lyon Empire started to move. From the commoners, to small nobles, and to the Great Nobles. All of them packed up their things and prepared to move out.

The Buddha Empire’s Imperial Clan as well as its Great Nobles couldn’t just sit still with this development. If their subordinates decided to move, then what use would they have? What would a Noble Title and a Crown do? They would become Generals with no army.

The Buddha Empire’s Nobles convened before deciding to migrate as well. The Buddha Emperor and the others understood how bad it would be for them if they didn’t move. The Demons and the Divine Race were yet to break through, however, the Buddha Empire’s people were currently inside the Lyon Empire. If the war continues for long, then the citizens would slowly be integrated to the Lyon Empire. So when Zhao Hai drives the invaders out, will the citizens come back? Because of this, the Buddha Empire’s nobles decided that it would be better to be inside Zhao Hai’s Space. At the very least, they would still have their own people and territory.

Zhao Hai had promised them that after moving to the Space, then they would be given land that was just like the Buddha Empire. Cities would be made and the place would look and feel like the old Buddha Empire.

Zhao Hai can definitely achieve this promise. The Space is under his control, and he can change its terrain at will. Because of this, Zhao Hai can change the Space’s terrain and make the Buddha Empire out of essentially nothing. It would be no different from the Buddha Empire outside.

Zhao Hai knew everything about the Buddha Empire as well as the rest of the Ark Continent. Zhao Hai ordered Cai’er to make the Space’s background to be like the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai hadn’t prepared to migrate the Ark Continent’s people to the Space. And since he didn’t want people to go to his villa everyday, He had a separate continent made with the same structure as the Ark Continent, he would have people move there.

However, Zhao Hai was not only building the terrain of the Ark Continent, he needed to make cities as well. And naturally, this came at a price. The Space deducted tens of millions of gold coins from Zhao Hai’s account, almost resetting Zhao Hai’s money to only a couple of gold coins.

Zhao Hai looked at the rapid decline of his gold coins with a frown on his face. In the end, the number stopped going down, leaving Zhao Hai with a bit more than 10 thousand. Zhao Hai felt his heart stop, but fortunately Cai’er told him that there were a lot of things in the Space that can be sold. As long as those things mature, then they can get millions of gold coins once more.

Zhao Hai was confused by this. He remembered that the crops from the Space weren’t worth this much money. If he was able to sell them for millions of gold coins, then he would’ve already done it a long time ago.

It was only after he asked Cai’er that he understood. Those plants were cultivated in the magic world backgrounds. Plants harvested there were more than those grown in the Space’s background.

After hearing this, Zhao Hai’s sadness immediately vanished. Zhao Hai wasn’t a stingy person, and he knew how much tens of millions of gold coins can do in the Space.

As for the migration, the Fishmen didn’t need to be managed as much as the Humans. This time, Zhao Hai was taking care of the Lyon Empire. It was good that the Great Nobles of the Empire were already familiar with the environment. They immediately established their authority before leading the commoners in.

The civilians that entered the Space was actually a mix between the Lyon and Buddha Empire’s commoners. The people of the Buddha Empire were already sent to the Space’s Buddha empire. Later on, when the Buddha Empire’s Nobles arrive, the Empire would be re-established once more.

When the people from the Buddha Empire saw their homes, the couldn’t help but cry. This was especially true for the old people, they really thought that they had returned to their hometowns. They never expected that they would be able to see their homes for the rest of their lives. Although this wasn’t the original Buddha Empire, it was not different to their original home, all of them were very happy.

Fortunately for Zhao Hai’s pockets, the Radiant Empire has been completely decimated by the Divine Race. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t need to reconstruct the Empire inside the Space. The Space’s Ark Continent was much smaller compared to the original one; it didn’t have the Black Wasteland, the Carrion Swamp, the Northern Icefield, and other uninhabited places.

If Zhao Hai really remade the Ark Continent, then he would surely be bankrupt. Even if he sold his own clothes, we still wouldn’t be able to remake the Ark Continent.

The Buddha Empire and Lyon Empire’s mass migration naturally couldn’t be hidden from the other people. This made the other Empires unable to sit still.

The first to become anxious was the Rosen Emperor. The Emperor was Zhao Hai’s father-in-law, so he supported Zhao Hai. However, he was still afraid that after moving to the Space, his high status would be gone. This made him think twice. But after seeing the actions made by the Lyon and Buddha Empires, his heart began to beat quickly.

However, even if his heart was beating fast, his actions were the contrary. On the other hand, another person made a quick move, it was Wales!

Chapter 793: Agreement!

After receiving Zhao Hai’s notice, Wales immediately gathered the heads of the cow-headed race and discussed the migration with them.

Wales’ prestige in the Cow-headed race was quite high. When the Herculean Bulls were in a slump, he led them to regain their place. Although Zhao Hai’s help was critical to the success, it still doesn’t take away from the fact that Wales was a talented leader.

At the same time, Zhao Hai held a high status in the Cow-headed race. After all, he was their Foreign Prince as well as the Beastman Race’s Foreign Prince. Because of this, after Zhao Hai suggested that they move, none of the Cow-headed race’s patriarchs disagreed.

However, the Cow-headed race was no small group in the Prairie. It would take a long time for them to be moved. Because of this, their migration was much slower compared to the Humans and the Fishmen.

But this matter also highlighted the advantages of the Beastmen. Since they have tents, it didn’t take too long for their property to be transferred to the Space. This nomadic way of life proved to be more convenient compared to the Humans when it came to migration.

When Zhao Hai heard that Wales was done preparing, he immediately opened a spatial rift near the Herculean Bulls’ camp. Then he started to guide the Cow-headed Beastmen to enter the Space.

The place where Wales entered was just right behind the Lyon Empire. In this place, there was a huge piece of grassland, much bigger than the original Beastman Prairie. There wouldn’t be any problems if the entire Beastman Race relocated here.

Moreover, the grass in the Space was much more abundant compared to the outside. At the same time, they regrow quicker. This would make the lives of the herding Beastmen much better.

Zhao Hai doesn’t intend to separate the Humans and the other races. After all, they used to live together. Moreover, Zhao Hai noticed that the races in the Ark Continent actually complemented each other, able to live alongside each other in harmony. If it wasn’t for the Radiant Church, then there won’t be any discord between the various races.

After the Cow-headed Beastmen entered the Space, they immediately took a liking to it. For them, the place was just like heaven. Blue sky, green grass, jade textured water; everything here made up for the most ideal place for herding.

The Cow-headed Beastmen couldn’t help but smile widely at the place. Some elderly Cow Beastmen even went to the ground and chewed on the grass. After tasting them, their eyes shone as they loudly said, “This is high grade grass! The Prince hasn’t deceived us, this is the ideal place for us Beastmen!”

The cheer of the people resounded all over the place.

In the entire Cow-headed race, the last to enter was Wales’ Herculean Bull Tribe. However, Zhao Hai had already arranged a good spot for them to transfer their golden tent to as soon as they came in.

Wales was more than satisfied with the grassland around him. After looking out, he thought that this was a nice place to settle in.

Just like the Lyon Empire and the Buddha Empire, Wales’ move to the Space influenced the entire Beastman Race. After seeing the Cow-headed race willingly entering Zhao Hai’s Space, they started to be convinced to move as well.

After Wales and the others entered the Space, Zhao Hai wasn’t too anxious of bringing them back out. In fact, Zhao Hai wanted Wales to stay inside for a while so that Wales can help sway the minds of the other Beastmen.

After settling down for some time, Wales and some of the Cow Beastmen went out of the Space. The place where they appeared out of was Beast God City.

Wales now understood how Zhao Hai was able to appear on the Prairie on a whim. It turned out that it was because of the Space. Wales came out of the Space and immediately went to the Beast King’s Palace in order to inform the Beast King about their condition inside Zhao Hai’s Space.

The Beast King also wanted to move the Beastman Race to the Space. He knew that it was much safer inside the Space compared to outside. Migrating there would a good for the entire Beastman Race.

However, it was clear that the Beast King’s words alone wouldn’t make this happen. Therefore, he can only discuss this matter with the Patriarchs of the big warring clans. He wanted them to move as soon as possible.

Even so, the Patriarchs still didn’t agree. This annoyed the Beast King. With the White Tigers, the Polar Bears, and the Blue Hawks being held back, this meant that their enemy was a strong one. Additionally, there was the encroaching poisonous dark mist. Counter-attacking and reclaiming lost lands was virtually impossible. In this case, wouldn’t moving to the Space a much better choice?

However, the Beastmen had the same mentality as the Humans when it came to this matter. They needed someone to take the lead. Once one of them went and migrated, then it would be easier for the others to follow suit.

The Beast King actually wanted his Tiger Tribe to take the lead. After all, he was the Tiger Race’s patriarch, it would be appropriate for them to make the first step. However, this move might not be enough to convince the other races.

If the Tiger Tribe were the only ones to do this, then the effect might only be light. Just as the Beast King was annoyed at this matter, Wales came and told him that the Cow headed Race had already settled down inside the Space. This was definitely a good news for the Beast King.

After hearing Wales’ report, the Beast King immediately decided to call the Patriarchs of the big warring tribes. He wanted them to hear Wales’ report firsthand.

Although the Cow-headed race wasn’t considered as a warring tribe, they were still quite influential in the Prairie. Their special relationship with Zhao Hai provided them with a higher status among other Beastmen. All of the Beastmen know about the matters between Zhao Hai and the Herculean Bulls.

Also, Zhao Hai’s status had risen even more when he sold the Beastmen his grain, when he found the Beast God’s Spear, and when he established a milk wine business with the entire Prairie. All of these feats elevated Zhao Hai’s image inside the hearts of the Beastmen.

And now that the Demons and the Divine Race had come, Zhao Hai’s status became even higher. This was because Zhao Hai was in the forefront of the battle between the two invaders. The Beastmen admires brave people the most, because of this, their respect for Zhao Hai was quite high.

After the Patriarchs heard Wales’ report about the Space, all of them became excited. However, they had a request, they wanted to personally visit the Space.

When the Beast King heard this, he immediately took his messenger fish and told Zhao Hai about what happened.

Zhao Hai didn’t even need to think about it. Inside the conference room, a spatial rift suddenly appeared. After that, the Patriarchs were then led to witness the Space for themselves.

These Beastmen have always been weary about Zhao Hai’s skills. But for the sake of the Beastman Race, they still entered the Space.

The place where Zhao Hai sent them to was the place where the Cow-headed Beastmen were located. After looking at the grassland, the Beastmen Patriarchs immediately believed Wales’ words. The grass was indeed very good.

Beastmen had been herding for all their lives. For them, good pastures can be discerned in just one glance. This grassland was indeed very good and there were even plenty of water sources. It would be very strange if the Beastmen didn’t move after seeing this.

The Beastmen Patriarchs stayed in the Space for quite some time before they left. Once they got out, the Patriarch immediately returned to their territories and prepared their people to move out.

Their decision made Zhao Hai smile. And even more worth celebrating was the fact that the Rosen Empire had decided to move in as well. In order to convince the Emperor, Zhao Hai even promised him that there would be no change in authority once they move to the Space. Zhao Hai also showed the Space’s Rosen Empire to the Emperor. Because of this, the Emperor finally agreed.

The last time the Rosen Emperor visited the Space, the new Ark Continent was yet to be made. Now that a complete copy of the Rosen Empire was created, and people were going to live here, the Rosen Emperor naturally agreed.

Actually, the Rosen Emperor was still quite reserved about the decision. After all, he was Zhao Hai’s father-in-law. Once he entered the Space, then his position as an elder would be affected. But in the end, after Lizzy’s persuasion, the Rosen Emperor finally agreed.

As the matter stands,  only the Elves, the Dwarves, and the Aksu Empire were yet to make a decision. At this moment, it had been half a month after the last attack made by the Divine Race.

Half a month wasn’t a long time, and this showed why Zhao Hai’s Space was a wonderful thing. In just half a month, Zhao Hai was able to move most of the people from the Buddha and the Lyon Empire into the Space. At the same time, large numbers of Beastmen and Fishmen had also moved in.

But although Zhao Hai was taking care of the migration, he still kept an eye out for the actions made by the Demons and the Divine Race. At this time, the Demons and the Divine Race were focused on amassing troops. Their losses in their past operation wasn’t small, so they needed some reinforcements to replace the losses. It was clear that they were yet to discover the arrival of the Underworld. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have waited for the troops and instead went forward and just attacked.

Less than two days after the Beastmen and the Rosen Empire started to move to the Space, the Aksu Empire, Elves, and Dwarves also agreed to migrate. The Aksu Empire had no special requests. On the other hand, the Dwarves and Elves had something to ask before migrating. The Elves wanted Zhao Hai to move their entire city into the Space. The Dwarves requested Zhao Hai to get the ores that they had mined all these years and then take them to the Space.

Chapter 794: Blown Away

The Demon Dragon King looked at the report on his table. This was his fifth time reading the report, he has yet to comprehend what it meant.

This report was none other than the Ark Continent’s mass migration. The report stated that the Buddha and the Lyon Empire just moved while the Aksu and Rosen Empires were packing their things. At the same time, the Beastmen were also moving. The Dwarves and the Elves’ situation were unclear.

The report also stated that once the migration becomes successful, then there would be no people left in the Ark Continent.

The Demon Dragon King doubted the authenticity of this information. Where would the people of the Ark Continent move? The continent was a huge place, where would they fit?

The Demon Dragon King knew that the Ark Continent had a lot of people. The Humans alone accounted for more than a billion people. With the other races included, then it would reach a couple billion people. What place would allow this many people to live in? Moreover, the food and living conditions of these people needed to be considered. And now that the Ark Continent showed their ability to resist, why would they decide to move?

However, the Demon Dragon King knew that it would be impossible for their spies to deceive him. This made him even more confused.

Although it was the truth, it was still too hard to believe. Therefore, he was stuck on what decision to make upon receiving the report.

He didn’t know what Zhao Hai was scheming. After their multiple confrontations, the Demon Dragon King had learned to fear Zhao Hai’s plans. If the Demon Dragon King loses more people, then he wouldn’t be able to shoulder the responsibility.

At the same time, the Divine Race also received this information. The Divine Race had their own spies in the Ark Continent. After all, the Radiant Church had managed it for many years, their foundation was quite solid. With how many people they had, weeding them out was quite hard.

It was only because the Ark Continent were strict in the past that these people hid themselves while some were being ambushed. However, since the Ark Continent had gotten more chaotic than before, it was inevitable that the attention on the spies had lessened. Therefore, the Divine Race were able to receive reports from the Ark Continent.

Like the Demon Dragon King, the Divine Race were also baffled by the report. They couldn’t comprehend what it meant. They even thought that the information was a trap.

The reason these people were yet to make a move was because they had yet to find a way to deal with Zhao Hai’s harassment tactics. Zhao Hai’s move was just too scary.

They did exactly what Zhao Hai wanted, giving him time. At this time, the Buddha and Lyon Empire had been moved to the Space. The Aksu and Rosen Empire had also begun their move along with the Elves and the Dwarves.

One could say that the most difficult to move were the Elves and the Dwarves. The Dwarves needed to have mines where they live. Therefore, Zhao Hai prepared a place with an iron and coal mine for them.

Since the Space leveled up, Zhao Hai can now make optional arrangements for the minerals of the Space. Because Zhao Hai had pure iron, he decided to place it in the new Ark Continent’s Dwarf mountain, allowing it to turn the rocks around it into iron.

On the other hand, the Elves were more difficult. They were used to living in a forest, the type that was never been touched. This was a difficult condition, needing specific planning for the Space. Having a new forest in a short time was just impossible. Zhao Hai can only leave a place for the Elves to plant trees in.

In the end, Zhao Hai decided to choose a forested background and modify it to look like the Elven Forest. The only thing he couldn’t achieve was the Elven Tree City itself.

Zhao Hai didn’t know what kind of tree it was. The Elves had grown it for a long time, it was impossible to duplicate that city in the Space.

It was fortunate that the Elves asked Zhao Hai to relocate the tree itself into the Space. After thinking about it, Zhao Hai agreed.

To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t want to leave the Elven Tree City behind as well. To Zhao Hai, that city was a miracle of nature. When Zhao Hai agreed to take the Elven Tree City along, the Elves decided to dig the city out. Otherwise, there would be now way for Zhao Hai to take it to the Space.

But as the Elves were starting to dig, Zhao Hai told them that there was no need. Zhao Hai guaranteed them that the tree wouldn’t be affected by the move.

The Space hadn’t disappointed Zhao Hai, it easily absorbed the Elven Tree City. The Elves had now officially settled inside the Space.

The condition made by the Dwarves were very unique. They wanted Zhao Hai to take the weapons and armor, as well as the ingots that they had accumulated over the years. Naturally, Zhao Hai was happy to agree.

Although the Space already had a large amount of iron, Zhao Hai was still happy to add some more.

But when Zhao Hai saw the Dwarves’ stock, he couldn’t help but be shocked. The Dwarves had almost hollowed the mountain range after all these years. And all of the iron ore that they weren’t able to process were stockpiled and then turned to ingots for later use. Also, one needed to know that the amount of ore mined in a day was much bigger than the amount that could be processed in the same timeframe.

The iron ore was just too much, Zhao Hai simply couldn’t estimate it. The iron ingots and products were already piled in huge mountain-like piles, not to mention the iron ore. The Dwarves’ stockpile was just too large.

After taking all these things, Billy also proposed something. He wanted to leave a few people behind and completely dig the entire mountain of ores.

When Zhao Hai heard Billy, he thought about it for a moment before he agreed. Leaving those iron ores in the Ark Continent would be a waste. Also, it might even benefit the Demons and the Divine Race. So Zhao Hai would rather use them for himself.

In the past, the Dwarves were considering their safety when they were mining the mountain. There were places that they haven’t dug out because it might cause the mountain to collapse. Since they didn’t need to worry about that now, then they would clear the mountain even if it cause it to crumple.

This idea also opened a new thought for Zhao Hai. Although the valuable things inside the Ark Continent were already taken to the Space, there were still things in the continent that were of value, things like wood, bamboo, some machines, metal and the like. Naturally Zhao Hai didn’t want to just leave them be. Since the Demons and the Divine Race didn’t attack and the people had already moved, Zhao Hai released massive amounts of undead to collect things. The ransack was even more ruthless than the shakedowns made by corrupt officials. As long as something can be used, they weren’t let go.

The ones who gave Zhao Hai the least worry were the Beastmen. All of their items were very easy to move. They just placed their belongings on carts before they moved, it was a completely easy process.

On the other hand, the ones Zhao Hai worried the most were the Fishmen. The people of the sea were just too numerous. As the Fishmen entered the Space, Zhao Hai discovered that they were too slow. To solve this, Zhao Hai told the Elf Queen to concentrate the Fishmen and he would just take them to the Space. This process would be quicker than having them go through the spatial rift.

The Queen agreed to Zhao Hai’s proposal. Groups of Fishmen made cube formations and stayed where they were. Then Zhao Hai continuously absorbed them towards the Space.

This takes more time and effort, but Zhao Hai had no other choice. But what moved Zhao Hai was the fact that there were also a lot of useful things in the sea, such as iron ores, other metals, and sea products. It would be a waste to leave them be.

However, Zhao Hai also knew that it wouldn’t be so easy to extract those things out. And compared to the seas, the mainland still had a lot of resources he could use. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to just take the easy route and leave the seas for now.

The Demons and the Divine Race didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have a thing such as the Space. The people who moved discovered that things weren’t different after they moved. They were just met by their empty house, the same style that they were used to. Under the efforts of the officials, their residence didn’t change. For the people, it was just like moving all of their things outside their house before placing it right back in. Moreover, their new homes seemed more comfortable compared to before.

In the past, the homes of these commoners were worn out since they didn’t have the money for repair. Although Zhao Hai made a complete copy of the Ark Continent, it was troublesome for him to also imitate the worn out look of the houses. Because of this, the commoners were given with newer versions of their old house. Naturally, the commoners were happy with this result.

After going through great effort, the relocation of the Ark Continent was short of completion. Except the Fishmen who lived far, all of the people were already settled inside the Space.

Chapter 795: Bird Flying on a Vast Sky

The Demons and the Divine Race finally felt that something was wrong. They haven’t received news from their spies for a couple days now. Although Zhao Hai’s soldiers didn’t retreat, the information that they received made them feel uneasy. They were starting to believe that the information was true. If the people of the Ark Continent really migrated, what would they do?

Although both invaders were restless, the unease felt by the Demons were less compared to the Divine Race. Their main goal was the Ark Continent’s land, so even if the people have moved away, it didn’t matter that much.

On the other hand, the Divine Race wanted the people of the continent. They saw this invasion as an act of revenge. This was because the Ark Continent had bested them once before. For the proud Divines, this was completely intolerable. However, the Divine Race found that they won’t be able to do that now.

The Demons were constantly receiving reinforcements, with the Great Demon King coming in a few days. The Demon Dragon King didn’t want to attack before the Great Demon King arrived.

The situation of the Divine Race was complex. When they sent news to the Barbarian and Winged Pegasus Race, they expected them to send their elites in order to deal with Zhao Hai.

However, they didn’t think that even if the two races said that they would send people in, their preparation was too slow. Many days have passed yet their army were yet to arrive. It was very obvious that they were delaying time. This made Thunder Yun confused, he couldn’t understand why the two races would do this. But in fact, Thunder Yun had forgotten. The two races did indeed feel they needed to take revenge against Zhao Hai, however, their hatred for the Divine Race was deeper. Strictly speaking, they couldn’t blame Zhao Hai for killing their people. If the Divine Race didn’t invade the Ark Continent, then those Barbarian and Winged Pegasus people wouldn’t have died. Their deaths were actually because of the Divine Race.

Thunder Yun hadn’t thought about this point. He has been thinking as someone far above the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus people. In his mind, these two races should always obey the Divine Race. The deaths of the two units were well deserved. They were slaves of the Divine Race, they didn’t have the right to resent the Divine Race.

It was because of this mindset that Thunder Yun miscalculated the reaction of the two races, costing him a lot of time in the end. Finally, Thunder Yun felt that something was wrong. After a strict order towards the two races, the process of reinforcement went forward a bit faster. While this was happening, huge changed already happened in the Ark Continent. Aside from the magic beasts, one could hardly see anything alive. The ones being busy at this time were the undead.

Zhao Hai sat in the Space and took a deep breath, he can finally sigh with relief. The entire Ark Continent had migrated to the Space, everyone was now safe. A large worry in his heart has been removed. The only thing left to worry about was upgrading the Space as well as repelling the Demons and the Divine Race.

The people of the Ark Continent were very happy to live in the Space. The Space’s air was much better compared to the Ark Continent. The growth of crops was also faster compared to the mainland. When the Empires moved to the Space, their reserves were transported by Zhao Hai as well. Because of this, the lives of the civilians were much better than before.

In the past, the commoners were also worried about being unable to eat their meals. But now they don’t need to worry about it. There was a lot of land in the Space, and the crop yield was very high. Additionally, Zhao Hai was providing food and clothing subsidies to the people. One could say that the commoners were already set when it came to necessities and shelter.

Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the villa, looking at the troops in the Buddha Empire. However, these troops weren’t the ones who harassed the Demons and the Divine Race. After transporting their families to the Space, Zhao Hai had the original army take a rest in order to recuperate.

Zhao Hai wasn’t thinking of letting the Demons and the Divine Race off. These two groups didn’t come with good intentions. This was especially true for the Divine Race, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to forgive them. He was unlike the people who migrated to the Space, they were already living great lives, thinking that there was no need to deal with the Demons and the Divine Race.

After the Ark Continent’s people were moved to the Space, Zhao Hai had finally breathed a sigh of relief. When he deals with the Demons and the Divine Race in the future, he would be less reserved compared to before. At this point, Zhao Hai was thinking about how to deal with the two invaders.

Zhao Hai also discovered that there was no need for him to use the continent’s military. After all, the people had just moved to the Space for two days. If Zhao Hai decided to mobilize them once more, then there would be little point to sending them to migrate.

The military strength that Zhao Hai depended on would originate in a certain place, the Northern Icefield!

The Northern Icefield has been fully occupied by the undead. The undead propagating there right now were just low level undead or low level dark creatures. These things held no threat against Zhao Hai. The reason the Beastmen were afraid of the Underworld was because of the Dark Mist. Not only was the mist poisonous, it also hindered people from seeing through it. Because of this, the Beastmen weren’t able to see that the undead they were going against were just low level ones.

And for Zhao Hai, these undead were very good manpower sources. These things would immediately be subdued by the Space, transforming them into Zhao Hai’s own undead army. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t plan on sending more troops out into the battlefield.

The entire Ark Continent had become Zhao Hai’s large playground. He was now able to fight in however way he wanted. With his current strength, he can now fight with the Demons and the Divine Race. It was time to find out whether Zhao Hai’s tactics were stronger compared to the Demon and the Divine Race armies.

Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race’s camp and sneered. Now he was thinking about how to start dealing with the Demons and the Divine Race. At this moment, a voice was heard, “Brother Hai, can I ask you one thing?”

Zhao Hai turned his head to see Berry. Zhao Hai looked at Berry and asked, “Berry? What’s wrong? As long as I can do it, then I’ll help you. After all, I’m your husband, tell my what you want.”

Berry looked excited at Zhao Hai’s response before she sighed and said, “Brother Hai, this might sound awkward. But, I, I want to ask you to allow my people to enter the Space.” Zhao Hai stered, he didn’t think that Berry would say this. He turned to Berry and said, “Why did you suddenly think of this?” Berry looked at the blue skies outside and said, ‘Brother Hai, we cannot see this kind of sky in the Demon Realm. For the Demons, skies like these can only be found in heaven. My Succubus Race has a high status in the Demon Realm, but those strong Demons like to treat us as playthings. If the Succubus race wanted to survive, then they would need to marry those with great power. In exchange, we would keep our living space. We Succubi didn’t want to live like this, but there was no other way. Brother Hai, your Space is huge. If there is a chance, I’d want to have a place for my family to live in.”

Zhao Hai looked at Berry’s face and smiled, “There’s no need to think about it. That’s not a problem. As long as an opportunity comes, then I can make the Succubus of the Demon Realm enter the Space. But we need to consider where they’ll live in, we can’t have them be in the villa at all times.”

When Berry heard Zhao Hai, she smiled before throwing a kiss towards Zhao Hai’s face. Zhao Hai turned his head to meet Berry’s lips, then the two went on to passionately kiss on the spot.

At this time, Megan’s voice can be heard, “Everyone, come quick. There’s two affectionate people here.” Then came the giggles of the women.

When Berry heard Megan, her body immediately jumped up as she looked at Megan and the others with a reddened face. Megan and the others went to the Space’s Ark Continent to see how the people were doing, therefore, Berry had the confidence to get bold. But now she was seen by the other women, naturally she would be embarrassed.

When Zhao Hai saw that the women were back, he smiled and said, “You’re back. How are the people? Are there no problems?”

Megan pouted and said, “Brother Hai, don’t change the topic. You haven’t kissed me like that before.”

Megan’s response made the women’s laughter even louder. Although Megan was red-faced, she was still giggling. She didn’t care. After all, only they were left in the villa. Shue and Shun, along with Blockhead and Rockhead were out and exploring the new Ark Space.

This Ark Space was where the people of the Ark Continent were. Zhao Hai had officially named it Ark Space. Besides that there was also the Fishman Space, naturally, it was the place where the Fishmen were.

As soon as these two places were arranged, Zhao Hai felt great relief. He finally felt like a bird flying in a vast sky.

The Ark Continent’s people had become shackles that prevented him from doing a lot of things. There were the Demons and the Divine Race, and more importantly, the cultivation realm. Now that the Ark Continent was safe, Zhao Hai can finally focus his full effort in dealing with his problems.

Chapter 796: Zhao Hai’s Depression

Megan felt that Zhao Hai’s mood has become better, that is why she made this joke. Zhao Hai looked at Megan and couldn’t help but laugh, “Alright, I’ll give you one just like that. My little Megan, come here!” Then he opened both of his arms towards Megan.

Megan made an ugly face as she said, “I won’t hug you.” Then she ran of while giggling like a little girl.

Seeing Megan running off, Zhao Hai felt specially relaxed. The one feeling happy wasn’t just him, Megan and the others felt it as well.

When Zhao Hai thought about it, he finally understood what was going on. Laura and the others were native to the Ark Continent. Besides their family members, they also had friends and relatives who lived there. Although Zhao Hai had resisted the invasion made by the Demons and the Divine Race, the women still couldn’t help but worry for the future. If Zhao Hai couldn’t resist one day, then their families and friends wouldn’t have good lives.

Megan and the others had always been right beside Zhao Hai during the war. Because of this, they knew firsthand how powerful the Demons and the Divine Race were. Naturally, this fact made them even more worried.

They were worried for their family and friends’ safety, so how could they be at ease. Since Zhao Hai was busy thinking about how to deal with the invaders, he had failed to notice their mood.

But now that the people of the Ark Continent were in the Space, it wasn’t only Zhao Hai who felt great relief. Megan and the others felt happy as well, their worries had vanished into thin air.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai’s heart couldn’t help but feel warm. Megan and the others had it hard, but they still didn’t tell Zhao Hai to send their family and friends to the Space. It can be seen that they still held Zhao Hai first in their hearts, this touched Zhao Hai’s heart.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also felt guilty. He hadn’t thought into how Laura and the others felt. If he wasn’t firm in his resolve to transfer the Ark Continent’s people to the Space, then he wouldn’t have seen their happy expressions right now.

Zhao Hai got up from his chair and hugged his wives as he whispered “Sorry” in a soft voice.

Laura and the others were intelligent, so they immediately understood what Zhao hai meant. They couldn’t blame Zhao Hai and just didn’t say anything. Instead, they gently held Zhao Hai and hugged him tightly as well.

After some time, Zhao Hai said, “I just discussed with Berry, if an opportunity comes, we’ll have her people move to the Space.” Laura and the others nodded, Laura replied, “Right, the Demon Realm’s environment is just too terrible. The Space is much better in comparison.. On the other hand, Brother Hai, those commoners won’t have food problems anymore. After a long time, those people might go lazy. Should we give them something to do?”

Zhao Hai stared, then he said, “Right, that wouldn’t be great. Do you have any ideas? Tell me?”

Laura smiled and said, “What are the reasons why we received the people of the Ark Continent into the Space? One of them is to gather faith power while another is to increase our strength. The Space’s environment is much better compared to outside. There are no natural disasters here and there was no need to worry about food. If this continued, then the people would get lazy, so we need to make them do something. The main things we need to take care of is faith and their strength.” When Zhao Hai heard this, he replied, “You mean, we’ll have them worship me as a god while training them in magic and battle qi?”

Laura nodded and said, “At this time,  we can’t have them just worship you. That is just impossible, it might even cause dislike. Therefore, I have thought of a good way to do so. In the Ark Space, we need to have a projection in each city, showing the fight against the Demons and the Divine Race. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “That wouldn’t be hard. When fight comes, we can have projections in each city. But will this work?” Laura was full of confidence, “It’ll work, definitely. Brother Hai, every time you fight with your undead, people will surely cheer.”

Megan and the others smiled when they heard Laura. In fact, they had already discussed this matter before. Having the people of the Ark Continent worship Zhao Hai as a god wouldn’t be an easy matter. After all, Zhao Hai was just like them, a person of the Ark Continent. Would you suddenly worship a friend at your side as a god? That would be impossible. Because of this, Laura and the others decided that forcing Zhao Hai as a god would be impossible.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, let’s do it according to you plan. However,  we need to wait for some time before we fight the Demons and the Divine Race. There are still good things left in the Ark Continent. I was thinking that as long as they don’t attack us, then we wouldn’t make the first move. In the meantime, we’ll slowly take more good things into the Space. What do you think?”

Laura smiled and said, “Brother Hai is really mad with money. But if those things remain in the Ark Continent, then they might be used by the Demons and the Divine Race. in any case, the Ark Continent’ people needed to adapt for some time. Also, I’m afraid that the Demons and the Divine Race would wait too long.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Don’t worry, the Demons and the Divine Race should be aware of the change in the Ark Continent. After all, we caught a lot of spies last time.”

When Zhao Hai moved the people of the Ark Continent to the Space, the spies of the Demons and the Divine Race began to come out. Naturally, those people wouldn’t go and see Zhao Hai face to face. Instead, they made backhanded remarks, saying malicious words towards Zhao Hai. Their purpose was to stop the people from listening to him.

However, they underestimated Zhao Hai’s control over the Space. Along with Cai’er, it was easy to investigate who these people were.

At first, the people of the Ark Continent didn’t understand why Zhao Hai was arresting these people. Zhao Hai didn’t do the job this time, he hired Dark Mages from the Space to kill these people and turn them into advanced undead before asking them what they were doing. Before long, the people understood who those arrested people were.

And from the mouths of those people, it seems like the Demons and the Divine Race were already aware of the migration. However, this didn’t affect Zhao Hai. In any case, the relocation has been completed. The next step to consider was how to deal with the Demons and the Divine Race.

Laura smiled and said, “Alright, the Demons and the Divine Race should be anxious right about now. But Brother Hai, how are you planning to deal with them? Will it be just like before?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Why not. You should know that we are only facing against the Taurus Divines, the other nine continents are yet to appear. And now that the Ark Continent has been destroyed by us, how about we go and explore the Divine Realm. And if an opportunity comes, we can also go to the Demon Realm. Let’s see if they have things that can upgrade the Space.”

Laura nodded, “Right, if we can get more things that can upgrade the Space, then that would be great. The most important thing for us right now is to upgrade the Space. Then if we meet the Immortal Cultivator in the future,  we would have more ways to defend ourselves.”

Zhao Hai nodded before he sighed inwardly. To be honest, Zhao Hai was a bit depressed right now. It was because of the Space’s Ranch. When he played the game before, he can remember that the Ranch was able to summon divine beasts at a later time. For example, he can summon the Nine Dragons. The Space had a lot of those kinds of Divine Beasts, and their strengths were indeed very strong. What depressed Zhao Hai was the fact that these Divine Beasts should already be available once the Space reaches level 70. However, they were yet to appear. Currently, the strongest creatures in the Space were those God-rank magic beasts. Zhao Hai didn’t understand why this was at first.

However, after the Space’s backgrounds were introduced, Zhao Hai was given a prompt. Since the Ark Continent was a magic plane, then the only beasts that can be brought to it were magic beasts and normal animals. On the other hand, Divine Beasts such as the nine dragons were part of the cultivator background. This explained why they were yet to be purchased in the Ranch.

In other words, if Zhao Hai wanted to raise these Divine Beasts, then he would need to be in the cultivator realms. At this time, the only thing he can raise were magic beasts.

This made Zhao Hai depressed. If he was able to get just a couple of these Divine Beasts, then there would be no problem in dealing with the Demons and the Divine Race.

Lizzy turned to Zhao Hai and said, “We can also use this period of time to slowly wean the people to treat Brother Hai as a God. But unfortunately, our understanding of faith power was just too limited.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Let’s not dwell on that matter for long. Let’s take care of the Demons and the Divine Race first. Lizzy, Megan, do you have any plans?”

Chapter 797: Death Qi Army

Lizzy and Megan had great insight when it came to the battlefield that Zhao Hai didn’t have. Therefore, he hoped to ask Lizzy and Megan about this matter.

Lizzy knit her brows and said, “Big Brother Hai, I think we need to have different attitudes in dealing with the Demons and the Divine Race. We need to fight one while we keep the other.”

Zhao Hai frowned and said, “What do you mean?”

Lizzy replied, “The reason why the Demons and the Divine Race invaded the Ark Continent is different. The Divine Race wanted to enslave the people of the Continent. Brother Hai should already know that the Divine Race wanted more faith power for that immortal cultivator. And from what it seems, their hatred for the Ark Continent is deep. I’m afraid they won’t let the Ark Continent’s people go easily. On the other hand, the Demons only wanted the Ark Continent’s land. They wanted a better place, so they needed to deal with the Ark Continent’s resident. However, if we provide them with a better place, then wouldn’t they stop their invasion?”

When he heard Lizzy, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. What Lizzy meant was the Demons migrating to the Space. Was this possible?

Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy’s face and said, “How do we go about it?”

Lizzy smiled and said, “We need to look for an opportunity. Winning the Demons immediately is not good. I think we must wait for some time and then hit the Demons with a painful attack before winning them over. As for the Divine Race, they are already devout followers of the immortal cultivator. It would be impossible to shift them to our side.”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and said, “It doesn’t matter if we can or cannot win them over. The ghosts of the Ocean Waves Dynasty’s people wouldn’t allow it. In any case, we are need to go and prepare for a fight. There is still the Underworld. The circumstances related to that place is vastly different compared to the Demons and the Divine Race. What do we do about them?”

Lizzy smiled and said, “We deal with them as well. Big Brother Hai, have you forgotten? When it comes to manpower, the Underworld’s creatures are our number one source. Later on, we can get reinforcements from them.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he replied, “Alright, we’ll take care of that. Later on, the Underworld would supply us with a lot of troops.”

Ever since he received the Ark Continent’s people to the Space, Zhao Hai can be said to be extremely confident. Without anything holding his ankles down, he can now do whatever he wanted.

‘Dragon returning to the sea, tiger returning to the mountain’, this was Zhao Hai’s mood right now. He wasn’t afraid that he couldn’t deal with the Demons and the Divine Race. If that happens, then he could just hide inside the Space and slowly develop his strength. That way, even if he couldn’t beat them, he could still cause them massive headaches. This was where Zhao Hai was good at.

While Zhao Hai was being relaxed, the Demons and the Divine Race were actually anxious. This was because their reinforcements were coming.

Needless to say, the Demon reinforcements were personally led by the Great Demon King; an army of 50 million with 1 million God ranks. Although this might look inferior compared to the Divine Race, their actual fighting strength couldn’t be underestimated.

The Divine Race’s reinforcements were also quite special since it came from three parties. There were the elites coming from both the Barbarians as well as the Winged Pegasus Race, and lastly, the reinforcements coming from the Taurus Divines themselves. Altogether, their number reached an astonishing 40 million troops.

Naturally, these people were yet to arrive at the Continent. However, news of their approach came, three days later, they would arrive.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about these, but he didn’t need to. At this point, he was scraping the Ark Continent’s landscape. Everything useful have been collected to the Space. He sent undead to dig wherever possible, every mineral was sent over to the Space.

In addition to the mainland, the endless sea was also providing materials for the Space. For Zhao Hai, these were indispensable, they cannot be left to waste.

This wasn’t to say that Zhao Hai was afraid that he wouldn’t be able to beat the Demons and the Divine Race. On the contrary, Zhao Hai believed that he would drive them out in the future. He just knew that it would take a long time. And when the time comes, he needed to make sure that the Demons and the Divine Race were the weakest they could be. The Demons and the Divine Race weren’t stupid, once they occupy the continent, they would surely scour the place for resources, just like what Zhao Hai was doing.

At that time, the Ark Continent would surely be devastated. Therefore, Zhao Hai might as well do it himself.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that time  what was waiting for him, but that is irrelevant. At this point, he had already taken all the cavalry units out of the Buddha empire. The only ones left in the continent were the busily mining undead.

The Demons and the Divine Race also noted the lack of movements from the Buddha Empire. Before long, they discovered that both Rising Sun City and Upper Bank city’s garrison troops had vanished. However, they still didn’t dare to walk towards the Buddha Empire. Their previous blunder was still clear in their minds.

Three days went by in a blink of an eye. Zhao Hai sat inside the Space as usual, looking at the monitor. Naturally, he was looking at the state of the Demons and the Divine Race. Although Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of the reinforcements, the conversations from both camps predicated the arrival. Because of this, Zhao Hai was closely paying attention to the two camps.

While Zhao Hai was looking at the two camps, he was also looking at the Goblins that were working the fields. It can be seen that the strength of these Goblins were great. Compared to the Humans, they might be as strong as an average woman. But even then, they still kept doing their job without resting.

Zhao Hai knew that this wasn’t because the Goblins didn’t want to stop, they just couldn’t dare to. Before his own eyes, Zhao Hai saw Goblins being killed just because they attempted to rest.

Upon seeing this scene, Zhao Hai held a new understanding about the cruelty of the Divine Race. For a race who worshipped a deity, they were more disgusting to look at compared to the Demons.

Zhao Hai pitied these Goblins. He knew that if these Goblins were allowed to develop, then they would’ve developed a Magic and Mechanical Civilization. It was just a pity that the Divine Race snuffed that potential out.

While Zhao Hai was sighing in regret, Cai’er suddenly said, “Young Master, there is a commotion at the Demon camp. Their reinforcements have arrived.”

Zhao Hai gawked before he changed the monitor’s display to the Demon camp. On their spatial rift were large quantities of Demons. Moreover, their numbers were increasingly piling up.

When he saw the Demon Army, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but frown. He discovered some differences between this army and those who came before them. Although the Demons in the past weren’t weak, and their training was very good, they were lacking something when compared to these reinforcements, Death Qi!

Death Qi, not killing aura. As long as you have killed people, then your body will exude a killing aura. If you kill an ordinary person then you will get a killing aura, killing a large amount of magic beasts would gain you a killing aura as well. However, this Death Qi was an evolved version of killing aura. If one hadn’t killed at least a thousand people, then it would be impossible for someone to gain Death Qi.

This Death Qi was actually a state of disregarding the difference between life and death. People with Death Qi fight as though they were undead. They weren’t in a brainwashed state or in a mind-controlled condition. These people just killed too many people that they disregarded life altogether. They stopped caring about how many they killed and even stopped caring about their own life.

What made Zhao Hai frown was each person in this army had Death Qi. In other words, this army had walked through mountains of corpses and seas of blood. Even if faces with people higher rank than them, there was a high probability of these Demons being able to win.

This army had pitch black full body armor. Their weapons were pitch black spears. They looked like any ordinary army, but Zhao Hai reckoned that if these people face the Divine Race, then the Divine Race would have no choice but to retreat.

Zhao Hai carefully observed the reinforcing army. Batch upon batch continuously appeared out of the Spatial Rift. Millions upon millions of Death Qi army appeared, it was a terrifying sight.

Although Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about the Ark Continent anymore, he still couldn’t help but wipe a bead of cold sweat. He couldn’t imagine how they would defend if the Ark Continent didn’t migrate to the Space.

Not to say the continent’s army, even Zhao Hai’s undead would find it hard to face this kind of enemies.

Zhao Hai also found out that after this army arrived, those Demons doing construction were looking at them with admiring eyes. Although the Death Qi army were standing there like statues, the other Demons couldn’t help but look at them with eyes of worship.

Zhao Hai believed that this army was certainly an extraordinary unit in the Demon Realm.

At this time, a huge magic beast suddenly appeared from the spatial right. This enormous magic beast looked like an elephant. It had large fan-like ears and two long ivory tusks, however, what made this beast different was the horn on top of its head. Moreover, its skin looked just like metal armor. From its appearance alone, one could see how hard its skin was. The elephant’s four long legs were like four sturdy pillars. Its tail was very long and at its tip was a sharp arrow shape, just like a devil’s tail. The arrow was moving as though it had a life of its own.

Chapter 798: Domain Weapon

As this magic beast went out of the spatial rift, it suddenly made a world-shaking roar. Its imposing aura can only be described as terrifying.

At this time, a jet black whip had flung out of the spatial rift. Whap! It hit the back of the magic beast. The once imposing magic beast immediately calmed down after being struck by the whip. It seems like it became a bullied puppy as it flapped its ears and behaved.

Although this magic beast was enormous, it was actually flying in the sky. And from how it looked, it wasn’t a 9th rank beast, but instead it was clearly God-rank.

Along with the magic beast were several of its kind. Strapped on their bodies were iron chains, seemingly dragging something.

These magic beasts weren’t fast, but they eventually made it out of the spatial rift. After the thing they were dragging was seen, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. It looked like a carriage in a shape of a huge demon’s head.

The head shaped carriage looked exactly like a devil’s head. Two curved horns, two blood-red eyes, and long fangs that jutted out of its mouth.

Although it was a carriage, there were no wheels attached to it. It was a head flying in the sky, there was no need for wheels. To be honest, it looked more like a flying house than a carriage.

This floating house was more than ten meters high and looked very spacious. When Zhao Hai looked into the carriage, the devil’s eyes were actually inlaid with two pieces of red gems.

On the mouth of the devil’s head sat a tall man. He wore black armor that blocked his face. He sat there as if he were an iron statue. In his hand was a jet black whip, the same whip used to silence the large magic beast.

The large carriage pulled by five elephant shaped magic beasts slowly went out of the spatial rift as it stopped right in front of the Demonic Abyss.

Strangely, even if the magic beasts have stopped, the carriage still stayed floating there.

At this time, the black dragon carriage stopped by the flying carriage. Next to the black dragon carriage were a large group of God-rank experts.

When the black dragon carriage stopped, the Demon Dragon King stood up from his seat before he gave a loud greeting, “Welcome, my King!” And just as his voice fell, the God-ranks following him gave their greeting as well, “Welcome, my King!”

After that, all the Demons in the Demonic Abyss knelt simultaneously and said, “Welcome, my King!”

After the greetings faded into the air, the devil carriage’s mouth started to open up. Then a Vile Demon walked out of the mouth.

The Demon was not very tall and looked just like any other Demon. He wore a black robe and had some wrinkles on his face, just like an old Vile Demon.

However, the imposing aura that emanated from this person was very astonishing. He just stood there but one could feel as though they were seeing a mountain, something that could stand forever, never to be toppled down.

The presence of the Great Demon King was roaring. When Zhao Hai saw this, he couldn’t help but smile faintly before saying, “He looks very strong. It seems I’ll get to meet him soon.”

Cai’er’s voice came, “Young Master, that is the Demon Realm’s Great Demon King. In his over a thousand years of life, his prestige in the Demon Realm is incomparable to anyone else. Nobody really knows how strong he really is since he hadn’t made a move for several hundred years. The carriage that he rode in is called the Devil’s War Chariot. It’s a floating carriage made entirely out of a special kind of iron. Moreover, several magic formations are installed in the carriage as it was built. Not only could these formations make the passenger feel comfortable, it also allowed the carriage to be used in a fight. This carriage can unify with the Great Demon King’s Domain, becoming a Domain Weapon. It’s power is very overbearing.”

Zhao Hai asked, “Domain Weapon? What’s that?”

Cai’er answered, “From what I’ve heard, Domain Weapons are weapons that a God-rank’s Domain could use. Just like the Young Master, your Domain can transform into whatever you want. And after your Domain can transform into human-shape, it can use a weapon for itself. When other God-ranks become strong, their Domains would embody large versions of themselves. In this case, it would be impossible for these Domains to use conventional weapons. Therefore, these people would make weapons that would specifically be used alongside one’s Domain. And there are materials in the universe that allow such weapons to be made, and these weapons would be called Domain Weapons. These weapons are more formidable compared to ordinary weapons. Moreover, they allow a person’s Domain to exhibit more than their usual power. These weapons are incredibly valuable treasures.”

Zhao Hai nodded, this was the first time that he heard about these Domain Weapons. To be honest, he hadn’t thought about Domains having weapons before.

At this time, the Great Demon King spoke, he looked at the Demon Dragon King and the others before nodding, “Very good, you’ve done a great job. Demon Dragon, come with me. As for the others, go back to what you were doing.” Then he turned around and went back into his Devil’s War Chariot.

The action of this old Demon can only be described as serene, but to all Demons this was how it should be. Especially those who followed the Demon Dragon King, all of them were smiling. Even if the Great Demon King spoke words to them in passing, saying they did a good job, they still couldn’t help but feel their bones become lighter.

These Demons knew that the Great Demon King wouldn’t crack a joke, and will not say any sarcasm. If he said they did well, then the Great Demon King did praise their job, no hidden meanings. Being able to obtain a commendation from the Great Demon King was an enormous morale boost for these Demons.

The Demon Dragon King nodded before he jumped out of his black dragon carriage and into the Great Demon King’s chariot. While he did so, he was met with envious looks from the other Demons. Those who can enter the Great Demon King’s chariot can only be counted on one’s fingers, and the Demon Dragon King was one of those people.

This wasn’t the first time that the Demon Dragon King entered the chariot, but when he did the first time, he couldn’t help but exclaim in surprise.

One would be met with a hundred square meter lobby upon entering. Spread across the lobby was a thick carpet, in the middle of it was a table and a smaller table to hold pots and cups. On the table were small plates with normal plates as well.

The Great Demon King sat on the other side of the table, pouring liquor on the cups. The Demon Dragon King slowly sat on the opposite side before be bowed to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, I have disappointed you.”

The Great Demon King placed his liquor pot down, he waved his hand and said, “You haven’t disappointed me at all. Tell me how the fights went. You only failed because your enemy is too strong. I couldn’t blame you for that. Here, join me for a cup.”

The Demon Dragon King took the cup respectfully as he matched the Great Demon King in drinking the liquor. After placing their cups down, he took the liquor pot and poured the Great Demon King a cup.

The Great Demon King didn’t take the cup as he looked at the Demon Dragon King and said, “So what’s the problem with Zhao Hai? Is he really that strong?”

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “Strong, very strong. Aside from you, Your Majesty, I haven’t seen someone as strong as he is. I am not his match.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “It seems like this person is too problematic. Right, what’s the deal with his undead army? Tell me.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, “I don’t know why, but Zhao Hai had a lot of strong undead. His ordinary undead had 9th rank strength. And if a God-rank expert dies and was turned into undead, they would retain their God-rank strength. Moreover, Zhao Hai had several tens of millions of strong undead.”

The Great Demon King knit his brows and said, “This Zhao Hai is formidable, and you said that he defeated the Divine Race?”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, “Ever since the Divine Race has descended, we have sent for people to monitor their advance. Once they set out, we would dispatch our troops. In the past, when we heard that the Divine Race had set out, we sent our troops onward as well. But I didn’t expect that the Ark Continent would be this formidable in harassment methods. Their mounts were very fast, not even God-ranks can overtake them. Because of this, our every step was made with excruciating pace.” After speaking here, the Demon Dragon King stopped and looked at the Great Demon King.

The Great Demon King waved his hand as he took up his cup and drank. Then the Demon Dragon King continued, “Although we were dragged behind, I thought that it would be difficult for ZHao Hai to defeat the Divine Race. So I thought that if we retreat this time under their constant attacks, then we would give the bulk of the benefits to the Divine Race. Because of this, I decided to move forward while capturing cities along the way. However, I didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would actually repel the Divine Race’s advance. After that, he led his undead army to make a hard assault on our numbers. This caused us to lose a lot of men. Along with his undead, Zhao Hai also had devil mosquitoes to harass us. The mosquitoes are strong, and their numbers are enormous as well. They’re very difficult to deal with.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “This Zhao Hai is the Ark Continent’s most formidable person since its existence. For him to have the strength to block both the Demons and the Divine Race. Good, good, this person is already a hero!”

The Demon Dragon King looked at the Great Demon King before he said, “Your Majesty, I have received additional information in the past few days. Please take a look.” Then he took out a beast skin scroll and placed it on the table.

Chapter 799: Cai’er Is Jealous?

The Great Demon King took the scroll on the table and carefully read it. By the time he placed the scroll back on the table, he was already frowning, he looked at the Demon Dragon King and said, “Has this been confirmed?”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, “It’s confirmed. When this information was sent, it was done in code. So even if it was intercepted, it would be impossible for outsiders to understand it. There’s no way for it to be tampered.”

The Great Demon King knit his brows and said, “Do you have any other information?”

The Demon Dragon King shook his head and said, “After this one, no additional information was sent. I couldn’t make up my mind about this information. First, because it was too outrageous. Second, because it might be a misinformation sent by the enemy. They might already know the identity of our people, so they sent misleading information to be sent to us. And lastly, it might be true. It wouldn’t be good for us if this was true. And two days ago, I got information from our scouts that the garrison troops of the Ark Continent have all vanished. I’m still confused about what is happening.”

The Great Demon King knit his brows, then he nodded and said, “Right, we shouldn’t advance recklessly. It’s possible that its another trap. The enemy is very sly, we need to be careful.”

The Demon Dragon King replied, “I think the Divine Race wouldn’t just step back with their previous failure. They will certainly make a stronger attack. At the same time, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to let the Divine Race off. When the Divine Race descended they used an entire Empire’s worth of people to do their blood sacrifice. I heard that when Zhao Hai knew about this, he coughed up some blood while swearing to kill all invading Divines. His hatred for the Divine Race should be greater compared to us.”

The Great Demon King frowned and said, “Is that the case? The people don’t treat the Demons as the evil ones? They think that the Divine Race are more vile?”

The Demon Dragon King smiled bitterly and said, “Others might not know this, but Zhao Hai doesn’t think like ordinary people. It’s possible that he didn’t have any hatred for the Demons. On the other hand, his hatred for the Divine Race is true. I can see Divine Race soldiers among Zhao Hai’s undead. It’s clear that he turned them into undead immediately after killing them.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “I believe Zhao Hai’s hatred for us wouldn’t be less. After all, we are invading the Ark Continent. Anyone who invades the continent should be enemies to Zhao Hai. Going back to the information you’ve received, I think there are some inaccuracies about it. Ever since the Demons and Divine Race had arrived in the continent, it can be said that Zhao Hai always had the upper hand. In this case, there is no reason for him to suddenly move the people of the Ark Continent. From what I think, there should be another situation happening in the continent, something we have yet to know. Did you send people to check it?”

The Demon Dragon King’s expression turned ugly before he gave a nod, “I did, but after sending all of them, nobody came back. I reckon they have been killed of by Zhao Hai. This caused me to doubt making an attack while also being more and more suspicious about the authenticity of the report. I think it’s Zhao Hai’s trap.”

The Great Demon King nodded, “Right, we don’t want to make a blunder against Zhao Hai. Good, you arrange for the reinforcing army to take a rest, let them be used to the Ark Continent’s environment. I think the Divine Race’s reinforcements wouldn’t take too long before they arrive. As soon as the Divine Race makes their move, we’ll dispatch our troops as well. I really want to meet this Zhao Hai.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded before he bowed and asked to be excused. After seeing the Demon Dragon King walk out, the Great Demon King took his wine cup and drank some liquor. Then he muttered, “Just wait, sooner or later, the Demons will be out of your control.” Then the Great Demon King turned his gaze towards the Demon God’s portrait. The Demon God had three heads, six arms, and an ugly facial expression. Besides weapons, the Demon God also held several heads in his hands. This caused the portrait to emanate a vile aura. If one were weak of mind, they might even see blood dripping from the picture.”

Why would the Great Demon King say this to the portrait? What was wrong? Does he want to change their faith?

Naturally, ZhaoHai didn’t know these. The Devil’s War chariot was a Domain Weapon. It’s quite powerful that the Space’s monitor wasn’t able to see inside it.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t care about it, he only cared about looking at the reinforcing Demon Army. Besides the ten million or so Death Qi warriors, there were also ordinary Demon soldiers.

From Zhao Hai’s count, there were about 50 million people that came out of the spatial rift. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but mutter,”They actually went full force. I didn’t think they would send this much people.”

After the reinforcement army came, the Demonic Abyss up to Demon City had become huge military compound. On the other hand, the Great Demon King’s chariot stayed on the skies above the Demonic Abyss.

At this time, Laura and the others were merrily taking a walk. They didn’t have anything to do in these past few days, so they strolled around the Ark Space looking for something to do. Although everything in the Ark Space was the same as the Ark Continent, there were still things needed to be taken care of. Because of this, Zhao Hai sent them over to help.

Although the Buda Clan was also inside the Space, they were in a separate island a distance away from the Ark Continent. And even if it was quite close, one couldn’t easily reach the island. This was exactly what Zhao Hai wanted. In doing so, the Buda Clan wasn’t too far nor too close to the continent. This was to maintain a sense of mystery to the clan.

Naturally, Laura and the others wouldn’t have him help the people of the continent. That would be the job for the Buda Clan’s people. Because of this, Zhao Hai hadn’t appeared in the Ark Space since.

This was actually Laura’s idea. It wouldn’t be easy to deify Zhao Hai in the minds of the Ark Continent’s people. After all, nobody would see someone they can casually talk to as a god,

When Laura and the others walked into the living room and saw the Devil’s War Chariot on the monitor, they couldn’t help but gasp in surprise.

After seeing their reaction, Zhao Hai laughed before he enlarged the devil’s face. This frightened the women even more.

With Zhao Hai’s laughter, the women understood that Zhao Hai was intentionally scaring them. They immediately went to Zhao Hai and pinched his sides. Naturally, they knew that this wouldn’t do anything to Zhao Hai.

But Zhao Hai still yelled in pain. He didn’t brace himself, moreover, he can still feel pain.

After pinching Zhao Hai many more times, Laura and the other gave a snort before stopping and sitting with Zhao Hai. Laura even told Cai’er, “Cai’er, play that scene back!”

Upon hearing Laura, Zhao Hai almost spit out blood. He couldn’t handle the pressure in the room so he stood up and pulled Berry over while saying, “Berry, let’s go, join me for a bath. In any case, nothing great would happen in the Demon Army soon.” Then he took Berry downstairs to the hot spring.

Berry’s face was red but she still continued to follow Zhao Hai. Megan turned to Berry and yelled, “Sister Berry, if you can’t take it anymore don’t hesitate to ask for help!”

After Megan said that, Laura and the others laughed. This made Berry’s face even redder. Berry’s joking skill was weak, so she couldn’t think of anything wise to retort. She just turned to Megan and said, “Hmph, I don’t need help. If you come, then I’ll turn you away!” This made the women laugh even more.

That night, Zhao Hai was very tired. The reason for this was because he was unable to stop the women from invading his room.

The next morning, while Zhao Hai was still asleep, Cai’er entered his room. Zhao Hai was lying naked in his bed, Laura and the others were also right by Zhao Hai’s side. All of them were sleeping quite smoothly.

When Cai’er saw this, her face couldn’t help but turn red. Then she snorted before making a water ball and splashing Zhao Hai’s face with it. Her control was very good, not a single drop of water splashed on the women’s bodies.

Zhao Hai immediately woke up, he sat up and looked at Cai’er, “Cai’er, what did you just do?”

Cai’er snorted and said, “Young Master, get up. The Divine Race’s reinforcements have arrived.” When Zhao Hai heard Cai’er, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment before he carefully got up from his bed. He took extra care to not disturb the women.

Cai’er looked at Zhao Hai’s movements before he snorted and flashed out of the room. Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er’s direction before he muttered, “What happened to Cai’er? Strange.”

However, he still went to the bathroom and cleaned himself up. Then he wore some clothes before proceeding towards the living room. After Zhao Hai left, Laura smiled along with the other women. Laura opened her eyes, looked at the others and said, “Brother Hai is really too daft when it came to reading sentiment. He couldn’t even recognize Cai’er’s jealous look.”

Lizzy opened her eyes and replied, “Yeah, but Big Brother Hai is like that. He would never know about those things. I wonder what Brother Hai’s face would be once he discovers that Cai’er likes him.”

After imagining Zhao Hai’s shocked expression, the women couldn’t help but look at each other. When they noticed that all of them were naked, their faces immediately turned red. Meanwhile, Megan hugged Lizzy from behind as she traced Lizzy’s chest and said, “Lizzy, these are really big. No wonder Brother Hai likes to touch them so much.”

Lizzy had no intention of just receiving Megan’s attack, naturally she would counter attack. Before long, the women were noisily laughing inside the room.

Chapter 800: Transfer

Zhao Hai sat in the living room and looked at the Divine Race Army in the monitor. The Divine Race reinforcements this time were divided into three teams, the heavy Barbarian cavalry, the light winged pegasus cavalry, and the Divine Race infantry.

The Winged Pegasus light cavalry were in front, being the first to enter the Radiant Empire. The Divine Race infantry went next and after that were the Barbarian heavy cavalry. Their motion was fast, it didn’t take too long for all of them to arrive at the Radiant Empire. However, the one who attracted Zhao Hai’s attention the most was the carriage right in the middle of the Divine Race infantry.

Similar to how the Great Demon King arrived, this carriage was pulled by one high level magic beast. But instead of an elephant shaped beast, the magic beast used to pull this carriage was a type of lion. The lion was snow white, with two steady wings on each of its side. With how white the magic beast was, one could feel an extraordinarily holy aura coming out of it.

The carriage itself was as interesting as the lion type magic beast. The carriage looked like a large great sword. But instead of metal, the great sword was made out of white wood, probably saint light wood. However, one could see that it was leagues better than the conventional saint light wood.

On the sides of this carriage was a team of knights. The knights resemble the Radiant Church’s Knight Corps. They all wore white armor with white cloaks behind it, had spears on their hands and shields on the other, and on their waists were swords.

These knights amounted to about ten thousand. Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that these Knights were all God-ranks.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. The Taurus Divines had sent a strong army this time, just like the Demons. But what made Zhao Hai interested in the matter wasn’t the army. Zhao Hai was looking at the carriage, he reckoned that it was a Domain Weapon as well.

Zhao Hai had discovered a different feature on the Space’s monitor. Usually, the monitor would display red on Zhao Hai’s allies while green on his enemies. If the enemy party used a magic formation to block the surveillance, then the area would be depicted by a white spot. However, Zhao Hai saw something that he hadn’t seen before. When the Great Demon King arrived, his carriage was displayed as a light blue dot. This light blue dot was shown on the Divine Race’s carriage as well.

Because of this, Zhao Hai boldly assumed that the Space would detect Domain Weapons as light blue spots. If this is correct, then that Divine Race carriage should be a Domain Weapon as well.[1]

However, Zhao Hai was also curious about who was riding the carriage. He wanted to know if the person was like the Demon Realm Ruler, the Great Demon King. Was it the Taurus Continent Monarch?

While Zhao Hai was thinking about this, Thunder Yun and his people came forward to express their greetings. Thunder Yun, along with the other Generals went to the carriage and simultaneously said, “Welcome, Sir Marshal”

Just as Thunder Yun’s voice fell, a door opened on the tail end of the great sword shaped carriage. The door was fitted well with the entire sword, Zhao Hai wasn’t able to notice it at first.

The hollow area inside the carriage were inlaid with transparent crystals, one can see that they were used for lighting purposes. The entire sword carriage was about 20 meters long, perfectly suited to be used by a human shaped Domain.

At this time, a few people came out of the sword carriage door. When he saw these people, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get stunned. This was because it wasn’t the king of the Taurus continent, but several maids instead. The maids were very beautiful, even under a thin veil over their faces. All of them were 9th rank and looked like fairies as they came out.

Zhao Hai originally didn’t take it seriously when he saw that the person was escorted by the maids. So when he saw Thunder Yun’s ugly expression, Zhao Hai was confused.

However, Zhao Hai was quick to understand Thunder Yun’s expresion. This was because after eight maids came out of the sword carriage, a young man walked out.

The young man wore a white robe, his face was pale but beautiful. He had a smile on his face but it wasn’t a smile of happiness, instead, it was a smile of someone looking down on people, showing his arrogance. He also held two women on his sides.

When he saw that a young man was sent as reinforcement, Zhao Hai was shocked. He believed that it would be impossible for this young man to be the King of the Taurus Continent. His temperament alone wasn’t something found on strong Divine Race characters. It was impossible for the Divine Race to follow this young man.

Moreover, Thunder Yun greeted the Marshal. However, his age was just too low for a position as head of a military. It might even be possible that he hadn’t been on a battlefield before.

No wonder Thunder Yun’s expression was ugly to behold. The young man wasn’t the man he thought would come.

Thunder Yun looked at the young man and respectfully said, “Your Highness the Third Prince, why have you come to the Ark Continent and taken the carriage of the Marshall?”

The Third Prince chuckled and said, “It’s nothing, I told my uncle that I want to see this world. He had me go instead and take his carriage.”

Thunder Yun’s expression turned uglier, he looked at the Third Prince and said, “Your Highness, have his Majesty the King read the letter? The situation here is dire, things can get dangerous in an instant. If you have nothing to do here, then I ask Your Highness  Third Prince to please return.”

When he heard Thunder Yun, the Third Prince’s complexion sank. He snorted before he gave a retort, “Thunder Yun, who do you think you are? What qualifications do you have to order me? You think I can’t have my father revoke your status as Chief Commander?”

Thunder Yun fearlessly stared right back at the Third Prince and said, “If your highness can do that, then I would gladly step down.”

The Third Prince’s complexion turned colder when he heard Thunder Yun. Then he snorted and took out a Command Token and a scroll. Then he looked at Thunder Yun and said, “No wonder Father said that you get more useless as you got older. Even a small plane such as the Ark Continent needed a large number of troops. Thunder Yun, listen to my command. You shall now be transferred away from your position as Chief of Command. However, you will stay in the frontlines as I take command of the troops.”

The Third Prince’s command caused an uproar to the military officers behind Thunder Yun. They didn’t expect this to happen. The Third Prince would replace Thunder Yun as commander? One must know that the Third Prince had never gone to the battlefield before. Although he had studied the ways of battle, how could he compare to a seasoned General like Thunder Yun? Have the King and Marshal really sent this order?

Thunder Yun’s stunned face looked at the Third Prince. Then his startled expression turned into anger as he said, “That is impossible. I need to see His Highness’ decree!” The Third Prince didn’t say anything as he just coldly snorted and threw the scroll over to Thunder Yun. Thunder Yun took the scroll and impatiently opened it. Upon seeing its contents, he couldn’t help but be shocked, he muttered, “Impossible. This is impossible. This can’t happen.”

While Thunder Yun was muttering to himself, a hand suddenly came and snatched the scroll away from his hands. Naturally, this hand belonged to the Third Prince. The Third Prince looked at Thunder Yun and said, “Now that you’ve finished reading, do you have anything else to say? Everyone listen! From now on, I will officially be the Chief Commander of this army. If violations occur, then they would be judged by martial law!”

After having said that, the Third Prince turned around and returned to his sword carriage. Then the carriage moved slowly forward without caring about Thunder Yun and the other Generals. All of them were staring blankly, they didn’t know what happened, everything went by too quick. What happened was way out of their expectations that they weren’t even able to respond.

It wasn’t only Thunder Yun and the others, Zhao Hai was also dumbfounded about what just happened. He couldn’t comprehend what just occurred. A transfer of command? Does the Divine Race really want to do this?”

However, Zhao Hai changed his mind. This development was a godsend to him. The Divine Race just traded a veteran General with an inexperienced young man. In other words, Thunder Yun’s removal alone has caused great damage to the Divine Race army.

Dealing with an inexperienced fellow was much easier compared to an old fox like Thunder Yun. For Zhao Hai, this was an extremely good thing.

After thinking about this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, “Hahaha, good, good job Divine Race. You actually helped me a lot. I couldn’t thank you enough.”

While he was laughing, Laura and the others came into the room. It seems like they had just come back from taking a bath judging by their wet hair. When they saw Zhao Hai laughing, Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai? What are you so happy?”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and the others in the eyes before he smiled, “Something good arrived. The Divine Race just removed Thunder Yun from being the commander of their army. What they replaced him with was an inexperienced Third Prince of the Taurus Continent. This fellow even looks like he hadn’t been on a battlefield before.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Laura and the others couldn’t help but stare. Then they looked at each other before staring blankly at the monitor. After some time, Lizzy said, “The Divine Race are courting death. Big Brother Hai, it seems like we need to change our tactics to capitalize on this move.”

* * *

Ignoring the fact that it is shaped like a weapon.. Geez Zhao Hai

Chapter 801: Fei’er’s Strange Action

Thunder Yun’s face was ugly as he sat in the hall. Having the same expression as him were the other generals of the army. The arrival of the Third Prince and the decree brought by him had made these people feel like the skies were falling apart.

They knew about the Third Prince. The Taurus Continents King had six children. The First Prince didn’t have any interest in martial cultivation. Because of this, he was just stuck at being an ordinary Demigod. This was rare in the Divine Race, especially among the royals.

But Thunder Yun and the others understood why this was the case. The First Prince was a bastard son, thus he had no inheritance nor background to speak of. However, since he was the first son of the Taurus King, many people still hoped that he would inherit the throne.

However, the Taurus Continent’s Queen was from a very influential clan, and the Second Prince being her son with the Taurus King. Having such a powerful mother meant that the Second Prince’s status was high as well, and succeeding the throne would be a natural path. If the First Prince were to exhibit extraordinary talents, then he would become an eyesore to the mother-son pair. It might even be possible for the First Prince to be killed off. Because of this, the First Prince had no other choice but to stay as a Demigod Expert, relinquishing any rights to the throne.

On the other hand, the talents of the Second Prince would make one speechless. The Second Prince was now a Full God-rank expert. Moreover, he had experience in commanding an army. With the learning he gained from his mother and father, the Second Prince was able to handle the matters of the court. This made him the perfect candidate to become the Next King. Many Great Clans on the Taurus Continent supported the Second Prince’s ascension to the throne.

But as the matter stands, a situation came up. The Taurus King was still at the prime of his life, and he was unwilling to hand the crown over, he wouldn’t die anytime soon. Now that the Second Prince was showing his superiority, the King felt that his position was being threatened. Because of this, the Taurus King had found a way to keep the balance against the Second Prince, and that was to favor and trust the Third Prince.

The Third Prince was also a direct descendant between the Taurus King and Queen, him being the younger brother of the Second Prince. However, the Third Prince was different from the Second Prince. The Second Prince was diligent in his effort since childhood. He had gained military experience while being strong himself, making him favored by the people.

But the Third Prince was different. Ever since he was little, the Third Prince has been smothered by the King with affection. Although he was intelligent and diligent in his studies, the Third Prince was very arrogant. Moreover, he didn’t like to listen to any criticism. Also, he didn’t go out and gain experience. So in matters of military, he was completely out of the loop.

But there was one thing that the Third Prince was the best at among his brothers. He was very good in making his parents happy.

The Third Prince was very adept in satisfying the King and Queen, he grew up perfecting this skill. In front of the King and Queen, he would be that clever and obedient son. However, when the two weren’t looking, he would act arrogant and conceited. His eyes were as high as the skies. Moreover, he was addicted to women. He would frequent himself with the other playboys of the Divine Race. Naturally, there wasn’t anything good to learn from this, so he only had the strength of a normal God-rank.

People with discerning eyes can see that the Third Prince completely falls short compared to the Second Prince. However, the Taurus King was very fond of the Third Prince, giving him favor and his trust. The King wouldn’t even accept any criticism thrown towards the Third Prince, the Queen was the same.

The other three children of the Taurus King were still young, so they were yet to enter the game and compete for the throne. Because of this, the battle had become the Second Prince against the Third. The Second Prince was an excellent leader and everybody was fond of him. His only downside was the jealous King. On the other hand, the Third Prince was popular with the King and the Queen as well as Nobles who wanted to advance their status. Because of this, the momentum of the battle was quite strong.

What made the Taurus Continent’s Great Nobles surprised was that the Taurus Continent’s Marshal, the King’s Younger Brother, was actually quite fond of the Third Prince as well. Meanwhile he was being cold towards the Second Prince. Because of his support, the likelyhood of the Third Prince ascending to the throne has increased by a lot.

But for people on the frontlines like Thunder Yun and the Generals, they knew that the Third Prince was unsuitable. He was clearly inferior compared to the Second Prince.

However, although Thunder Yun liked the Second Prince, he couldn’t actively support him since the Marshal of the army, Thunder Yun’s superior officer, supported the Third Prince.

What Thunder Yun and the others don’t know was the fact that it was the Marshal’s idea to send the Third Prince to the Ark Continent. He wanted the Third Prince to gain military exploits, so that he could prepare for his ascension to the Throne in the future.

Actually, aside from the decree, the Marshal also sent Thunder Yun a private letter via the Third Prince. The Marshal wanted Thunder Yun to make the Third Prince take command of the army as merely a title, the Third Prince wouldn’t encroach upon Thunder Yun’s commands. The Third Prince would just get the credit while Thunder Yun does the actual job.

The Marshal also told the Third Prince about the contents of this letter. After the Third Prince arrives at the camp, he would then listen to the arrangements made by Thunder Yun.

This might work on a normal person but it was useless when it came to the Third Prince. The Third Prince didn’t like the Marshal’s arrangements but he still pretended to be obedient to the Marshal’s command while completely disregarding it in his mind.

With Thunder Yun’s temperament as well as his reaction when he saw the Third Prince, it was even more reason for the Third Prince to withhold the Marshal’s letter from Thunder Yun. Instead, he just used the imperial decree to directly remove Thunder Yun’s authority altogether. The Third Prince had learned the art of war from a young age, so why couldn’t he conquer the Ark Continent? What? Even Thunder Yun didn’t succeed? It’s because he had grown dull from age, he had become less useful the older he got.

The twists and turns of fate were difficult to predict, however, the imperial decree was certainly set in stone. This was also where Thunder Yun was having trouble with.

Cloud Ying looked at the silent Thunder Yun, in the end, he couldn’t endure it and said, “General, why would the Marshal send an order like that? It’s too strange, don’t you think?”

Thunder Yun knit his brows and said, “I also think that it’s strange. Normally, when the Marshal sends a decree, he would also hand me a private letter. However, there was no letter this time. It’s absolutely strange.”

Everyone in the hall frowned. All of them were aware of how different this time was. Cloud Ying looked at Thunder Yun, his eyes shone as he said, “General, is it possible that something happened back at the capital?”

When Thunder Yun heard Cloud Ying, he couldn’t help but gawk, then his complexion changed as he said, “What do you mean?”

Cloud Ying replied, “Sir Marshal might have encountered an accident. All these years, our Taurus Continent has been striving to expand in all directions. And the majority of all these accomplishments belong on Sir Marshal himself. With his popularity, there are people who know of him while being unaware of the King. So I have some worries.”

Thunder Yun’s complexion sank, he immediately shouted, “Fei’er, come here!”

Fei’er, who guarded the entrance, immediately walked over. Thunder Yun looked at Fei’er and said, “I will write a letter. You need to find a way for this letter to reach the hands of the Marshal. Remember, you need to be quick.”

Then Thunder Yun began to brandish his brush as stroke upon stroke brought words into his letter. Then he placed the letter into a small bamboo tube before handing it over to Fei’er. After that, Fei’er bowed to Thunder Yun before he turned around to leave.

Thunder Yun turned to Cloud Ying and the others and said, “No matter what happens, go and return to your divisions. Get ready for anything. Remember, if the Third Prince wanted to make you into cannon fodder, make sure to cleverly dodge the responsibility.”

Cloud Ying and the others weren’t fools, so they immediately understood what Thunder Yun meant. They were all members of the Marshal’s camp. If something did happen in the capital, then the enemy certainly won’t let the Marshal’s subordinates go. They would cut the wings of the Marshal before going on to their next plan.

However, it wasn’t easy to just deal with them. Each of the Generals had their own army, and these people were with each other for many years. It can be said that the Generals’ control over their own army was unparalleled. If someone took their positions away, a mutiny might happen within the army. Because of this, the best way to remove these people was to use a borrowed knife to kill. They would have these people act as cannon fodder against Zhao Hai, using Zhao Hai’s hand to kill the Generals and their army. When that happens, the threat would vanish without spilling blood on their hands.

Cloud Ying and the others nodded before they stood up and bowed to Thunder Yun. Thunder Yun went out of his hall and gazed at the floating sword carriage, a flash going through his eyes.

The Third Prince didn’t think that his move would elicit such serious reaction from Thunder Yun. Moreover, he didn’t expect that this matter would just be a fuse, causing events to happen in the background that was beyond his expectations.

At this time, the Third Prince was throwing a tantrum inside the sword carriage. He thought that he was insulted. His maids just stood there with their heads down, doing their best to not make a move. They knew the Third Prince’s temper, if they dared to move, then they would certainly be severely punished.

After throwing a fit inside the carriage, the Third Prince finally stopped breaking things. Then he turned his head to one of his maids before grabbing one of them and tearing her clothes open…….

After Fei’er received Thunder Yun’s letter, he immediately left the Divine Race’s camp and flew towards the Divine Realm’s direction. But after completely leaving the camp, Fei’er slowed down. Then he took the letter out of the bamboo tube and read it without hesitation.

After reading the letter, a twinkle appeared on Fei’er’s eyes. Then his figure moved as he changed his direction. Instead of heading towards the Divine Realm, he actually chose to head towards the other side of the Radiant Empire!

Chapter 802: Prosperous Ark Space

Zhao Hai has been paying attention to the Divine Race’s camp ever since the Third Prince arrived. Although he couldn’t find out what Thunder Yun and the others talked about, he managed to see Fei’er’s action. However, he couldn’t understand what Fei’er was doing.

Zhao Hai was certain that Fei’er was sent to deliver a letter. But Fei’er actually read the letter before going off to a different direction.

Zhao Hai saw Fei’er go to the Winged Pegasus camp first, then to the Barbarians. Only after visiting the two camps did he head towards the Divine Realm. This made Zhao Hai feel that something was fishy.

Laura and the others also saw Fei’er’s action. When Fei’er finally went to the Divine Realm, Laura looked at Zhao Hai ni confusion as she asked, “Brother Hai, why do I feel that something isn’t right? It seems like there is a problem with the Divine Race’s interior.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Remember when I said that the Winged Pegasus and the Barbarian Clans hate the Divine Race more than us? I thought the Giants were different, and were completely loyal. But it seems like those those conquered by the Divine Race are all unwilling to stay as slaves.”

Laura stared before her two eyes shined, “Brother Hai, you mean?”

Zhao Hai smiled and then turned to Lizzy and said, “From now on, make sure to minimize the losses made to the Winged Pegasus and Barbarian troops. As long as they don’t go too far, then we’ll leave them be.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “I don’t think the Third Prince will allow them to do that. But we still need to prepare. I believe the Prince would stage an attack in a couple of days.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Go make some plans.” Lizzy nodded before she turned and took Megan upstairs to plan their move.

Laura looked at the two before she turned to look at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Now that the people of the Ark Continent has entered the Space, I’ve become less busy compared to those two.”

Zhao Hai smiled as he extended his arms over Laura and Ruyen’s shoulders before saying, “You had it hard. Make sure to take a proper rest in the following days. Don’t forget, we still need to get those Goblins later.”

Laura nodded while Ruyen stayed silent. For Ruyen, being close to Zhao Hai was already enough.

At this time, Cai’er flew towards Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, Brother Wales is inviting you over for a drink. Will you go? He has been inviting you over for several times already,”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he couldn’t help but laugh, “Why wouldn’t I go? I’ll go, i’ll go. My Brother is asking for drinks. I wouldn’t not go.” Then he took the women along with him to Wales

Even Lizzy and Megan who were formulating plans were pulled over.

Before long, Zhao Hai appeared in the Ark Space’s Prairie. Wales was pacing back and forth in his tent, eagerly waiting for Zhao Hai.

After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, Wales immediately laughed and said, “You guys actually came. Its been a few days, you really made me wait.”

Zhao Hai laughed and replied, “Things have been quite busy. Right, Big Brother, wait for some time, I have something good to show you.”

Wales looked in anticipation, “Something good? What is it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “When the time comes I’ll let you know.”

Wales stopped caring about it as he laughed and said, “Alright, just tell me whenever you want. But for now, come have a few cups with me. Someone, quickly go and roast some cows.” Needless to say, when they heard that Zhao Hai arrived, the other Herculean Bulls went over to see him. These people were very familiar with Zhao Hai, so they joked and laughed with each other.

Zhao Hai looked at them before he frowned jokingly, “Why are you all here? Stay away, I need some room to breathe.”

The Herculean Bulls weren’t afraid of Zhao Hai’s fake anger. Instead, they went forward before one of them chuckled and said, “Prince, you have been working hard. I had my wife make some milk skin just for you.”

Zhao Hai looked at the person and said, “Get lost. When I said milk skin, I meant those made from Argali.” The person didn’t care. He still grinned by Zhao Hai’s side as the two of them laughed and joked with each other. In the end, Zhao Hai gave each person a bottle of milk wine before they scurried away.

Wales looked at all of these with a huge grin. When the people went away, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “These guys treat you better than me. When they see you come, everyone welcomes you very well. I don’t get treated this way.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s natural. They like me more than they like you.”

Wales laughed, “I just said that to flatter you, I didn’t think you’d eat it up. Hahaha. Come on, let’s have a drink. I’m afraid that your capacity for alcohol has regressed. You have been fighting the Demons and the Divine Race all this time. There hasn’t been a time for you to drink.”

Zhao Hai laughed as well, “And I’m afraid that you won’t be able to return to your tent. Right, Big Brother, why haven’t I seen mister Yale? Where is he?”

Wales smiled and said, “He’s in close door cultivation. He said he had some epiphany and wanted to make a new beast token. Don’t worry about him. At this point, we have been living great lives. No wars are happening since the grass here is so good. The grass grow so quickly that the argali couldn’t eat them all in time. In addition to the grass, there are caravans going along the grassland every day, selling inexpensive human goods. Along with that, we also enjoy Dwarf and Elven items.’[1]

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s good that you’re happy, that means I didn’t make a wrong choice. Brother, later on, I will open a shop here. If you have anything excess to sell, then you can just take it to the shop. At the same time, if you want to buy anything, you can also go there. I can guarantee the supplies offered in the shop.”

Wales’ eyes shone, “That’s good. Although there are a lot of caravans in the Prairie, it’s still quite difficult to look for certain things.”

At this time, some people got up and offered the two of them some milk wine. Naturally, this wasn’t the one purified by Zhao Hai, instead, it was one made by the Beastmen themselves. This was only done to offer respects, the other cups were drank with purified milk wine.

Zhao Hai drank the milk wine and let out a long breath before saying, “When you entered the Space, I can finally feel relief. These days, the Demons and the Divine Race have increased their forces. The Divine Race had their Third Prince come personally. But more worrying are the Demons, their Great Demon King actually came. I’m afraid we won’t be able to hold of for too long.”

Wales placed his glass down as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother, you’ve been working hard.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not really that hard. I just find the Divine Race disgusting so I want to give them a good beating.”

Wales slightly smiled and didn’t say anything. Wales knew that when they entered the Space, Zhao Hai would no longer have any extra worries. However, this also meant that Zhao Hai was now alone in facing the Demons and the Divine Race.

In the past, the groups in the continent were very eager to send troops because their lives were threatened. If they don’t help in the war, then they would be killed by the Divine Race. But now it was different. Since they were now inside the Space, the threat of the Demons and the Divine Race had virtually vanished. From this point on, it would be difficult to convince the people to fight against the Ark Continent’s invaders.

What Wales didn’t know was the fact that this aspect only held truth because they hadn’t been inside the Space for too long. With enough time, the people inside would be predisposed to regard Zhao Hai’s needs. Not to say dispatching troops, even if Zhao Hai wanted them to die, then they wouldn’t hesitate to do so.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to explain this ability. After all, this came with the Space. Even if he wanted to change it, he couldn’t. Besides, Zhao Hai preferred this development, this meant that there would be no traitors inside the Space.

Before long, the argali and bulls were roasted. Aside from Wales, everyone in the Herculean Bull tribe attended this meeting. Everyone ate and drank with each other.

After the event, Zhao Hai returned to the Space’s villa to take a rest. Then Zhao Hai went to the living room and opened the monitor. But this time, he wasn’t watching the Demons and the Divine Race, instead, he was looking at the events happening in the Ark Space

The people in the Ark Space has had it well. After the Great Clans re-established their authority, everything fell in place very quickly.

Zhao Hai was very happy about this situation. This was the reason why he decided to make the Ark Space identical to the Ark Continent. If he didn’t make them similar, then the people of the Ark Continent would need to adjust to their new environment, giving Zhao Hai unnecessary worries.

The Empires of the Ark Space were now up and running, even resuming trade with each other. Moreover, the situation was even much better compared to before since the Fishmen, Beastmen, Dwarves, and Elves were now mingling with the Humans and each other. Discrimination was also slowly diminishing, removing the barriers erected by the Radiant Church in the past.

Recently, the people of the continent had experienced a lot of things, especially when they were under pressure from the Demons and the Divine Race. This caused the Humans and the other races to unite with each other. Also, when people emigrated to the Space’s Ark Continent, Zhao Hai explicitly forbade the discrimination towards the other races. Because of this, the Humans started to accept the other races more and more.

After seeing that things have been normal in the Space, Zhao Hai felt relieved. Then he changed the monitor’s image to the Divine Race’s camp. Zhao Hai was quite curious about what changes the Third Prince would impose on the army.

And just as Zhao Hai shifted the monitor, he saw Thunder Yun approaching the imperial palace of the Radiant Empire. Zhao Hai knew that ever since arriving to the continent, the Third Prince had taken up residence inside the Empire’s Royal Palace.

* * *

It might be beast tablet, forgot which is which. I’ll change it when I go review the past chapters.

Chapter 803: Strange Javelin Attacks

Once Thunder Yun entered the Imperial Palace, Zhao Hai can no longer see his actions. Since that was the case, Zhao Hai turned his attention towards the Northern Icefield. He wanted to see how the Underworld’s creatures were doing right now.

At this point, the poisonous mist of the Northern Icefield had already swallowed a third of the Beastman Prairie. Inside the mist were a lot of undead wandering around. And as he neared the center of the Icefield, Zhao Hai found it harder and harder to see the situation because the density of the mist was too strong. However, he can still spot some low-level undead in the surroundings.

Zhao Hai certainly wouldn’t let this opportunity go. From time to time, he would grab some undead and place them in the Space. He wanted to see if he can bait some strong creatures out from the underworld.

Just as Zhao Hai grabbed another undead, he suddenly received word from Cai’er. The Divine Race were about to make their move. After he heard that, Zhao Hai immediately changed the monitor’s image back to the Divine Race.

After he turned the display, Zhao Hai loudly said, “Lizzy, Megan, come down here. It’s time for work.” Lizzy and Megan immediately gave confirmation before they went into the living room. They were just formulating plans on how to deal with the Divine Race, so when they heard Zhao Hai they immediately had their spirits up.

After the two arrived downstairs, Zhao Hai immediately adjusted the monitor to show Thunder Yun’s ugly expression as he left the Imperial Palace. Upon returning to his camp, the Generals of the Divine Race army started to amass their troops. It seems like they were getting ready to attack the Ark Continent.

When Lizzy saw this, she smiled and said, “It’s really his first time in the battlefield. He didn’t even give the reinforcing army enough time to rest. Just after one night and they are now starting to move. It seems like we’re facing an impatient person.”

Zhao Hai smiled as well, “Go do your thing. I really want to take a look at how that young man reacts.” When Lizzy and Megan heard Zhao Hai, both of them chuckled.

Their plan was to send out an army to harass just like before, but this time, the intensity would be reduced. This would make the Divine Race relax and overextend their advance into the Ark Continent. After two days, they would be so far into the mainland that they would take a long time to return to the Radiant Empire. At that time, Zhao Hai would attack the Radiant Empire, snatching some magic cannons for himself while also taking some Goblins into the Space. This should force the Divine Race to retreat.

If the Divine Race didn’t retreat, then Zhao Hai would use the defenses they built on the Accra Mountains to withstand the Divine Race’s attack. At that time, the Demons should have already gotten news. The Demons wouldn’t want to fall behind the Divine Race and will send troops after them. Then both of them would be blocked by the Accra Mountains. Zhao Hai also wanted to see whether the two invaders would work together in order to annex the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai believed that cooperation between the Demons and the Divine Race was impossible. When the time comes, the two of them would surely fight with each other. When that happens, Zhao Hai would grab more undead from the underworld and then wait for the strong underworld creatures to arrive. Then Zhao Hai would retreat from the Accra Mountain to allow the two races entry into the center of the Continent. Once the two meet the Underworld’s creatures, then Zhao Hai would hit them from behind.

As Zhao Hai thought of this, the Divine Race has dispatched their troops. Their advance wasn’t too quick. Moreover, Zhao Hai noticed that the Third Prince’s advance was at the front while Thunder Yun’s army took the rear.

When Lizzy saw this, her eyes shone, she smiled faintly and said, “Good. Their arrangement suits our plans very well. Once they go out of the Radiant Empire’s territory, we’ll send our harassment army. However, we cannot hit them too much, we’ll give them the expression that we can be easily dealt with.”

Megan smiled, “This is that Third Prince’s first time in the battlefield. We need to give him some face. If he gets terrified this quickly, then that wouldn’t be too good.”

Zhao Hai looked at the both of them and helplessly shook his head. These women are scary, sometimes scarier than men. Now that the Third Prince was faced against Lizzy and Megan, it would be difficult for him to have the courage to return to the battlefield in the future.

Zhao Hai turned his attention back to the Divine Race army. The Barbarian and Winged Pegasus soldiers who came with the Third Prince also moved alongside the reinforcing army, forming two wings beside it. Moreover, these troops were elites. There were flying 9th rank Barbarian Heavy Cavalry as well as some God-rank Winged Pegasus light cavalry. These God-rank cavalry units could also establish their Domains, providing them with terrifying prowess in the battlefield.

Then Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy and Megan and said, “The Barbarian and Winged Pegasus races had sent their elites. You need to send people and see whether they intend to go all out or were just acting. If they are acting, then don’t pressure them too much. We don’t want them to get angry at us even more.”

Lizzy smiled and said, “It’s fine. Although these Winged Pegasus are fast, there is still no way for them to catch up to the undead. We’ll clash with them at first, then after that we start our plans. We’ll make sure to send fewer troops to them compared to the Divine Race, showing them our kind intentions. At the same time, the Divine Race would have suspicion towards the two. Once a disagreement happens, then their army would surely crumble.”

At this time, Laura and the others went in. Seeing them arrive, Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Let’s go outside. Meg, please prepare some tea and snacks. Let’s eat while looking at the Divine Race’s advance.”

Lizzy and the others giggled as they followed Zhao Hai outside. On the other hand, Meg went with Cai’er to prepare some tea and desserts. Zhao Hai hadn’t been able to find some good tea in the Ark Continent before. However, he finally discovered some good leaves in the Elven Forest.

The Third Prince was currently sitting inside his sword carriage. A crystal was installed inside the carriage that allowed him to see the army outside. This was his first time in the battlefield, therefore he couldn’t help but feel excited inside.

However, when he thought about Thunder Yun’s actions in the morning, the Third Prince’s expression couldn’t help but sink. He coldly snorted and said, “That Old Guy certainly isn’t as powerful as they say. That Zhao Hai better wish that I don’t meet him, otherwise, I’ll show him how terrifying I could be.”

The ten maids stood behind the Third Prince. But their faces, hands, and any skin not covered exposed their bruises and wounds.

One could say that 9th ranks were full of vitality, small wounds like those can be healed in a short time. However, the Third Prince was as sick person. If someone he beat up would have their wounds heal, then the Third Prince would certainly hit them more. Because of this, the maids didn’t dare to heal their wounds. They can only stand there while enduring the pain.

Although the Prince hadn’t gone to the battlefield before, he still managed to properly study warfare. This allowed him to understand the situation of the battlefield. The King also had him carry out some bandit subjugation back in the Divine Realm. But these bandits were actually Goblins of the Divine Realm.

Even if the Goblins were subjugated by the Divine Race, there were still clumps of them hidden on unexplored areas. Although one would find it hard to survive on those places, the Third Prince still went on a killed all of them.

These Goblins can’t even eat properly, so how could they resist these Divine Race soldiers. Because of this, it was impossible for the Third Prince to gain proper combat experience. Still, when it came to marching, the Third Prince was quite experienced. His current army was well-trained, there were no problems in the march. They even managed to look elite while doing so.

The army slowly left the Radiant Empire. The Third Prince knew that not long after Thunder Yun left the Empire, they were met by harassment attacks from the Ark Continent. Moreover, he heard that those blood lightning javelins were very strong.

Although the Third Prince thought otherwise, he was still very careful. Once they reached the border of the Radiant Empire, the Third Prince immediately ordered the army to be alert, especially the Barbarian and Winged Pegasus armies on both sides.

On the other hand, Thunder Yun was at the rear observing the Third Prince’s actions. After some time he sighed and said, “Fei’er, what do think the Third Prince’s reaction would be after the attack?’

After hearing no reply, Thunder Yun turned his head to look only to see another Thunder Clan person and not Fei’er. Then he remembered that he had sent Fei’er off to send a letter. After seeing the Giant that wasn’t Fei’er, Thunder Yun sighed and stopped talking.

Once the Third Prince gave his order, his facial expression turned into excitement as he looked to both sides of the army. He wanted to know what attacks these Ark Continent people really have.

Sure enough, the Ark Continent didn’t disappoint him. It didn’t take a long time before a cavalry unit appeared on one side. These Cavalry units didn’t attack the Barbarian cavalry nor Winged Pegasus cavalry. Instead, it headed directly to the Center army. The Third Prince’s face flushed, his held his breath as he looked at the incoming cavalry attack.

That team of cavalry quickly arrived in front of the Divine Race army and let loose their javelins. This made the Third Prince anxious, he stared at the descending javelins to see how strong they were.

The javelin came down quite fast before an explosive sound was heard. Moreover, the explosion threw dust in the air. Once the dust has cleared, the Third Prince couldn’t help but be surprised at the result.

The attacked Divine Race soldiers had a bewildered expression on their faces as they stood there. They weren’t vaporized or even wounded. The attack just managed to dirty their armor and faces.

Chapter 804: Playing With You!

A Weak Explosion!

The explosion has prestige and power, but it completely lacked in might. This made the Divine Race dumbfounded. It was just like a midday thunder, just a loud sound but there was no rain.

The Third Prince looked blankly at the dirtied Divine Race soldiers, all of which were standing there looking silly. For a good while, nobody was able to mutter any words.

“Hahaha!” The Third Prince burst into laughter. He has no reason not to laugh, what happened was too funny. “These are the blood lightning beads that Thunder Yun warned me about? Hahaha. Such trash. Only trash like him would be defeated by that attack.”

The Third Prince was currently full of pride. He didn’t think that the Ark Continent’s attack would actually be this weak. In his opinion, destroying such an enemy would be as easy as turning his own palm.

Thunder Yun, who was at the rear of the army, had also paid attention to what happened. He was similarly staring blankly at the recent explosion. However, Thunder Yun knew that those weren’t the true blood lightning beads. As far as he knew, those javelins were weaker than those in the past by about a hundred times.

When Thunder Yun saw this, his complexion couldn’t help but change, “How can it be that weak? What is Zhao Hai planning to do? Does he want to lure us deep into the continent? I need to warn his Majesty about this.”

After he said that, Thunder Yun waved his hand and called a messenger over. He looked at the messenger and said, “Tell His Highness the Third Prince that the attack of the Ark Continent aren’t this weak. They are certainly up to something. Ask His Highness to be careful.”

The messenger nodded before he turned around and walked. But quickly after that, another attack came. And just like before, the javelins only managed to make a loud explosion, no damage was caused whatsoever.

At this time, the messenger arrived at the sword carriage. He gave respects to the carriage’s guards before saying, “General Thunder Yun sent this one to convey a message to His Majesty.”

The guard looked contemptuously at the messenger before he coldly said, “Wait here.” Then the guard turned around and walked towards the sword carriage. While he was looking at the guard, the messenger suddenly heard something. A guard whispered to another guard while looking at him, he said, “Those guys were defeated by those weak attacks. Hahaha. What a joke.”

The other guards replied, “Perhaps they died because of the climate here. Thunder Yun just said that they were killed in the war so that he can gain military merit despite his failure.”

Then the two of them laughed. Although their voices weren’t loud, they were audible enough to be heard by the messenger. The messenger’s expression immediately sank, then he looked coldly at the two guards.

Before long, the guard that went to the sword carriage came back. He looked at the messenger and said, “The Third Highness is very busy. He doesn’t have the time to see you. If you have something to say, then you can leave it here. If not, then you can leave.”

The messenger didn’t expect this to be the case, however, he endured the humiliation as he said, “General Thunder Yun asked me to tell the Third Prince that the attack of the Ark Continent aren’t this weak. They certainly have something planned. The General asked His Highness to be careful.”

The guard gave a halfhearted nod before he said, “Alright, you can leave now.” The messenger looked at the guard’s reaction as he bitterly clenched his teeth before turning around to leave.

The messenger was quite familiar with these guards. They were known as the Divine Sword Cavalry Division. They were elite cavalries of the Taurus Continent. Each one of them had God-rank strength. Moreover, their fighting strength were the strongest in the Taurus Continent. One could say that they were the elites among elites.

In the past, when the Taurus Continent was still fighting with the other continents, these cavalry soldiers were very formidable. However, the Taurus Continent was now in a state of peace. Even if a fight came, it would only be something that the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus Armies could deal with. There simply was no reason to dispatch the Divine Sword Cavalry units.

Most of the veterans of this unit had already retired, leaving the division with recruits that haven’t gone to the battlefield before. The reason they became God-ranks was entirely due to practice. Although such an army was still strong, one couldn’t be sure about their true might in the battlefield. When the messenger returned to Thunder Yun’s side, he bowed and said, “General, the Third Prince is said to be very busy. He doesn’t have the time to see me. Because of this, I can only leave a verbal message behind.”

Thunder Yun understood the meaning of what the messenger said. This made his expression sink. The Third Prince was expressing his stance on not listening to his advice.

Thunder Yun sighed. Although he wanted to do something, he knew that he was unable to do so at this time. His commanding position has been taken away by the Third Prince. In fact, except his own army, he didn’t have any power to command any other troops.

Thunder Yun knew that if he dared to order the rear army, then the Third Prince surely wouldn’t let him off. This made Thunder Yun confused. He didn’t understand why the Third Prince would single him out like this. He remembered that the Third Prince had always been in a good relationship with the Marshal. Why would the Third Prince’s attitude turn into this?

At this time, Zhao Hai was in the Space looking at how the undead were acting a play. They would throw javelins towards the Divine Race army, cause a loud explosion that threw dust in the air, and only managing to dirty the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai knew what’s wrong with the Javelins. Simply, those javelins weren’t equipped blood lightning beads at all. Instead, they were made with the Elves’ stone ball.

The Elves’ stone ball can explode as well, and their might was quite powerful. In the past, they were enough to cause problems to the Ark Continent’s armies. However, one shouldn’t forget that the Ark Continent only had 3rd to 4th rank soldiers in the past. Causing the same problems to the Divine Race would be impossible.

Zhao Hai had these stone balls made specifically for the Third Prince. He didn’t think that it would be this effective.

After seeing the Divine Race relax as they went forward, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh and said, “This is fantastic. The plan is a success. Now I want to see how that Third Prince would look like once he meets  our true attack.”

Lizzy, who was nearby, smiled and said, “This Third Prince is really interesting. Thunder Yun even sent a messenger over to warn him, but in the end, he turned him away.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Isn’t that better? Right, Lizzy, will Thunder Yun predict our plan?”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “He won’t.” Zhao Hai looked at her and asked, “Why?’

Without waiting for Lizzy to speak, Megan answered, “Because deep inside Thunder Yun is also arrogant. He is still looking down on the Ark Continent. Although he already saw our attacks, he wouldn’t expect that we would attack their camp. He would only think that we would lure them deep into the continent. Hehe, the arrogance of the Divine Race wouldn’t change in a short time.”

Zhao Hai nodded. No matter what move the Divine Race made, Zhao Hai was already determined to attack the Radiant Empire to get some magic cannons and Goblins.

The attacks were still going on, but for Zhao Hai and the others, this was only a spectacle to joke at. Nothing noteworthy was to be seen here. Instead, they shifted their attention to another place.

Naturally, they were looking at the Demons. Now that the Divine Race had made their move, it was inevitable that the Demons would have some changes in their camp. Zhao Hai wanted to look at how the Demons plan to deal with his harassment tactics.

In order to urge the Third Prince to go further, Zhao Hai didn’t use his blood devouring mosquitoes for attack. Although Zhao Hai had been quite busy because of the evacuation of the Ark Continent, he didn’t stop accumulating blood devouring mosquitoes in the Space. Every time the mosquitoes were available, he release them in the Space. Because of this, the number of mosquitoes that Zhao Hai had was extremely astonishing. Perhaps aside from the Demons and the Divine Race, no other group could resist the attack of this group of mosquitoes.

Laura and the others have been relaxing lately. But Laura had found something she can busy herself with, and it was analyzing the Processing Machine. The Processing Machine can make anything, some were pre-designed while some needed custom blueprints. Not only was Laura studying its function, she was also looking into the costs.

Using the Processing Machine costs money. There were things that both the Ark Continent and the Processing Machine can make at the same time frame. The only difference is the overall cost.

Laura was studying which product was better made in the Processing Machine and which were more suited to being made by the Ark Continent.

This study held great significance to them. The Space’s consumption of gold coins was just too absurd. They needed gold for the potions as well as changing the Space’s landscape. It would be impossible for them to go forward without means to acquire more gold. Laura wanted to see which places they could save on costs. Moreover, Laura was also planning to use the Space to conduct trades with the people in the Ark Space.

There were things that were very valuable when sold to the Space’s store but were cheaply made in the Ark Continent, and the same was true for the other way. They could buy things from the Ark Continent for cheap and then sell them to the Space for more money. At the same time, they could also use the Processing Machine to make cheap valuable products and sell them in the Ark Space for a significant markup. This was an extremely lucrative business!

Chapter 805: Have A Chat

When Zhao Hai first heard that Laura wanted to do this, he persuaded her to do otherwise. It wasn’t useful. In any case, the things produced by the Space at this point was already very valuable. There’s no need to study the little things, their supply of gold coins would still mount up regardless.

However, Laura insisted that she do this. In the end, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything more. He knew that Laura was just looking for something to do, she didn’t like idling around.

Berry and Ruyen had found themselves going along with Laura in the past few days. They weren’t interested in matters of war. Therefore, Zhao Hai just left them to do their own thing.

A day passed by and the Divine Race army was still advancing. Moreover, they had already occupied three cities in the first day. They were almost caught up to Thunder Yun’s progress in the past.

Zhao Hai didn’t carry any large scale attack on this Divine Race Army. He was aware that his real targets were the Radiant Empire as well as the Demons.

On the second day, the Demon Race finally moved. Under the leadership of the Demon King, an army of 40 million Demons set out towards the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai looked at the 40 million strong Demon Race Army. With his attention mostly focused on the Death Qi army.

The Demons were fully prepared this time. They were plenty of archers as well as powerful crossbows in their army. Moreover, surrounding the army were countless Demon scouts.

Zhao Hai noticed something peculiar, both the Demons and the Divine Race were completely lacking when it came tom cavalry units. The majority of Demons have wings, allowing them flight, hence they didn’t need to use cavalry units. At the same time, a fully grown Divine would reach 9th rank, which also allowed them to fly.

However, Zhao Hai believed that it wasn’t because they didn’t care about cavalry, but instead because they lacked proper mounts. The magic beasts of the Divine Realm were very strong. And it was precisely because of this strength that people found it hard to tame them. Because of this, most people were unable to get mounts for themselves. In this case, forming a cavalry unit would be very difficult. The same situation applied to the Demon Race.

On the other hand, the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus people were special. These two races were predominantly cavalry. The Elites that they had sent out were all cavalry units. Needless to say, the mounts of the Winged Pegasus people were the winged pegasus. These winged pegasus can fly, so it wasn’t weird for them to be made into mounts. What made Zhao Hai confused were the Barbarian people.

The mounts of the Barbarians were their rhinoceros beasts. Although this magic beast was powerful, one could see at a glance that they were innately unable to fly. However, all of the Elite Barbarian Cavalry were actually on top of 9th rank rhinoceros beasts. This surprised Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai had the Space, so it wouldn’t be strange for him to be abundant when it came to 9th rank beasts. But for the Barbarians, how could they amass such high numbers of 9th rank beasts?

Later on, Zhao Hai called the undead Barbarian King and found out that the Barbarian’s way of advancing was the same as the Diamond Apes. Like the Diamond Apes, advancement in cultivation needed to be made alongside their beast companion. This made it harder for them to progress, the same was true for the Barbarians.

If a Barbarian wanted to increase their strength, then they would need to do so alongside their magic beast. Promoting their strength on their own was very difficult, close to impossible.

The he called Winged Pegasus Zhan over and asked about the Winged Pegasus people. Once the Divine Race conquered the Winged Pegasus race, it should be understandable for them to snatch the winged pegasus mounts and use them for themselves. However, Zhao Hai noticed the lack of cavalry units among the Divine Race army even with this arrangement. Only after asking Zhan about it did Zhao Hai finally understood. The winged pegasus couldn’t be used by anyone. Only when a person had the blood of a Winged Pegasus clansman would the winged pegasus agree to be mounted. Because of this, even if the Divine Race had conquered the Winged Pegasus Clan, they were still unable to use the mounts for themselves.

After hearing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh and think about the mysteries of creation. It was fortunate that Zhao Hai had the Space. The winged pegasus that the Space brought up didn’t have the problem. Anyone can ride the Space’s winged pegasus as long as Zhao Hai agreed to it.

Although the Demons didn’t have any mounts, most of them had wings, so they weren’t strangers to flight. This can be seen on the scouts that the Great Demon King had sent out, all of them were extremely fast fliers.

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Race and sighed. To be honest, he couldn’t find himself truly hating on the Demons. In Zhao Hai’s mind, the Demons had reasonable reason to conquer the Ark Continent. And since the Demons hadn’t done excessive things upon arriving, Zhao Hai couldn’t really hate on them.

But not hating on them doesn’t mean that they would just be left on their own. Zhao Hai understood that the Demons just wanted to have a good life. However, Zhao Hai wasn’t a saint. If you march on his home, intending to snatch the place where his family lives in, then prepare to face retaliation.

At this time, Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, go drag the Divine Race for two days. We’ll deal with the Demons first. I want to have a chat with the Great Demon King.”

Lizzy frowned when she heard this, she said, “Chat? Big Brother Hai, do you think you can convince the Demons to retreat?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I’m not that naive. However, the situation changed. The Demons are unaware of the Underworld’s connection to the Ark Continent. I want to try and give him this information to see if they wanted to stop their advance.”

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai before she nodded and said, “Alright. But Brother Hai, I urge you to not get your hopes too high.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s going to be fine.” Then Zhao Hai’s body flashed as he went out of the Space. This time he didn’t bring Shue and the others.

As the Demons advanced forward, their scouts were carefully examining their path. The scouts that the Great Demon King had brought were the elites of their class. Their speed was fast, moreover, they were unlike the Divine Race, they didn’t underestimate the people from the Ark Continent. The Demons would always do everything at their full power, no matter who their enemies were.

As the scouts went on, one of them suddenly noticed a black spot on the horizon. As the scout stared, he quickly saw what the black spot was. It was a person wearing a Dark Mage’s robe. And this person was stepping on a blood red sword.

The Demon couldn’t help but stare blankly at the approaching person. When the person drew nearer, the scout can finally identify who it was. It was the Demon Race’s biggest enemy, Zhao Hai.

The Demon scout immediately became afraid as he prepared to turn around and run. But at this time, Zhao Hai opened his mouth and said, “Demon Race friend, wait. This Zhao Hai wants you to convey his words to the Great Demon King. Please tell his Majesty that this Zhao Hai wants to have a chat with him.”

Zhao Hai inspected the Demon scout. This scout was different compared to the Vile Demons. This Demon had a face but his body was just like a vulture. He was tall and slender, his neck was naked but at its base there was a swathe of feathers, looking just like a scarf. He had azure black feathers that had a metallic luster. He also had a bare tail, two strong looking claws, and two axe like wings that spanned about 10 meters from tip to tip.

The Demon couldn’t help but stare blankly at Zhao Hai. He looked at the scout calmly and smiled, “Please send my message.”

The Demon looked at Zhao Hai for quite some time before he looked at the sword Zhao Hai was steppin on. Then after that, he turned around and flew.

Zhao Hai had always thought of cruising the skies on top of a flying sword. He had long envied those Chinese stories where a character would step on a flying sword and enjoyed the freedom between the heaven and the earth. Because of this, Zhao Hai deliberately transformed his staff into this flying sword.

The Demon scout quickly returned to the army and went directly towards the Great Demon King’s chariot. He went to a group of Death Qi warriors and said, “Please send word. Demon Vulture Division’s Third Squad member Luo is seeking audience with the Great Demon King.”

The Death Qi soldier looked at the Demon Vulture and with his cold voice he asked, “What do you want to say. Have you found the Ark Continent’s troops?”

The Vulture Demon doesn’t want to send the wrong message, so he shook his head and said, “We haven’t. However, this one has been blocked by Zhao Hai himself. He had me send a message saying that he wanted to have a chat with His Majesty the Great Demon King.”

Upon hearing the Vulture Demon, the Death Qi soldier couldn’t help but knit his brows. Then he nodded and said, “Wait here.” Then he turned around and flew towards the Devil’s War Chariot.

The Great Demon King was currently sitting inside his chariot. The contents of his table was the same as before, two side dishes and a bottle of liquor.

At this time a knock was heard, then a voice came, “Your Majesty, a Demon Vulture Scout has sent a message. He said that Zhao Hai had sent word that he wanted to have a chat with you.”

The Great Demon King stared, he stood up and then opened the chariot’s door. The soldier gave his respects to the Great Demon King before he said, “Your Majesty, the Demon Vulture Division’s Third Squad Member Luo came said that Zhao Hai stopped him only to have him send a message that he wanted to have a talk with you.”

The Great Demon King knit his brows and said, “He wants to chat? Interesting. Go and call Demon Vulture Luo. I want to personally ask him about this matter.”

The soldier complied and the turned around to leave. Before long, Demon Vulture Luo appeared by the side of the Great Demon King’s chariot. When Demon Vulture Luo saw the Great Demon King, he immediately lowered his head and gave a salute, “This one has seen Your Majesty.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Are you sure it is Zhao Hai?”

Demon Vulture Luo nodded and said, “Replying to His Majesty. From what I saw in the official document, it is indeed Zhao Hai. However, he didn’t have his undead along with him. Instead, he was stepping on a blood red sword that was floating in midair.”

Chapter 806: The Great Demon King Meets Zhao Hai

Normally, the last detail would be insignificant. However, when the Great Demon King heard it, his expression couldn’t help but change. He looked at the Demon Vulture and said, “Did you really see Zhao Hai stepping on a flying sword? Not something else?”

Demon Vulture Luo was given a scare when he saw the Great Demon King’s change in expression. He quickly replied, “Replying to His Majesty. This one has indeed seen a blood red sword. But that sword was somewhat different compared to the ones we use. That sword had a tassel trailing behind it.

Upon hearing Vulture Luo’s answer, the Great Demon King’s expression changed once more. Then he said, “Alright, you can go back.” Demon Vulture Luo gave a bow before turning around to leave.

When Demon Vulture left, the Great Demon King immediately gave command, “Stop the army. Call Demon Dragon over.” Then the guard outside complied and went on to transmit the orders.

The Great Demon King stood in front of his carriage door, looking into the distant skies as he muttered, “Is he one of them? That’s impossible!”

Before long the Demon Dragon king arrived by the chariot. He gave the Great Demon King a salute before saying, “Your Majesty, you called for me.”

The Great Demon King nodded, then he said, “Zhao Hai just sent someone to tell me that he wanted to have a chat. I’ve stopped the army and will hand temporary authority to you. I will be going first to meet Zhao Hai.”

When he heard the Great Demon King, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but stare. Then his complexion changed as he said, “Your Majesty, I ask you to think about it once more. Zhao Hai is strong, and his schemes cannot be counted. Your Majesty, this is too dangerous.”

The Great Demon King shook his head and said, “You don’t understand. When the scout came to give his report, he also told me that Zhao Hai was riding on top of a flying sword. And that this sword has a different style to those we generally use.”

When he heard the Great Demon King, the Demon Dragon King stared, then he whispered, “Your Majesty, you suspect him to be…..”

The Great Demon King nodded, “Correct. Because of this, I need to meet Zhao Hai. Don’t worry, although Zhao Hai is strong, I’m quite formidable myself.” This time, the Demon Dragon King didn’t stop him. Then the Great Demon King turned his head to the chariot’s driver and said, “Go forward.”

As soon as he heard that, the driver raised his hand and whipped the elephant-type magic beasts, urging the carriage to go forward. Before long, the carriage has left the army behind.

Zhao Hai was currently standing on his flying sword that the blood ghost staff transformed to. He felt that standing on a flying sword did indeed feel very good. The breeze brushing on his face while the clouds fluttered around him.

Before long, block spots were seen in the distance. These black spots became bigger and bigger as its figure was clearly seen, it was the Great Demon King’s carriage. What surprised Zhao Hai was the fact that the Great Demon King didn’t bring any escort along with him.

Zhao Hai stood calmly on his flying sword as the Devil’s War Chariot got closer and closer. It didn’t take too long before the chariot stopped in front of Zhao Hai. Then the chariot’s door opened as the Great Demon King appeared. He looked at Zhao Hai before shifting his gaze on the flying sword by Zhao Hai’s foot. His eyes shone a flash of light before he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I heard that Mister Zhao Hai wanted to chat with me.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I do indeed have something to discuss with Your Majesty the Great Demon King. I have some information that may interest you.”

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai’s eyes, then he smiled and said, “Alright, then how about you come in and we talk about it inside?” The Great Demon King wanted to see if Zhao Hai had the courage to accept his invitation.

Zhao Hai just gave a smile and said, “Since Your Majesty is inviting me, then how could I decline?” Then his figure moved and appeared in front of the door as he gave the Great Demon King a salute.

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai with interest, then he smiled faintly and said, “Mister, come in.” Then him and Zhao Hai entered the chariot.

When he went in the chariot, Zhao Hai looked around for a moment and didn’t say anything. Then he followed the Great Demon King to his table before sitting on the opposite side. The Great Demon King took his bottle of liquor and poured a glass for Zhao Hai and then for himself. He raised his glass towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, cheers.”

Zhao Hai raised his glass as well and said, “Your Majesty, cheers.” Then the two of them downed their liquor in one go. The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “Mister is really something else. Not only did you enter my chariot, you even drank wine with me. Not a lot of people were as carefree as you. You have my admiration.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty overpraises me. This one just believes that Your Majesty wouldn’t poison the wine. You don’t want to get rid of me at this time.”

The Great Demon King stared, then he said, “Oh, Mister is quite confident.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I am. Your Majesty should be aware that I am the supporting pillar of the Ark Continent. If I were to disappear, then the Ark Continent is finished. Because of this, you wouldn’t deal with me prematurely. I am still quite useful for the Demons.”

The Great Demon King laughed and said, “But just as mister said, you are the pillar of the Ark Continent. Wouldn’t it be great if I kill you right now?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That would be an average person’s thinking. However, Your Majesty isn’t an average person. Your Majesty has another enemy aside from me, the Divine Race. Since Your Majesty has yet to deal with them, then you would want to keep me alive as long as possible. This would allow me and the Divine Race to wound each other, giving the Demons great profits for cheap work.”

The Great Demon King smiled and didn’t say anything more. However, this was a signal that he agreed. Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and said, “I came to meet Your Majesty in order to tell you something. I believe Your Majesty will change the Demon Race’s plan upon hearing it.”

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai. He had no clue what Zhao Hai was about to tell him. Zhao Hai smiled and then continued, “I think Your Majesty has already received information about the Ark Continent preparing to migrate. Am I correct?”

The Great Demon King’s pupils couldn’t help but shrink when he heard this, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Did mister deliberately send this information out?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No. People under Demonic influence has just been found by me recently. I came to know from them about you receiving information. And that information is true.”

The Great Demon King knit his brows, he looked at Zhao Hai, urging him to go on. Zhao Hai then said, “I’ll be honest to Your Majesty. The Ark Continent’s invaders not only comprise of the Demons and the Divine Race. There is another strong group that appeared. They are the main reason why I had the entire continent migrate.”

The Great Demon King was frowning as he listened to Zhao Hai. He wasn’t sure whether Zhao Hai was telling the truth or not. If what Zhao Hai said was real, and a new enemy has appeared on the continent, then migration was a valid move. The only question about this was; where did the Ark Continent’s residents migrate?

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King’s expression then he said, “After repelling both the Demons and the Divine Race, an accident happened in the Ark Continent’s Northern Icefield. I had been there before because I needed to retrieve the Beastmen’s Beast God’s Spear. Because of that I’ve become quite familiar with the place, there were almost no living creatures there, and the temperature is very low, completely not suitable for living in. Due to my prior experience in the icefield, I completely disregarded it when the Demons and the Divine Race came. In my opinion, the icefield was even the safest place in the Ark Continent.”

The Great Demon King nodded, he believed what Zhao Hai said. He was also aware about the Northern Icefield’s situation. He had read the same information from their people in the Continent. They even went on to explore the place for some time. They wanted to take a look whether it was suitable for the Blood Void formation. But in the end, they left disappointed, there were no living beings there to be used as sacrifice.

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and continued, “After knowing that something happened in the icefield, I immediately went there to investigate. At that point, the icefield was covered in a dark mist, in it were large quantities of undead. Fortunately, I’m a Dark Mage. So I captured some undead and turned them into my subordinate before asking them about their origin.” After speaking this, Zhao Hai looked into the eyes of the earnestly listening Great Demon King before he said, “These undead came from the Underworld!”

The Great Demon King’s complexion changed when he heard this. He gave a long stare at Zhao Hai. who gave him a nod and said, “Your Majesty, you haven’t heard it wrong. The undead came from the underworld. A spatial rift is currently at the Northern Icefield, and it leads directly towards the Underworld.”

The Great Demon King stood up and made some steps back and forth. After some time he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Did the Underworld open the spatial rift? Or did they have assistance from other parties?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “There was no help. Although the war had caused the continent to be hectic, there were still three powerful Beastmen tribes left to guard the Icefield, nobody should be able to go through their territories undetected. I suspect this has something to do with the Divine Race’s action. In order to invade the Ark Continent, the Divine Race decided to break the laws of the continent. This caused damage to the Ark Continent’s natural barriers, allowing spatial rifts like the one connected from the Underworld to appear.”

The Great Demon King’s expression changed once more. Then he sat back on his chair and drank a glass of liquor before he muttered, “I thought this would be an opportunity for the Demon Race. It’s a pity. It seems like the Ark Continent would turn into another Underworld.”

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and said, “Does Your Majesty believe me? Aren’t you afraid of me deceiving you?”

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and smiled bitterly, “With Mister’s strength, what’s the use of deceiving me with this? Also, you cannot hide this lie for so long. Wouldn’t we be able to uncover the truth sooner or later?”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Right. Your Majesty, I am not lying. After a period of time, information about the Underworld should reach your ears. I just came here to save you the time.”

The Great Demon King looked straight at Zhao Hai, after some time he said, “It looks like Mister has already completed the Ark Continent’s migration. Otherwise, you wouldn’t be this carefree right now.”

Chapter 807: Eye of Truth

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and smiled, “Your Majesty guessed it right. I didn’t explicitly tell you but the entire Ark Continent’s population had already been moved. Moreover, it’s a place much better than the Ark Continent.”

The Great Demon King faintly smiled and didn’t speak anything else.  Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and couldn’t help but smile as well, then he said, “To be honest, I don’t really feel any hatred for the Demon Race. The Demons invaded the Ark Continent just to have a better life, nobody can judge you for that. You are different from the Divine Race, they just want to invade for the sake of conquest, you don’t.”

The Great Demon King raised an eyebrow, Zhao Hai continued, “I don’t know if Your Majesty is interested about this, but this happened in a previous battle with the Divine Race. In that fight, the Divine Race performed a summoning. But who would’ve thought that the one they summoned was a person? He was called Deity by the Divine Race. And it wasn’t the actual person, but just a projection of his true self.”

When the Great Demon King heard Zhao Hai, his complexion couldn’t help but change. He couldn’t hide the anxiety on his eyes. Upon seeing this reaction, Zhao Hai thought that he might have hit something.

Earlier, Zhao Hai had discovered the Great Demon King’s interest in the flying sword. This interest wasn’t due to curiosity, it was something different. What puzzled Zhao Hai was the hint of anger on the Great Demon King’s eyes.

How could one be angry at a sword? Because of this, Zhao Hai believed that the Great Demon King might have known something, or may even hate a person with a sword like that. The flying sword Zhao Hai chose to model his blood red sword belonged to Lu Wei. In other words, the Great Demon King knew Lu Wei judging by his reaction.

Because of this, Zhao Hai spoke a few words as a test, and he didn’t expect that it would actually yield results. It was clear that the Great Demon King was interested in this topic.

Zhao Hai didn’t hide anything, he looked at the Great Demon King and said, “I ate some losses under that man’s hand. But fortunately, I had some methods of my own, defeating him in the end. I also used a secret technique to find the origin of that man.”

The more he listened to Zhao Hai, the more the Great Demon King became startled. Upon hearing that Zhao Hai knew of that person’s origin, the Great Demon King couldn’t sit still, his two shining eyes looked straight into Zhao Hai as he said, “Can mister tell me?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Before telling Your Majesty, may I know why you are interested in that person? I’ll just let you know, there is no bad blood between the Demons and the Ark Continent. In the future, if I were given the choice to fight with the Demons or not, then I’d rather not. After all, we’ve already left the Ark Continent behind. On the other hand, the Divine Race used their blood sacrifice to invade the Ark Continent. I couldn’t let the Divine Race off lightly. At this point, I couldn’t be considered to be Your Majesty’s enemy.”

The Great Demon King looked deeply into Zhao Hai’s eyes, after some time he nodded and said, “Just as mister said, there is no true hatred between the Demons and the Ark Continent. There’s no reason to fight with each other anymore. However, Mister needs to assure me that what you’ll say would get my interest. Otherwise, you can’t blame me for getting angry.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I can guarantee my own words, Your Majesty. You won’t be disappointed, instead, you might find it good.”

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai before he sighed and said, “I hope so. Mister might not know, but the life of a Demon is quite long. Among the people in Ark Continent, I’m afraid only the Elves would compare to our lifespans. Because of this, every Great Demon King reigns for a very long time. And when a Demon ascends to being a Great Demon King, the Demon God would manifest himself to offer blessing to the new Great Demon King.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he was already aware of this from asking Cai’er. At that time, he needed a deeper understanding of the Demon Race, he needed to know their customs and lifestyles.

The Great Demon King didn’t know what Zhao Hai’s nod meant. He thought it might be because he was listening. So the Great Demon King continued, “When I ascended to the throne, the Demon God showed his image. At that time, I was very excited, after all I was receiving the Demon God’s blessing.”

Zhao Hai understood the Great Demon King. It was the same thing for a successor who believes in a Deity. When they suddenly become the Ruler and receives the blessing of their god, it was normal to feel excitement.

It was at this point that the Great Demon King’s tone changed, “However, I didn’t think that I would see something different. Not a single Demon in the Demon Realm knew that I have a divergent ability. The name of the ability is “Eye of Truth”. All illusions and magic are useless under my gaze. I haven’t told anyone about this, thus, nobody knew.”

Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but light up. He looked at the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, is the Demon God’s appearance different from what you expected?”

The Great Demon King nodded, “This is why I’m interested in what mister will say. Just as Mister said, the Demon God’s appearance was different than what I thought. The Demon God should look like that, but what I saw was not.” Then he pointed to a big painting by the wall. Zhao Hai turned to look at the portrait of the Demon God and then nodded.

The Great Demon King continued, “Although he manifested in the form of the Demon God, his appearance changed in my eyes. He turned into a person wearing a long robe, an attire completely different to those found in the Demon Realm, Divine Realm, or even the Ark Continent. It’s something I haven’t seen before. Most importantly, that person was just a projection attached to a tiny pagoda. In other words, the Demon God that we’ve worshipped all this time, was completely fake!”

As he spoke the last sentence, the Great Demon King crushed the glass on his hand. One could see the obvious agitation in his actions. Then the Great Demon King cleaned his table before continuing, “At that time, a suspicion arose inside me. However, I didn’t disclose this information, allowing me to smoothly assume the position of Great Demon King. After that, the projection vanished from thin air. But I clearly saw that the projection went into the tiny pagoda before flying away into the skies. After I ascended the throne, I tried my best to find clues. In the end, I finally found one in our Demon Race’s Great Demon God statue.”

Zhao Hai listened to the Great Demon King’s tale with interest. The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “That Great Demon God’s statue was said to be an unsurpassed treasure of the Demon Race. According to legend, the Demon God bestowed that statue to the Demon Race. However, I found that inside the statue was a magical formation that was constantly running!”

Zhao Hai suddenly gained clarity. He had always been confused, if the Ark Continent was a minor plane that belonged to a major plane, of which belonged to Lu Wei, then how does he collect faith power? It was obvious that he wouldn’t collect it personally. Now Zhao Hai knew, it was because of that magic formation.

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai, seemingly aware of what Zhao Hai was thinking about. The Great Demon King couldn’t help but ask, “Mister, did something come to mind?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I did think of something. But first I need to tell Your Majesty about the person the Divine Race summoned. From what Your Majesty described, that person looked just like what you’ve seen. I have a portrait of that person here, please take a look.” Then Zhao Hai turned his hand and took out a piece of paper. This paper had a picture made by the Space showing the exact image of Lu Wei.

The Great Demon King looked at the picture that Zhao Hai took out, his expression immediately changed, “Right, it’s this man. This is the person pretending to be the Demon God. After I had my suspicions, I immediately looked into the records of my clan. I didn’t believe that I’m the only one to have the Eye of Truth. In the end I had found out that every single member of my clan that had the ability all died of unknown causes. There were even two of them who became Great Demon Kings, but they still died. Because of this, I reckoned there was someone who didn’t want our ability to see through something. Fortunately, people with Eyes of Truth had the same eyes as those who don’t. Moreover, since I didn’t tell anyone about it, I was able to survive.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “This person was the one summoned by the Divine Race, and they call him Deity. When he was fighting me, he used weapons one after another. One of which was a sword that looked just like mine, however, his sword was smaller. When I defeated him in the end, I was able to obtain his tower. It looked gloomy at first, but after I refined it, it turned into this form.” Then Zhao Hai took the tiny pagoda out.

The Great Demon King looked at the Tiny Pagoda and nodded, “Although there were some changes in style, this should be the pagoda that I’ve seen. Mister, do you know anything about him? Who is he? Why does he want to be worshiped?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Your Majesty, don’t worry, I’ll tell you. When the man’s weapons were broken by me, he decided to use his tiny pagoda. The tiny pagoda turned out to have a soul attack. I was almost killed. Fortunately, I was able to subdue the small pagoda. Then I used a secret technique in order to refine the soul within it, allowing me to know the truth.”

Chapter 808: Taking the Great Demon King

Bang!

The Great Demon King slammed his palm on the table, smashing it in the process. His two eyes were blood red as he puffed and said, “Mister, are you telling the truth? In the eyes of that immortal cultivator, we’re just a means to get faith power? We’re merely tools?”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and didn’t say anything. Although Zhao Hai stayed silent, the Great Demon King understood, what Zhao Hai said was true.

The Great Demon King’s face was pale. Their god was actually just using them to get this faith power. He was currently having a hard time comprehending it right now.

The Great Demon King stood up, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Since mister knew about this, do you have any solutions?”

Zhao Hai nodded, he moved his hand as the table and the glass fragments vanished. In its place was another table with two glasses, several small dishes and a wine pot. Then he invited the Great Demon King to take a drink.

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai, he stared for a moment before he laughed. He sat down and poured himself a glass of wine before drinking it. He smacked his lips for some time before he said, “Nice Wine. This is much better compared to the ones I drink.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, then he said, “This liquor has only been made recently. If Your Majesty likes it, I can give you some.”

The Great Demon King nodded but he didn’t say anything else. Although he looked calm, it was impossible for him to not feel anxious. He wanted to hear Zhao Hai’s plan to deal with the Immortal Cultivator.

Zhao Hai didn’t have the Great Demon King wait for a long time. He ate some dried beef before looking at the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, you should have some understanding with regards to the Ark Continent. The continent is just a minor plane. In the past, no God-rank experts were allowed to stay here. Once an expert reaches God-rank, they would immediately ascend to the Divine Realm. It can be said that the Ark Continent was a subordinate plane to the Divine realm. Am I correct?”

In order to deal with the Ark Continent, the Great Demon King had used a lot of methods in the past few years. This intelligence mission naturally didn’t fail. What Zhao Hai said was correct, and this was also the reason why the Demons decided to take the Ark Continent for themselves. The Ark Continent was a inferior plane compared to the Demon Realm, there should be no problems in conquering it.

Zhao Hai saw that the Great Demon King agreed, then he continued, “I found out from the soul of that Immortal Cultivator that the Demon Realm, the Divine Realm, the Ark Continent, and even the Underworld belong to a major plane. These minor planes can be seen as the rooms on a courtyard that is a major plane. We’re in the same courtyard, but in different rooms.”

The Great Demon King nodded, when Zhao Hai told him about the immortal cultivator, he already had this guess. Zhao Hai only served to prove his suspicion.

Then Zhao Hai said, “In our planes, the highest degree of cultivation is God-rank. Reaching Saint God would be very difficult, and it might even be possible that Saint Gods ascend to a higher realm. This higher realm might even be the immortal cultivator realm. If we manage to ascend to that world, then naturally we would start out as someone weaker than that immortal cultivator. No matter how angry we are, we still can’t do anything.”

The Great Demon King kept silent. He knew that Zhao Hai was right. This was just like when ascended God-ranks from the Ark Continent become Demigods in the Divine Realm.

And these Demigods could only be normal soldiers in the Divine Realm. In this manner, how could a newly ascended person from the Ark Continent get enough power? It was simply impossible.

Then Zhao Hai continued, “Your Majesty. You should know that I have transferred the people of the Ark Continent. To tell you the truth, they were transferred to a unique place. And once I ascend to the immortal cultivation realm one day, all of the people from the Ark Continent would ascend along with me.”

Zhao Hai had said so many things that had shocked the Great Demon King, he looked at Zhao Hai with perfectly round eyes as he said, “Are you lying?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Your Majesty, I wouldn’t dare. If you want, I can take you there.”

The Great Demon King laughed and said, “You have the courage to get inside my chariot, so why wouldn’t I come with you? Let’s go.”

Zhao Hai smiled then he nodded and said, “Then I’ll ask Your Majesty to get ready. We’re going now.” Then he waved his hand as the two disappeared from the room.

Actually, Zhao Hai’s original plan didn’t include taking the Demon King to the Space. He wanted to convince the Great Demon King that the Ark Continent wasn’t any good because of the Underworld. He would have the Great Demon King stop their plans to attack the Ark Continent so that he can deal wholeheartedly deal with the Divine Race.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Great Demon King to know something about Lu Wei. In the end, their discussion came to this. Zhao Hai always wanted to bring the Demons to the Space, however, it was just too far-fetched of an ambition. But when the Great Demon King opened up about Lu Wei, Zhao Hai decided to use this opportunity to win the Great Demon King over. This would be equivalent to convincing the entire Demon Race.

Zhao Hai brought the Great Demon King to the Space and took him for a tour. He wanted to relay how good the life of the people from the Ark Continent had been.

They were currently inside the Ark Space, specifically, inside the Buddha Empire. The Great Demon King saw how the Buddha Empire looked like a ghost country back in the Ark Continent. But here, the situation was completely different. Every city had people inside, all of them were evidently happy with their current situation. It was a bustling scene.

Zhao Hai and the Great Demon King were invisible so that nobody could see them.

After their visit to the Ark Space, Zhao Hai brought the Great Demon King to an ordinary Space that nobody lived in. This place had mountains and flowing water. It had an environment not worse than the Ark Space.

Zhao Hai lead the Demon King to the place and toured the scenery. After looking around for some time, Zhao Hai turned to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, what do you think about this place?”

The Great Demon King was infatuated, “It’s very nice. Much much better compared to the Demon Realm. It would be great if the Demons could live in a place like this.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “As long as Your Majesty agrees, your people can move in..”

The Great Demon King stared, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, you mean?”

Zhao Hai replied, “Your Majesty, to tell you the truth, this place is just like the Ark Space. It is my divergent ability. I can decide who I can let in and who can leave. If Your Majesty wants to settle the Demons here, then it would only be as simple as giving your approval. As long as you agree, then the Demons can live here.”

The Great Demon King gawked, then his complexion sunk as he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What are your conditions?”

To be honest, the Great Demon King was completely captured by the Space. The Demon Realm’s environment was really terrible, anything even a bit better than it would be a blessing to the Demons.

However, the Great Demon King also knew that Zhao Hai wouldn’t propose this if he didn’t have any conditions. He doesn’t believe that Zhao Hai was a saint. From the material that he had acquired, this Zhao Hai was a vicious and merciless character.

Zhao Hai looked at the Great Demon King and smiled, “I actually don’t have anything to ask you. Just like I said, I don’t have any deep hatred for the Demons. I can completely understand why the Demons wanted to invade the Ark Continent, you just want to live in a better place. Additionally, if you live here, then I would have one less enemy to worry about. As for the Divine Race army, they wouldn’t survive. I wouldn’t give them this opportunity, I want all of them to be turned into undead!”

The Great Demon King still didn’t believe Zhao Hai. Suddenly, he thought of something, he turned his head at Zhao Hai, and said, “Do you want to use us to gather faith power?”

Zhao Hai laughed out loud, then he said, “Your Majesty, you overthink too much. Faith power? If I hadn’t met that immortal cultivator, I wouldn’t even know what it was. Even now I still couldn’t quite fathom what it is. If you arrive at the Space, I wouldn’t dare ask you to worship me.”

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and said, he still wasn’t convinced, “So there’s no other condition?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “No other reason. Your Majesty can rest assured. You should have seen the life of the people from the Ark Continent. Did I force them to worship me? Did I make a church dedicated to me in their cities?”

The Great Demon King recalled and hadn’t seen any churches in the cities they visited. He couldn’t help but nod and said, “If you promise this, then the Demons will immediately move here.”

This was Zhao Hai’s turn to be surprised. He looked confused at the Great Demon King, “Your Majesty, did you just agree? Why? Do you believe me?”

The Great Demon King smiled bitterly and said, “It’s not about whether I believe you or not. It’s about something you might not know. It’s about the Underworld.’

Zhao Hai stared, “Underworld? What’s wrong with the Underworld?”

The Great Demon King forced a smile, then he spoke……

Chapter 809: The Demon Realm and the Underworld

The Underworld was a very mysterious place, but that was in the Ark Continent. The Demon Realm actually held some understanding about the Underworld.

One can say that the relationship between the Demon Realm and the Underworld was somewhat similar to the relationship between the Ark Continent and the Divine Realm. The Demon Realm was quite like a subordinate realm of the Underworld but not really a lower realm. If the two realms were to fight, then the Demons weren’t necessarily afraid of the Underworld’s residents.

Because of this, the Demon Realm knew about the Underworld. The Underworld’s strength was very formidable. If the Demons wanted to defeat them, they needed to pay a steep price.

Most importantly, the Great Demon King knew about the Underworld’s dark mist. Although it looked common, it was actually the Underworld’s ultimate weapon.

Not only was the dark mist toxic, it can also turn dead people into undead. The people of the Demon Realm were full of vitality that they can still blow themselves up. This made it hard for Zhao Hai to turn them into undead. However, this wasn’t the same case when it came to the Underworld. Demons who blew themselves up can still be made into lich and ghosts by the dark mist. The Demons weren’t afraid of both the Divine Race and the Ark Continent, but instead, they were terrified of the Underworld. The Underworld was their complete nemesis.

And now, the Underworld had arrived in the Ark Continent. It would take a lot of time and energy in order to repel them. Most importantly, the Demons had also opened a spatial rift. Rifts can be opened easily but closing it would be difficult. If the spatial rift couldn’t be closed, then the creatures of the Underworld would arrive at the Demon Realm soon. With this in mind, the Great Demon King happily agreed to Zhao Hai’s proposition.

Upon hearing the Great Demon King, Zhao Hai finally understood what was up. He looked at the Great Demon King and said, “If Your Majesty agrees, then that would be great. You can enter the Space at any time you want, but I hope you won’t be too anxious about it. It would be best to lead me to the Demon Realm first so that we can transfer those left behind. You and your army will stay here and help me contain the Divine Race. We should also do our best to hide the fact that we had become allies.”

The Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “You really won’t forgive them?”

Zhao Hai coldly snorted and replied, “Of course. Those people are just from one of the 13 continents of the Divine Realm. But they used blood sacrifice on my people. There’s no way for me to let them go.”

The Great Demon King took a deep breath, then he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Alright, I’ll go with your arrangements. However, our matters needed to be prepared as well. I need to go back and take care of it.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “If Your Majesty need to send me information, you can use this. It can directly send word to me.” Then Zhao Hai took out a bottle. Naturally, it contained a messenger fish.

The Great Demon King looked curiously at the small fish. When Zhao Hai explained its uses, the Great Demon King couldn’t help but be surprised. He didn’t expect a thing like this to exist.

It didn’t take long for the Demon Dragon King to think how useful this thing would be during war. If this thing was present, then relaying commands would be more efficient.

Zhao Hai didn’t give the Great Demon King more time to revel on the fish as he led the Great Demon King to return to his chariot. After the two had sat down, Zhao Hai said, “Your Majesty, since we already arrived at a conclusion, then I won’t extend my stay. I have to go back and arrange things. At the same time, I’ll be dealing with the Divine Race.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Alright, I have things to take care of as well. I’ll talk to you soon.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then just as he was about to leave, the Great Demon King stopped him, “Mister, wait. I just want to ask. That sword you were stepping on, it looks just like the one I’ve seen on the immortal cultivator. What’s that about?”

When Zhao Hai heard the Great Demon King, he couldn’t help but laugh as he took his blood ghost staff. “This is not a sword. My staff has an ability to transform into many things. I just used the staff to make a flying sword. As you can see, I’m just doing it for fun.”

The Great Demon King gawked, he didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. The reason he revealed his secrets to Zhao Hai was precisely because of the flying sword. He didn’t think that it was just a prop.

After Zhao Hai bade farewell to the Great Demon King, he immediately returned to the Space. Inside, Laura and the others were waiting for him. After Zhao Hai came back, the women immediately went forward to greet him.

They were also made aware of Zhao Hai’s meeting with the Great Demon King. Because of this, they came here in order to see its progress. They just didn’t expect things to go smoothly.

After Zhao Hai sat down, Laura said, “Brother Hai, I didn’t expect the Great Demon King to accept your proposal that easily. Wasn’t it too easy?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Maybe its just because we don’t understand how important a good environment is to the Demon Race. Berry, am I correct?”

Berry herself was a Demon, so she had the most understanding about how they think among the people here. When she heard Zhao Hai, she quickly nodded and said, “It would be impossible for the people of the Ark Continent to understand just how important a good place was for us Demons. To be honest, I don’t find anything strange about how easily the Great Demon King agreed to Brother Hai’s idea. On the contrary, it would be strange if he declines. In order to live in an environment like the Space, we would do anything, even providing faith power.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he already knew that the Great Demon King would accept his proposal long before he spoke it. He could clearly see how infatuated the Great Demon King was when looking at the Space.

With the Demon Race’s matter taken care of, another chunk of worry was lifted off of Zhao Hai’s heart. Finally, he can focus on dealing with the Divine Race. At this point, Zhao Hai didn’t care about the Underworld. In any case, those low level undead would just be more manpower to him.

The Underworld was just too big compared to the Ark Continent and only low level undead were could be seen on the parts that were covered with the dark mist. In other words, the Ark Continent was just too small that stronger undead had yet to take notice.

Even so, the Underworld had already occupied the Northern Icefield as well as a third of the Beastmen Prairie.

After discussing the Demons with Laura and the others, Zhao Hai changed the topic to the Divine Race. Zhao Hai looked at the current progress of the Divine Race and discovered that they have gone further than what he expected.

Zhao Hai turned to Lizzy and said, “Lizzy, what’s happened? How could the Divine Race advance this fast? Haven’t you controlled their speed?”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “I did. However, I didn’t slow them too much. It would be best for us if they arrive at the Accra Mountains sooner. We can block them there while dispatching troops towards the Radiant Empire. Once they turn back to help, then we’ll hit them seriously. By the time they reach the Empire, they should have lost about 50% of their total numbers.”

Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy as he took a deep breath. Then he turned to Laura and said, “Laura, is it just me or Lizzy has become more and more evil as time passed. I’m a bit afraid now.”

Laura giggled. Lizzy didn’t let this go, she went to Zhao Hai and twisted his side. Megan turned her eyes and said, “We learned from you. You’re the most evil one here!”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he sported an angry look and said, “Alright, if I’m evil, then I will show you how bad I can be!” Then he grabbed Megan and threw her over his shoulder as he went inside a room. Laura and the others just giggled, nobody followed.

Laura and the others weren’t jealous, Zhao Hai had treated each of them fairly. Moreover, he was very fond of them. Whatever they wanted to do, Zhao Hai would certainly allow them. If they want something, then Zhao Hai would provide.

There were some people who say that when one’s love becomes too deep, it could make a person disregard their own gains and losses just to be with someone they love. Laura and the others were currently feeling this right now. They only wanted to make Zhao Hai happy, anything else was irrelevant.

Zhao Hai also felt the same for them. Although he was quite busy, his wives were always on his mind. At this point, they were even more important to him compared to the Buda Clan.

Zhao Hai was not the type to pursue longevity, status, or power, becoming a cold and unfeeling person. In his mind, if a person’s most basic feelings were gone, then even if one becomes a god or a fairy or an immortal, what use would life be? What would be the difference between you and a piece of rock? A rock lying there, if one wouldn’t touch it, then it would stay there forever. However, would you envy that rock? No, nobody would envy that rock. It’s because you’re alive, and that was a rock! People who were cold and unfeeling were like this rock, completely lifeless and bland.

Chapter 810: An Astute Great Demon King

The Third Prince was feeling very proud. He’s currently running free in the Ark Continent. The harassment attacks were simply useless  to his army. The Third Prince felt an overwhelming sense of power, he felt like a wargod.

While the Third Prince was feeling good, Thunder Yun’s face was quite ugly to behold. He was currently getting more and more worried. He didn’t know what Zhao Hai was planning. Why would he push them onward? There was surely some plot happening.

As a battlefield veteran, Thunder Yun knew that formidable enemies wouldn’t oversee opportunities to make a move. But at present, he couldn’t understand Zhao Hai’s actions.

Although he had received word about the Ark Continent’s migration, he didn’t care too much about it. In Thunder Yun’s mind, the residents of the continent had nowhere else to go to.

They came from the Ark Continent’s upper Realm, so where would the Ark Continent move? Compared to the Ark Continent, the Divine Realm was more familiar about the planes around it. The Divine Race knew very well that there was no other plane that can accept the Ark Continent’s residents. Therefore, Thunder Yun only gave that report a glance before ignoring it.

In addition to ignoring the report, Thunder Yun was also very disappointed with the enemies that were left. He didn’t understand why the enemy, who had harassed them since the start, would send such out such an information.

Actually, nobody can blame Thunder Yun. In the end, he was still from the Divine Race. They knew too much about the planes around them. Additionally, their pride was deeply ingrained in their bones. They didn’t put Zhao Hai in their eyes, even after suffering such huge losses under his hand.

Since they arrived, they haven’t looked at Zhao Hai as their equal. If they did, then Zhao Hai would’ve had given more problems in dealing with their invasion.

But although Thunder Yun was arrogant, he still had some sense in him to not disregard Zhao Hai. Because of this, he was currently thinking what Zhao Hai was planning. The more he thought about it, the more worried he got. And the more worried he got, the less clear his mind would be. It was a vicious cycle.

At this point, Thunder Yun was hoping for Fei’er to come back and bring him good news. When that happens, he can then make plans accordingly.

However, Fei’er was yet to arrive. Thunder Yun also knew that Fei’er wouldn’t be able to get information this quickly, but he still couldn’t help but worry.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about what Thunder Yun was thinking, he was currently preparing for their attack on the Radiant Empire. At the same time, they were also positioning their people in the Accra Mountains. In fact, Zhao Hai doesn’t need to arrange people in the Accra Mountains, but he still did it since he has nothing else to do right now.

Aside from the Divine Race, Zhao Hai was also paying close attention to the Demon Race. After the Great Demon King arrived back at the army, he immediately issued a retreat. This made Zhao Hai relieved, now he only needed to wait for the message from the Great Demon King.

The Great Demon King was also dealing with this matter with importance. Just like Berry said, the Demon Race’s desire for a better environment was far beyond what Zhao Hai can comprehend.

Although the Demons couldn’t understand the Great Demon King’s intent, they still acquiesced due to their faith towards their king. The army was now going back to Demon City.

When they returned to Demon City, the Great Demon King immediately called all the Demon leaders to his room. Before long, everyone was present inside the residence.

After the group sat down, the Great Demon King scanned everyone present before he said, “I went to see Zhao Hai and had a long chat with him.”

This wasn’t a secret. Almost everyone present here were wondering why the Great Demon King stated something obvious.

Then the Great Demon King continued, “I think everyone already knew about the Ark Continent’s mass migration. At that time, I couldn’t make heads about the report, I don’t know whether it was true or not. But after meeting Zhao Hai, I became certain that the information was true.”

Upon hearing the Great Demon King, the room immediately hummed into action. This news shocked them. The mass migration of the entire Ark Continent was too huge to imagine.

The Demon Dragon King looked at the others before he stood up and said, “Your Majesty, the news being true is fine, but why did Zhao Hai confirm it?”

The Great Demon King nodded and replied, “Besides this information, Zhao Hai also told me another thing. And this is important for us. Zhao Hai told me that in the Ark Continent’s Northern Icefield, a spatial rift appeared. The this spatial rift is connected to the Underworld!

This information was akin to a bomb exploding in the minds of those present. They didn’t expect the Ark Continent to be connected to the Underworld.

The Demons dreaded the Underworld. For a connection to the Underworld to appear in the Ark Continent, this wasn’t good news for the Demon Race.

The Demon Dragon King’s expression was ugly to behold, he said, “Your Majesty, can you confirm this news?”

Although the Demon Dragon King held great trust towards the Great Demon King, this information was just too shocking, they needed concrete evidence in order to prove it.

The Great Demon King shook his head and said, “I don’t know whether this is true or not. But confirming this shouldn’t be difficult. At this point, nobody is left in the Ark Continent. So there shouldn’t be any danger in sending the Demon Vulture Division to check it out. With their speed, they should be able to quickly confirm the news.” The Demon Dragon King held a heavy expression. He knew that if this information was true, then with the Demon Realm being connected to the Ark Continent, the Underworld would soon be crawling towards them.

The Demon Dragon King didn’t delay for a minute as he immediately arranged for some scouts to check the situation. Those inside the hall were still thinking about the report, none of them spoke out.

After the Demon Dragon King was done, the Great Demon King looked at him and said, “Have you arranged it? How long will they take?”

The Demon Dragon King immediately answered, “Your Majesty, they should come back the day after tomorrow. Although they wouldn’t stop midway, the distance was just too far for them to make it in one go.”

The Great Demon King nodded, then he turned his head towards the others and said, “Go back to your camps. We need to wait for news before I can make a decision. This matter is very important for our Demon Race. Demon Dragon, you stay. Everyone else can leave.” Then after that, everyone except the Demon Dragon King stood up and gave a salute to the Great King before leaving. Before long, footsteps could be heard outside and it faded into silence.

When nobody else was left, the Great Demon King turned to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Actually, I just had you arrange the scouts so that the others can see it. I believe Zhao Hai wouldn’t lie to me. Also, there is one thing left to tell you.”

The Demon Dragon King replied, “I guessed that as well. Your Majesty, please tell.”

Then the Great Demon King told the Demon Dragon King about everything he talked with Zhao Hai. The Demon Dragon King already knew small things about Lu Wei. When the Great Demon King did his investigations, the Demon Dragon King was present. Therefore, the Demon Dragon King didn’t show too much surprise by the news.

After the Great Demon King finished his story, the Demon Dragon King said, “Your Majesty, you mean to tell me that we can move to Zhao Hai’s place later on? Is the place really that great?” The Great Demon King was showing how infatuated he was with the place, then he replied, “It’s great, very great. It’s much better than you can imagine, much better than the Ark Continent. I saw the people from the Ark Continent there as well. Zhao Hai made a place that looked just like the continent. I became quite envious when I saw them.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “Your Majesty’s decision is surely correct. However, we need to take care of this matter delicately. We don’t want an accident to happen in the process.”

The Great Demon King nodded, “I’m also worried about this point. Because of this, we need to make something up, I need you help with this. The days that the Demons would come out of misery has come.”

At this point, the Demon Dragon King actually frowned, “Your Majesty, if Zhao Hai is that powerful, then if we enter the Space, how could we assure our safety? We don’t have any leverage for him to take care of us.”

The Great Demon King gave a faint smile and said, “Zhao Hai is strong, yes, but it’s not like he wouldn’t get any advantage after taking us in. Don’t forget about that thing called faith power. With Zhao Hai’s strength, he would surely ascend to the immortal cultivator realm in the future. This faith power should be very useful to him. As long as we enter the Space and give him faith power, i believe Zhao Hai wouldn’t treat us unfairly.”

When he heard the Great Demon King, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but frown once more, he said, “Your Majesty, if we do that, then what would be the difference to our current situation?” The Great Demon King immediately replied, “You fool, naturally there are differences. What has that immortal cultivator given us? Our Demon Race had always been living in the Demon Realm, nothing has changed. Also, now that the Underworld appeared, the Demon Realm is placed in peril. Once we move to the Space, then we don’t have to worry about those things anymore. We can just give Zhao Hai faith power in exchange for a much better life. In any case, faith power is completely useless to people like us.”

Chapter 811: Showing A Movie?

When the Demon Dragon King heard what the Great Demon King said, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. But then, he finally understood what the Great Demon King meant. Just as what the Great Demon King said, the Demon God was just a fake, feeding off of the Demon Race’s faith power. Moreover, the Demon God hadn’t given them benefits in exchange for the faith.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai was providing them with a great place to live in, something much better compared to the Demon Realm. At the same time, Zhao Hai was a principled person. If they offer him their faith power, he certainly wouldn’t treat them unfairly.

And most importantly, the Underworld had come creeping in. If they don’t enter Zhao Hai’s Space, then the Underworld would sooner or later clash with the Demon Realm, causing colossal losses to the Demon Race. If they enter the Space, then they would no longer worry about this crisis. For the Demons this was a very huge development.

The more the Demon Dragon King thought about it, the more he thought that it was a good deal. He turned to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, I also think that this is great for us. We should start our preparations. How does Your Majesty plan to proceed?”

The Great Demon King said, “I’ll think about it after the Demon Vulture comes back with information. You take charge here first as I return back to the Demon Realm and arrange for the relocation. In any case, those left back in the Demon Realm had nothing else to do. You must pay attention and coordinate with Zhao Hai to deal with the Divine Race. Zhao Hai said that he wouldn’t let the Divine Race off, we’ll help him to prove our sincerity.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, “i can do it. But we have clashed with Zhao Hai several times in the past. Those with enmity might find it hard to accept it. Your Majesty need to take care of it.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “I’ll take care of that. As long as they enter the Space, that enmity should disappear into thin air.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, and after discussing further details, he asked to be excused. On the other hand, the Great Demon King looked at the Demons inside the Ark Continent before sighing in relief.

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware about any of these, however, he was able to see Demon Vultures. He didn’t care about it and just had them look at the Underworld’s arrival. In any case, this would prove that he wasn’t lying, he doesn’t want any bad impressions to stick to him.

Zhao Hai was now ready to confront the Third Prince. It has already been four days after the Third Prince left the Radiant Empire. And in four days, they unexpectedly flew quickly towards the Accra Mountains. One must say that their speed was really quick.

In order for the Divine Race’s advance to be quicker, Zhao Hai stopped the harassment. Although their current arrangement for the harassment had no damage to the Divine Race army, it still slowed them down. Zhao Hai stopped so that their speed would be faster.

Thunder Yun was quite uneasy and had repeatedly persuaded the Third Prince to slow down, but unfortunately for him, the Third Prince was at the peak of his ecstacy. The Third Prince had completely convinced himself that he was a wargod. His arrival actually pushed the Ark Continent’s residents back. Therefore, how could Thunder Yun stop the Third Prince?

While he continued his futile attempts to stop their advance, Thunder Yun also did a good job as the rear army commander. He also added more people to guard their supply line. He never did think that Zhao Hai would plan to attack the Radiant Empire.

The Divine Race had fought in many battles and in many planes, and never did they need to worry about their base being attacked, nobody dared to do so. It was because of this that Thunder Yun made a fatal mistake.

While the army advanced, Thunder Yun sat on his mount, frowning. At this time, Cloud Ying arrived by his side, he was also frowning as he said, “General, what is Zhao Hai planning? Where are the Ark Continent’s soldier? Have they been defeated by the Demons? Otherwise, how come nobody faced us?”

Thunder Yun was also confused, “I also don’t know. But Zhao Hai had always given me a feeling of someone who isn’t easily defeated. Otherwise, he would have already fallen long ago. Go back and inform everyone to prepare for a fight. Zhao Hai is surely planning something big.”

Cloud Ying nodded before he turned around and left. When Cloud Ying left, Thunder Yun took out a beast skin scroll from his chest. On this scroll was the map of the Buddha Empire. This was something he acquired in the Radiant Empire before.

After looking at the map, Thunder Yun muttered, “We’re quickly approaching Accra Mountains. Did Zhao Hai sacrifice the Buddha Empire? He wouldn’t.”

As he was thinking about this, the Third Prince’s front army was now able to see the Accra Mountains. The Third Prince was currently sitting inside his sword carriage. The door of the carriage was opened, how was the Third Prince drinking wine on his table. He was alone, looking very free and unfettered.

At this time, a cavalry soldier arrived by his side and said, “Your Highness, the scouts sent a report over. The Ark Continent had made a very solid defense line along the Accra Mountains. Undead creatures were stood above the fortifications, it seems like they are preparing to stop us there.”

The Third Prince stared before he laughed and said, “These cowardly Ark Continent people had finally decided to face us. Send this order, have the army accelerate, and break through the Accra Mountains in one go. I want to see where these Ark Continent residents hid themselves.”

The cavalry soldier nodded before he passed the order down. Before long, the army’s speed quickened as they dashed towards Accra Mountains.

These days, the Divine Race hadn’t met a decent attack. This allowed them to feel proud. At this point, they were completely disregarding the people from the Ark Continent.

In their view, this line of defense would be easily broken through. All the proud Divine Race soldiers were rushing forward, turning their formation a bit messy.

Zhao Hai was currently inside the Space, looking at the action made by the Divine Race. He turned his head to Lizzy and said, “These fellows are too impatient, they want to die as soon as possible. Lizzy, is everything prepared?”

Lizzy smiled faintly and said, “Big Brother Hai, rest assured, everything is going according to plan. Look.” Then Zhao Hai looked back at the monitor and saw a different angle to the operation.

Along the entire defense line were more than 2000 magic cannons with enough crystal stones to power them. There were also blood lightning javelins present. All of these were prepared in order to deal a heavy blow to the Divine Race.

At this time, in the Ark Space, while people were doing their own thing a voice was suddenly heard in the sky, “Brothers and Sisters from the Ark Continent, if you want to see Mister Zhao Hai’s undead battle the Divine Race, then you can go to the center of your city. There, you can see the whole battle.”

The voice disappeared after sounding out three times. After the people recovered from their blank stares, they immediately rushed over to their respective city squares. Most of them had only heard about the Divine Race. and now they were able to see them battle against the undead. Naturally, all of them were rushing over to spectate.

When the people had arrived in the city square, a transparent light ball suddenly appeared and then stretched into a rectangle shape. This bright rectangle slowly rose up before it stopped.

The bright rectangle showed the situation in the Accra Mountains. There were Undead and magic cannons everywhere.

At this time, the voice came once more, “In the past few days, the Divine Race reinforcements from the Radiant Empire had entered the Buddha Empire. At that time, Mister Zhao Hai didn’t face them in battle, instead, he decided to prepared to meet them in the Accra Mountains. He dragged the army here so that his undead cavalry could attack the Radiant Empire. As you can see, the Divine Race army had come to attack the Accra Mountain.”

This rectangular display was very big, with each side at least ten meters long.

The image slowly panned across the Accra Mountains, showing the whole defensive line to everyone. Then the voice came, “This is the defensive line we’ve built to block the advance of the Divine Race.” This description elicited surprise in the crowd.

The Accra Mountain’s defensive line looked like giant dragon that was lying down, once couldn’t describe how magnificent it looked. At times, the voice would describe certain aspects of the defense as exclamation sounded out here and there.

At this time, the image changed as it panned to the distant horizon. On the image, figures were getting more and more. Before long, the crowd finally saw that these figures were in fact Divine Race soldiers.

These soldiers were full silver body armor while they held their weapons in their hands. They were in a formation as they charged towards the Accra Mountains. The imposing manner of the enemy army caused those watching to be speechless.

The scene of the Divine Race was indeed terrifying. When commoners who haven’t seen the battlefield before saw this scene, they were frightened. It was at this point they realized that Zhao Hai had been fighting this army. Their sense of gratitude towards Zhao Hai had also increased.

At this time, the screen showed a red and white lights. These lights went straight towards the Divine Race army. When the red light hit the soldiers, a huge explosion appeared. In every corner of the Divine Race army, these same explosions happen, causing the Divine Race’s formation to be in turmoil.

On the other hand, the white lights froze the Divine Race soldiers. Then as they fell to the ground, they shattered into tiny pieces. Upon seeing the damages caused by the red and white lights, the crowd inside the Ark Space had become breathless.

Chapter 812: The Shocked Third Prince

The Third Prince was blankly looking out front. His hand slowly losing grip on his wine glass. The wine glass finally fell into the table and shattered. But even so, the Third Prince didn’t notice it, his hand was still lifted, as though it still held the glass.

In the Third Prince’s mind, the Accra Mountains should be as easy to break as paper. As long as they push one, then they would definitely break through. But now, it was obvious that they had underestimated the strength of the Ark Continent.

The red and white light came too fast that most of the Divine Race soldiers didn’t even have the time to do protective measures. Sure enough, they were immediately killed.

And that wasn’t the only thing, there were also javelins flying out of the defensive line. Naturally, these javelins weren’t thrown by people, they were fired using ballistas.

There were more ballistas compared to magic cannons in the defense line. This was because ballistas were easier to make than magic cannons. Moreover, people of the continent were using it more. Thus, there were more ballistas already made compared to magic cannons.

In the past, ballistas deal no damage to the Divine Race. Their arrows were simply useless against the Divine Race’s defense.

But now that the blood lightning javelins were made, these ballistas gained their deadly reputation once more. One must know that the ballistas from the Ark Continent were operated differently compared to those found on Earth. What Zhao Hai saw before were armed with one arrow and were pulled by about four to five people, it was quite troublesome to manage.

However, in the Ark Continent, people practice battle qi and magic. This made it possible for one person to use one ballista. Moreover, these ballistas don’t only fire one arrow, they can launch five and it won’t even affect the firing distance.

Since Zhao Hai’s undead were 9th ranks, operating a ballista for them would be extremely easy. In addition to firing five ammunitions, these ammunitions were all blood lightning javelins. Each voller packed an extremely terrifying might.

The DIvine Race soldiers who were about to flood the Accra Mountains were temporarily stunned by the attacks coming from the magic cannons and the ballistas. They can’t help it, the firepower as well as the speed was something they haven’t seen before.

These Divine Race soldiers were too stunned that many of them forgot to establish their Domains. They seem to just be standing there, accepting the baptism of fire.

It was only after some time that they had recovered. But at that point, a round of attacks had already been done. These attacks obliterated ten thousand people, most of them killed by the explosions made by the blood lightning javelins.

At this time, the Third Prince had also recovered. His face was pale as he loudly shouted, “Retreat, retreat, quickly! Everyone retreat! Get away from their firing distance!”

The Third Prince’s frantic response was clearly seen by the people from the Ark Space. The explosions on the battlefield had numbed their hearing. This made those who haven’t experienced it before have an overwhelmed expression.

Needless to say, it would only take one look to see that the Third Prince was an important person in the Divine Race Army. At this moment, a voice came, “The person you see on the screen right now is the Third Prince of the Divine Race. He’s currently the commander of the entire Divine Race Army.”

People had gradually been used to this voice. They really didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s place to be this magical. Not only could they see the battle outside, they could even hear the sound and have someone provide them with context.

When the Divine Race army slowly retreated and reformed their army, the people from the Ark Space felt relief. Then gasps of shock echoed out from the crowd.

This was the first time that they’ve witnessed a fight in the battlefield this detailed. The intensity of the clash had exceeded their imagination. But no matter what, since Zhao Hai had repelled the Divine Race army, all of them were quite glad.

On the other hand, the Divine Race were feeling the exact opposite The Third Prince looked at the Accra Mountain’s direction before he roared towards his subordinates, “What was that!? Can someone tell me? What just happened!? How could their attacks be that strong?!”

Nobody present dared to speak. In fact, these people were also dumbfounded. The attacks of the Ark Continent was leagues higher than the attacks made from the previous days. Compared to this attack, the attacks days ago was just like a kid’s prank.

The Third Prince kicked his table out of the sword carriage. Then with blood red eyes he turned to a cavalry soldier beside him and said, “Go and get me Thunder Yun. I want to ask him how all of this happened.” The cavalry soldier nodded before he turned around and left.

Before long, Thunder Yun arrived by the sword carriage, he gave a bow to the Third Prince and said, “Your Highness, might I know why you have called this lowly official over?”

The Third Prince looked at Thunder Yun’s expression and felt that he was being ridiculed. His face couldn’t help but turn ugly, but since he needed to ask something, he chose to refrain from scolding Thunder Yun. He said, “Thunder Yun, I want to know why the Ark Continent’s attacks suddenly became strong. What is this about?”

Thunder Yun looked at the Third Prince and then deeply sighed before giving a reply, “Your Highness, today’s attacks are the normal attacks of the Ark Continent. This lowly official hadn’t met those weak attacks in the past few days. If the Ark Continent had that kind of attack, then this one should’ve already conquered it long time ago.”

Thunder Yun was telling the truth, but to the Third Prince, it sounded as if he was being scolded. It looks like Thunder Yun was ridiculing his actions.

The Third Prince’s eyes turned red with anger as he frantically shouted at Thunder Yun, “Get lost! Take your face away from here! From now on, I don’t want to see your face!”

Thunder Yun’s expression darkened, he gave a small snort before he turned around and left. Thunder Yun was a decorated War General. His merits in the battlefield was too many that even the Taurus King would treat him politely. But now, this talentless Prince actually dared to shout at him.

The Third Prince looked at Thunder Yun’s departing back as he clenched his jaws to the point that blue veins were starting to appear on his forehead. He turned towards his people and roared, “Send the order, attack the enemy. I don’t believe that the Divine Race would be stopped by a measy mountain range. Everybody attack immediately! Attack!”

Along with the Third Prince command, the Divine Race army immediately started to attack the Accra Mountain. At the same time, the defenders of the Accra Mountains were also peppering the attacking Divine Race soldiers.

And due to the Third Prince’s anger, he had failed to notice something peculiar. It can be seen that the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus Cavalries weren’t doing their best. At the same time, the defenses of the Ark Continent were also only sending them the minimum amount of attacks. It looked like the three were in a tacit understanding.

The Third Prince didn’t take notice of this as he focused on ordering his army to go all out. The Accra Mountain’s defense line was also something not to be trifled with. The defense’s firepower was fierce, it had unexpectedly suppressed the advancing Divine Race.

When Thunder Yun went back to his rear army, Cloud Ying came to him and said, “General, what did the Third Prince call you for? Is the front army’s attack not doing so well?”

Thunder Yun snorted but didn’t reply, instead he closed his eyes. When Cloud Ying saw Thunder Yun’s action, his mind couldn’t help but turn blank. Then he turned to the guard that accompanied Thunder Yun and asked him in a low voice about what happened.

The guard told him what occured after Thunder Yun and the Third Prince met. When Cloud Ying heard this, his complexion changed as he turned to Thunder Yun and said, “General, this is going too far! What status did you have? Even His Majesty the King would treat you politely. How could you let the Third Prince just scold you?”

Thunder Yun kept closing his eyes and kept silent. Cloud Ying took a deep breath before he added, “General, what is the Ark Continent planning to do? They were weakly attacking in the past few days, but now they actually turned serious.”

Thunder Yun was still closing his eyes refusing to speak. Upon seeing Thunder Yun being unresponsive, Cloud Ying decided to turn silent. It was at this time that Silver Shuke and the others came. And just as the newcomers were about to open their mouths, they were stopped by Cloud Ying. Then Cloud Ying told them about what happened with the Third Prince. Naturally, Silver Shuke and the others also became angry.

Silver Shuke and the others had fought by Thunder Yun’s side for a long time. Their respect for Thunder Yun was quite high, even higher compared to their regard for the King. For a trivial Third Prince to scold their general, it was no wonder that they were enraged.

However, these people didn’t express their anger loudly. They knew that Thunder Yun was keeping silent because he was thinking hard about the situation.

Silver Shuke decided to stay quiet. At this point, Silver Shuke turned to Cloud Ying and said, “Cloud Ying, how come the Ark Continent suddenly went strong once more after attacking weakly in the past few days?”

Cloud Ying frowned and said, “I don’t know. Their previous tactic was quite a headache, so it should have also worked this time, but they didn’t use it. Instead, they fortified the Accra Mountains. It’s quite confusing, if this is what they’ve done, then it can only be said that they were intending to drag us here.”

It was at this point that Thunder Yun’s eyes opened up, his complexion paled as he said, “Not good! Zhao Hai lured us in to restrain us here. He’s going to attack the Radiant Empire!”

As soon as everyone present heard this, their complexion couldn’t help but pale as well. Their expression showed their disbelief, then Silver Shuke said, “How is that possible? Is Zhao Hai so brave that he would dare attack our main camp?”

Chapter 813: Anguish

Thunder Yun’s expression was ugly as he said, “There’s no reason not to. Don’t forget, Zhao Hai’s overall strength isn’t that worse compared to us. Moreover, Zhao Hai is a bold person. We brought a lot of our soldiers this time and left too little. If Zhao Hai wanted to attack the Radiant Empire at this time, then it would surely be dangerous for us.’

The group’s expression was quite ugly as well. They really hadn’t thought of the possibility of Zhao Hai attacking the Radiant Empire. They thought Zhao Hai wouldn’t have enough courage to do so.

However, after Thunder Yun presented his case, they were finally convinced of the possibility that Zhao Hai would attack the Radiant Empire. This result wasn’t what they want.

Thunder Yun immediately said, “Quick, have someone be sent back to the Radiant Empire to see the situation. I’ll immediately go and see the Third Prince. We need to withdraw the troops immediately.” Cloud Ying and the others complied before they turned around and left. At the same time, Thunder Yun directly flew towards the sword carriage. He didn’t care about the the Third Prince’s anger right now. The Radiant Empire was currently in peril.

However, just before Thunder Yun reached the carriage, he was blocked off by the cavalry soldiers. Thunder Yun’s expression turned ugly after seeing the blocking, he immediately said, “Give way, I need to see His Highness. I have an important matter to tell him.” The cavalry soldier disregarded his words and said with no emotion, “We’ll be unfair to General Thunder Yun. His Highness gave us an order to block you from seeing him. Please turn back.”

Thunder Yun roared, “Give way. I want to see the Third Prince. It’s related to the Divine Race army’s safety. Don’t blame me if you still dare to block.” The cavalry soldiers were still expressionless, “General Thunder Yun, please turn back. His Majesty doesn’t want to see you.”

Thunder Yun roared as he began to charge forward. But at this time, the cavalry soldiers actually held their spears and pointed at him.

Thunder Yun was shocked when he saw this, his face was flushed with red as he said, “You bastards, what are you doing? Are you planning a revolt?” The Cavalry disdainfully replied, “General Thunder Yun, we are responsible for His Majesty’s security. His Majesty doesn’t want to see you right now. For His Majesty’s security, we have no other choice but to block you. If you still dare to rush forward, then we will have to attack.”

Thunder Yun’s face was now pale white, he knew that the cavalry soldier wasn’t bluffing. They were special troops that answer only to the Taurus King. Even if those of higher status than Thunder Yun were present, these cavalry soldiers still wouldn’t bat an eye.”

Thunder Yun let out a long breath as he said, “Then I would have to ask you to tell His Majesty that I have an important report to tell. This concerns the safety of the Ark Continent’s conquest.” Naturally, the cavalry soldier was still aware of who Thunder Yun was, he hesitated for a moment before turning back to give a report. Before long, the cavalry soldier came back with a somewhat pale expression. He looked at Thunder Yun and said, “General, His Majesty said that he doesn’t want to see you. He wanted you to turn back. Also, the General needs to hand over his command token. By the order of His Highness, General Thunder Yun is no longer allowed to give command to any soldier in the Divine Race army.” Thunder Yun stared, color drained from his face. Then he looked straight at the cavalry soldier and said, “What did you say?”

The soldier said it once more, “The Third Prince asks the General to hand over his command token. Without any word from the Third Prince, the rear army isn’t allowed to make a move.”

Thunder Yun angrily glared at the cavalry soldier and said, “You bastards! Do you know what you are doing? Do you know the situation we are currently facing? Let me through, I need to see His Majesty.”

The cavalry soldier replied, “Please hand the command token over. Otherwise, we would be forced to make a move.”

Thunder Yun roared, he was planning to rush out. He knew that going forward at this time would be courting death. So instead, he would quickly go back to his army and immediately lead them to return towards the Radiant Empire.

But unfortunately, Thunder Yun wasn’t given the chance. The cavalry soldiers already knew about his plan. Before long other soldiers came in and blocked Thunder Yun’s retreat. Thunder Yun wielded his wooden totem as he struggled to break away from the encirclement.

At this time, Thunder Yun suddenly felt an ominous air behind him. Luckily for him, his wooden totem was quick to block the incoming attack. But even so, the attack was quite heavy, Thunder Yun was shaken by the impact, blood started to flow.

But while he was disoriented by the attack, another spear attack came from behind him. This time, Thunder Yun was unable to block it, and establishing his Domain was already too late. The blunt attack from behind had caused Thunder Yun to lose consciousness.

Behind him was the cavalry soldier who he spoke to. This man was a captain of the division, and he had formidable God-rank strength as well. Because of this, Thunder Yun was rendered unconscious by his attack.

After Thunder Yun was knocked down, the captain waved his hand and immediately two cavalry soldiers held Thunder Yun up. The captain took Thunder Yun’s command token away before sending him back to his army.

The cavalry captain also sent the Third Prince’s order along with Thunder Yun. He waved his hand to the two cavalry soldiers before he turned and looked at the war in front.

The Divine Race’s state in the battle was very disadvantageous. They had already been pushed on several times, but to no avail. They weren’t even able to come close to the defensive line. Each wave of attacks from the magic cannons and javelins would reap thousands of soldier’s lives.

The Third Prince had never expected their losses to be this much. However, this only made him more determined to push through the Accra Mountains. He decided that once they take the Accra Mountains, they would kill every single Ark Continent resident they would see. Not even chickens and dogs would survive.

At this time, on the rear army, the two cavalry soldiers carrying Thunder Yun had delivered him to his army. This caused the rear army to go into an uproar. Thunder Yun’s status in this army was very high. Thunder Yun just went to see the Third Prince, but now he came back unconscious.

Cloud Ying and the others had ugly expressions on their faces as they surrounded the two cavalry soldiers. Cloud Yin looked at the fainted Thunder Yun and angrily said, “What is going on? Who dared to hit the General?”

The two cavalry soldiers were fearless. With a loud and deep voice, they declared, “The Third Prince has confiscated General Thunder Yun’s command token. Not only did General Thunder Yun neglect the order, he also tried to rebel. Therefore, the Third Prince’s guards had no choice but to knock him unconscious. Additionally, without the Third Prince’s order, the rear army cannot take independent action. Martial Law has been established!” Then after the two said that, they rode their mounts as they dropped Thunder Yun’s body mid air.

Although the soldiers in the surroundings were angry, they also knew of the status of these two people. Therefore, nobody dared to block them, they were allowed passage as they left.

Cloud Yin and the others looked at the departing backs of the cavalry soldiers with blood red eyes. Cloud Ying quickly went to Thunder Yun and slowly guided his body down to the ground. Cloud Ying held Thunder Yun and called out, “General? General, wake up!”

Thunder Yun fainted due to a shallow force, so when Cloud Ying called out, he immediately recovered his senses. He turned to look at Cloud Ying before looking for the command token. Thunder Yun’s face turned beet red  when he noticed that the token was gone. He couldn’t help but shout, “He wants to kill the Divine Race!!” After saying that, Thunder Yun fainted once more due to excessive anger.

Cloud Ying and the others were very frightened. Cloud Ying immediately took a piece of wet cloth and wiped the sweat away from Thunder Yun’s face.

After some time, Thunder Yun woke up and looked at the clouds in the sky as he said, “Cloud Ying, have everyone help the Third Prince in breaking through the Accra Mountains. As long as we can break their defensive line, we can quickly seize the entire continent. At that point, Zhao Hai would certainly stop being a threat to us.”

Cloud Ying looked at Thunder Yun and said, “General, your wound?”

Thunder Yun shook his head and said, “I’ll be fine. Go and prepare the troops.” Cloud Ying complied, then he turned around and left. Thunder Yun slowly sat down and casted light element magic on his body. Then he stood up and looked at the battlefield in the distance, with a cold voice he said, “Zhao Hai, good. You’re really daring. You think you can block the Divine Race army with your defensive line?”

Thunder Yun understood that there was no time left for them to turn back and return to the Radiant Empire. Moreover, Zhao Hai would surely not let them retreat easily. Because of this, Thunder Yun decided to break the Accra Mountains’ defensive line and then use the Ark Continent’s residents as a threat towards Zhao Hai.

Up until now, Thunder Yun still didn’t believe that Zhao Hai had moved. For him, it was a totally impossible thing. Because of this, although the Third Prince had taken his command token, Thunder Yun thought of another way. That was to break through the Accra Mountains in the quickest time. Then they would kill the Ark Continent’s residents so that Zhao Hai would be the one to turn back.

If Zhao Hai doesn’t turn back to help his people, then they can also use the Ark Continent’s residents as a bargaining chip to negotiate with Zhao Hai.

Thunder Yun was clear that if Zhao Hai doesn’t take care of the people of the Ark Continent, then his position would be in trouble. When Zhao Hai is faced with this situation, he would surely have a hard time going forward with his plans.

Because of this thought, Thunder Yun shifted to another gear. He had Cloud Ying lead the troops to support the Third Prince.

Thunder Yun also knew that with the losses the Third Prince had incurred, he would surely ask for reinforcement soon. If no reinforcements come, then breaking through the defensive line would be slower, and Thunder Yun wouldn’t want that.

In the past, Thunder Yun certainly wouldn’t attack the Accra Mountains with this method. But now, he had no other choice. If they cannot break through, then the Radiant Empire would be placed in peril.

Chapter 814: Heart of Earth Fire

Zhao Hai was also aware of Thunder Yun’s plan, but he wasn’t worried even for a bit. The defenses of the Accra Mountains has been arranged for a long time. Although the people of the Ark continent had moved, the defenses still stayed there. As long as an army was there to operate it, then there would be no problem.

At this time, Zhao Hai was directing his undead to attack the Radiant Empire. When Thunder Yun went on with his action, there were no concealment magics applied, so Zhao Hai was able to witness all of it.

The changes to Thunder Yun’s plan went along with what Zhao Hai wanted. The longer the Divine Race engages in battle, the better it would be for Zhao Hai.

The undead were already prepared to attack the Radiant Empire. They had also planned the best direction their attack would come from.

There were several places to choose from, but in the end, Zhao Hai chose to attack from the sea.

The Radiant Church was originally the Ocean Waves Dynasty, a nation surrounded by water on three sides and by the Buddha Empire on one. It can be said that compared to land attacks, it would be much better to approach by sea.

Many of Zhao Hai’s undead were marine beasts. Moreover, moving by sea was more convenient compared to land.

Besides this reason, Zhao Hai also wanted to visit Inferno Island to take a look. Inferno Island was one of the Ark Continents Five Forbidden Places. It was some distance away from the shore and was extremely hot. It was also densely covered with volcanoes that housed special fire magic beasts and plants. Moreover, the island also had a special lifeform, Flame Demons!

These Flame Demons were like the Flame Demons found in the Demon Realm. They were advanced magic beasts that didn’t fear fire as it was their means of sustenance.

Countless experts of the Ark Continent ended up having the island as their cemetery. There were countless explorers who went there and never came back.

But the main reason why Zhao Hai wanted to visit the island was to try and get some fire element crystals.

In the war against the Divine Race, fire element crystals were the most convenient to use. Since the northern icefield had an abundant number of ice crystals, Zhao Hai doesn’t believe that Inferno Island wouldn’t have some.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to visit the island after he returned from the Northern Icefield. However, he didn’t expect that a lot of things would happen. In the end, his plan needed to be placed on the side.

Now, Zhao Hai wanted to use this opportunity to take a look at Inferno Island. Then after he dealt with the Divine Race, Zhao Hai would talk with the Great Demon King.

Zhao Hai took his blood ghost staff out and had it fly towards the direction of Inferno Island. They appeared at sea, so the island wasn’t that far off.

The reason they weren’t able to move that fast was because they needed to go around the Radiant Empire while also taking care not to be discovered by the Divine Race. The Divine Race were quite sensitive, any small disturbance would immediately urge them to take action.

Zhao Hai was currently looking at the blood ghost staff. Lizzy and Megan were taking charge of the battle with the Divine Race, so Zhao Hai had the opportunity to pay attention to other things.

The staff’s range was limited, therefore Zhao Hai didn’t wait as he turned to Lizzy and Megan and said, “I’ll be heading out, I’ll leave the battle to you two.”

Lizzy and Megan just gave a nod, they didn’t even take their eyes off of the monitor. After seeing their reaction, Zhao Hai smiled faintly before his body flashed out of the Space. At this time, the staff transformed into a flying sword and was stepped on by Zhao Hai.

While standing on his staff, Zhao Hai’s eyes were plastered out front. Not far away were pillars of smoke shooting up from a certain place. One could see that it was an undersea volcano belching smoke. Zhao Hai believed that he should be near Inferno Island.

Before long, a hot red island appeared in Zhao Hai’s vision. The island wasn’t small and was as big as the Ocean Waves Dynasty. The entire island, no matter soil or rock, were all red. It even included the plants, the color added more uniqueness to the place.

In the south of the island was a volcano spurting hot lava, but it can be seen that it was about to be done judging by the smoke it released. Below that volcano, Zhao Hai can see rivers of lava flowing down.

What made Zhao Hai feel strange was the fact that he hadn’t seen any magic beasts nor flame demons. If the volcanoes were excluded, the island was deathly still.

Zhao Hai stopped caring about this as he immediately took a round trip around the island. By looking at the surface, the island looked quite simple. There were volcanoes upon volcanoes, it was basically an island made entirely out of interconnecting volcanoes.

After Zhao Hai looked at the island’s terrain, he returned back into the Space. The battle in the Accra Mountains was still going on. Everybody had lost count on how many clashes had happened between the Divine Race and the undead. But time and time again, the undead were able to push the enemy back. Moreover, they also caused massive casualties each time.

But what angered the Third Prince and the Divine Race the most was seeing their own allies dying in battle and the suddenly being swallowed up by a spatial rift, only to turn into an undead fighting against them. The eyes of the Divine Race couldn’t help but turn blood red.

For the Divine Race, this was an insult, a blatant insult. Their blood red eyes gazed at the undead in the defensive line, seeing their former allies manning the enemy’s weapons and attacking the Divine Race.

After seeing that there was nothing to worry about, Zhao Hai went to his room and opened a small monitor. Then he started to look at the interior of Inferno Island. He wanted to see if the island had any crystal lodes or not.

After looking at the monitor, Zhao Hai finally understood why there were no magic beasts nor flame demons present. The volcanoes were spurting lava at this time, so all of the island’s inhabitants had hidden themselves.

The places where the flame demons and magic beasts were quite peculiar as well. They were in other craters far away from the erupting volcanoes. In those craters, the numbers of magic beasts and flame demons were astonishing.

Zhao Hai ignored the flame demons and magic beasts as he made the Space scan the island. Upon scanning the island, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised. Right below the layer of rock, ash, and soil, about ten meters below the surface, everything was filled with fire element crystal stones. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but wipe the saliva on the edge of his mouth.

Zhao Hai immediately moved his body as it appeared on the island. Then he drilled underground and started to frantically take crystal stones into the Space.

The number of crystal stones was too much, Zhao Hai lost count of how much he had already absorbed into the space. However, he still kept absorbing more and more.

No other thing can match the Space in absorbing resources, its speed was something far from what people can imagine. Zhao Hai doesn’t know how long he has been collecting crystals, but as soon as he felt that nothing was left, he stopped.

Zhao Hai looked all around and saw how hollowed out the underground of Inferno Island had become. But he didn’t care, in any case nobody else was here. If the flame demons and magic beasts die, then that wouldn’t be much of a problem.

After seeing that there were no fire element crystals left, Zhao Hai went along and drilled deeper. He believed that there should be more crystals further down. Zhao Hai continued to dig and each 20 meters he would take fire element crystals on that layer.

After about nine layers, the quality of fire element crystals were getting better. Not only were the crystals getting bigger, the energy inside them were also becoming stronger and the color became a deeper shade of red.

Zhao Hai looked around once more and then dug down after seeing that no more fire element crystals were left. And while he was digging, he suddenly felt a wave of heat. It seems like he had come across a river of magma.

He avoided the magma as he went further down. But just as he passed by the magma river, Zhao Hai became stunned. At the bottom of the magma river was something he hadn’t seen before. There was a layer of golden sand on the floor of the river.

When he saw the sand, Zhao Hai waved his hand and absorbed some of them inside the Space. Then he waited for a prompt.

The Space didn’t disappoint him, before long, a prompt came in, “Pure golden sand detected. Golden Sand is an item from the cultivation world. Host’s level is too low, Space is currently unable to use it. Hoping for the Host to level up quickly.”

When he heard this prompt, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh. He didn’t expect to come across something used in the cultivation world. Moreover, it seems like the item was too special that the Space’s current level wasn’t able to use it. The sand was surely something good.

However, the golden sand was under magma, so gathering it won’t be easy. Zhao Hai looked around before he clenched his teeth and linked the magma river to the Space.

Compared to the one present in the northern icefield, this magma river was much bigger. It’s good that Zhao Hai already had experience in handling sea water. This time, he opened the Space to absorb the magma river, and along with it was the golden sand.

There was no response from the Space after the magma entered. Zhao Hai stored the magma inside the warehouse for now, he wouldn’t dare to release it in the Space.

When the entire river entered the Space, all of the golden sand were absorbed as well. But since magma wasn’t as runny as water, absorbing all of it took quite some time.

But after receiving the magma, Zhao Hai suddenly discovered that its source was actually a very small flame!

A flame as small as this was actually the source of the magma river? When Zhao Hai saw this, he initially thought that he was seeing things. But soon enough, he was able to ascertain that the flame was indeed the source of the magma. This was because Zhao Hai recalled something else he had acquired before.

Zhao Hai once got ahold of a crystal bottle with a flame quite similar to this one. Presently, that flame was acting as the Space’s sun.

Zhao Hai inspected the small flame carefully. He discovered that at the center of the flame was a hint of magma, bubbling due to the intense heat. After looking at it for some time and not seeing anything else, Zhao Hai threw the flame inside the Space.

Just as the flame entered the Space, a prompt came, “Heart of Earth Fire detected. Can produce fire element crystals, magma, golden sand, and heat energy. Space has levelled up to level 80. Host may now purchase 10 magic world backgrounds as well as 20 ordinary backgrounds.”

Zhao Hai clenched his fist and said, “Yes!”

This was truly a great thing for Zhao Hai. This heart of earth fire actually had a lot of uses, moreover, it also upgraded the Space. This was extremely good news.

Then Zhao Hai looked at the surroundings of the heart of earth fire. All around it were high energy fire element crystals. Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and absorbed all of them into the Space.

It has been a long time after Zhao Hai left to collect crystal stones. After digging some more and seeing that nothing else was left, Zhao Hai returned to the Space.

As soon as he entered the Space, Zhao Hai immediately placed the heart of earth fire on the ground and also released the magma river. Upon taking the magma river our, the Space issued a prompt, “River of earth fire detected. Can be refined as a weapon and can also be used for attack.”

Zhao Hai gawked, he didn’t expect the magma river to have this use. However, Zhao Hai waved his hand, separating the magma from the golden sand before storing the magma back to the warehouse. In any case, the heart of earth fire has been placed underground, it can produce magma at any time. Since the magma river had uses, Zhao Hai decided to store it in the meantime.

Zhao Hai inventoried the fruits of his trip to Inferno Island. His harvest this time was truly huge. From what he saw in the warehouse, the fire element crystals had reached hundreds of millions. What Zhao Hai was surprised about was the Space automatically categorizing the crystals by grade. There was low grade, mid grade, high grade, and top grade crystals. Naturally, the top grade crystals were the rarest, there were less than a million of them. High grade crystals numbered to about ten million, mid grade about 100 million while low grade reached a billion pieces.

After looking at these numbers, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be startled. He didn’t think that he would gain this much crystal stones. This was surely an unbelievable haul!

Chapter 815: Prepared

Although there was no way to trade with the crystals, Zhao Hai still regarded them as more important than either gold or silver.

These crystals were too useful for Zhao Hai, especially now as he battled against the Divine Race. Because of this, Zhao Hai was more than happy to see his harvests in Inferno Island.

At this time, his only use for the crystals was as ammunition for the magic cannons. But Zhao Hai believed that he would be able to find ways to use them for other things in the future.

While Zhao Hai was inside the Space looking at his loot, he didn’t neglect his work outside. At this moment, the blood ghost staff was flying towards the Radiant Empire, this way, there would be no delays in his operation.

At this time, Laura came. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what happened? We heard the prompts.”

Lizzy and Megan were commanding the war against the Divine Race, so they couldn’t just leave. However, Laura had nothing significant to do, so when she heard the prompts, she immediately went to see Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I got a lot of good things. Take a look.” Then he turned to the page on the warehouse showing the amount of crystals that they currently had. Zhao Hai had a lot of things stored inside the Space’s warehouse, this caused the warehouse to have a lot of pages.

However, it was great that the warehouse arranged the items inside according to the time it was stored. Because of this, those stored earlier appeared on the earlier pages while those recently stored appeared at the back.

When Laura looked at the page, they were immediately surprised. River of earth fire, crystal stones, golden sand. Not to say about the river of earth fire and the golden sand, the amount of crystals alone was enough to stun anyone.

Laura looked at the crystals and said, “So there’s classifications with crystals. Brother Hai, what kinds of crystals have we been using so far?”

Zhao Hai forced a smile, “The low grade ones.” Then Laura looked at the 1 billion low grade crystals on the page, she was caught speechless.

Then Zhao Hai said, “Besides the crystals, there are also the river of earth fire and the golden sand. At this point, I don’t know how to use them. I wanted to but it seems like the Space’s level isn’t high enough.”

Laura stared at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you really don’t know? The Space is already had a high level, yet it still can’t find a way?”

Zhao Hai bitterly smiled and said, “Right, it’s still insufficient. But now we can buy ten magic backgrounds as well as 20 ordinary backgrounds. I think we should hold back in buying more, we’re still quite short on resources.”

Laura nodded, she knew what Zhao Hai meant. When Zhao Hai made the Ark Space, he had almost used up all of his money. Therefore, its quite unintuitive for them to buy more backgrounds.

After closing the warehouse interface, Zhao Hai lead Laura back to the living room, while they were walking he said, “I’ve already absorbed everything there is to acquire in Inferno Island. We don’t need to return there in the future. Moreover, the crystals that we have in our hands is more than enough to deal with the Divine Race.”

Laura nodded, then Zhao Hai continued, “Most importantly, I acquired the heart of earth fire. I’ve placed it underground so that in the future we would be able to produce crystals for ourselves. There might also be more river of earth fire and golden sand for us to harvest.”

Laura smiled and said, “That’s good. Right, Brother Hai, if we sell those crystals to the Space I reckon they would fetch quite a price.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Forget it. The Space will not take any losses. If we sell our crystals and end up wanting to use them in the future, then the Space would sell it to us with a higher price compared to when we sold it. In any case, our current resources are enough. There’s no need to sell the crystals.”

Laura nodded. As they were talking, they had already reached the living room. Lizzy and Megan were present inside, taking charge in fighting against the Divine Race. At this time, Lizzy was working while Megan rested on the side.

Zhao Hai was aware that commanding a battle would be taxing to the brain. If one were to take charge over everything, then they would definitely be exhausted sooner or later. It was good that there were two of them, one could command while the other rests.

Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them and returned to his own room to look at the monitor. He estimated the time before they reach the Radiant Church.

What Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of was the scene happening in the Ark Space. Besides the soldiers, most of these people had never witnessed a battle before. Even the soldiers present haven’t been in one with this large of a scale. They had battle against the Demons and the Divine Race, but participating in a siege of this big was something they haven’t done before.

While looking at the battle, the population was burning with pride. One could hear people cheering and applauding here and there everytime the Divine Race gets repelled.

However, there were also some people who looked at this scene with heavy expressions. This was because they can see how strong the Divine Race was. Although they had been repelled by the undead many times, those inquisitive enough could count that the Divine Race had been doing this for more than 40 times.

They had failed forty times, and with heavy casualties in each attack. Nevertheless, the Divine Race still pushed on with the same tenacity as before.

Although this was only a small thing, those in the know understood how fierce the Divine Race’s soldiers actually were.

In the battlefield, the pressure of the fight had a large impact on the fighting strength of a soldier. Facing repetitive failures under unending attacks from the enemies, seeing your allies die in front of you, these weren’t something that an average soldier could bear.

However, the Divine Race’s soldiers actually managed to harden their hearts. They seem to be unable to comprehend their losses. They still charged, time and time again. If they were faced with any other army, then they would’ve already broken through.

Upon recognizing the quality of soldiers that the Divine Race had, these people couldn’t help but feel terrible.

They initially thought that Zhao Hai was being extra when he made them move to the Space. Some of them even felt uncomfortable. After all, the Space belonged to Zhao Hai. His status inside this place was incomparably high. Even the Rosen Emperor was uncomfortable with this decision.

They had seen the battle with the Demon Race. And now that they had witnessed the battle with the Divine race, their sense of unwillingness immediately vanished.

The Divine Race was just too strong, they surpassed what these people imagined. The Rosen Emperor let out a long sigh. Randolph who stood beside him asked, “Your Majesty, what’s wrong?”

The Rosen Emperor forced a smile and said, “I didn’t think the Divine Race would be this strong. No wonder Little Hai urged us to enter the Space. If we disagreed at that time, then I’m afraid we would be in grave danger.”

Randolph nodded, he sighed and said, “I didn’t expect the Divine Race’s soldiers to be this aggressive.”

Both of them made another sigh before turning around and returned to the Imperial Palace. They were people of status after all, they had a lot of things to do. They didn’t have the time to stay and watch everything.

Zhao Hai was unaware of all of these since he was poised to attack the Radiant Empire. The magic staff had already arrived on the southeast side of the Radiant Empire, this was where Zhao Hai and the others thought to be the best place to stage their attack.

The Radiant Empire’s southwest side was where the Divine Race’s descended land had landed on. Zhao Hai didn’t want to attack that new land for now, if he did, then it was possible that the Divine Race would send forces directly from the Divine Realm.

Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to attack from the southeast then heading towards the northwest, diagonally sweeping the Radiant Empire. With this, he would avoid the new land while sweeping the most number of magic cannons and Goblins along the way.

Since the battle on Accra Mountains was still underway, Zhao Hai took command of the undead this time. The undead he used were Barbarians and Winged Pegasus people. All in all, the army numbered to near 20 million.

Zhao Hai didn’t have these undead participate in the defense of Accra Mountain, This was because he had discovered how discontent the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus were towards the Divine Race. If he dispatched these troops, then Zhao Hai’s hard work on bringing those two on his side would go to waste, it might even arouse anger in the two groups’ heart. If those two armies joined the Divine Race in attacking the Accra Mountains, then that would not be good.

Chapter 816: Attack!

Zhao Hai stood on his blood ghost staff transformed into a flying sword. Behind him was his near 20 million undead army. However, these undead were in their zombie form. The Barbarians were in the center while the Winged Pegasus flanked them.

Zhao Hai didn’t use the cube formation this time. Although the cube formation had great advantages in attack and defense, its downside was its slow movement. Also, maintaining a cube formation needed some mental energy.

Because of this, Zhao Hai chose his current formation. He wasn’t planning to wage a large scale battle, he only needed to kill and then plunder, speed was key in this operation. If he was tied down by the Divine Race, then even if he wasn’t in danger he wouldn’t be able to get a lot of benefits.

Zhao Hai looked at the undead before said, “Remember, the Winged Pegasus are tasked with getting the Goblins. Me and the Barbarians will take care of the cities as well as the magic cannons.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t commanding a Human Army, so after saying this, he didn’t have to repeat his words. For the undead, Zhao Hai’s words were gospel. There was no need to think about nonsense, they will execute it no matter what.

After saying his words, Zhao Hai waved his arm and said, “Depart!” Then he took the lead as he flew towards the Radiant Empire.

When Zhao Hai departed, another monitor appeared on the cities of the Ark Space. The people who saw the image displayed was stunned, they were afraid that Zhao Hai would be injured by the enemy’s defense.

Although they were now inside the Space, they were still concerned about the war going on outside. After all, they were inside Zhao Hai’s Space, and Zhao Hai was personally taking charge of the battle.

Before panic ensued, a voice came, “Please calm down. Mister Zhao Hai planned to entangle the Divine Race army in the Accra Mountain in order to execute his plan; attacking the Radiant Empire!”

Along with this voice, a map appeared showing the Accra Mountain’s defensive line. Red dots on the map represented the undead army, green represented the Divine Race. Along with the map and dots, arrows also appeared, explaining the plan.

Before long, the population calmed down as they looked at the monitor. The map’s activity looked just like an overhead view of the situation. There were mountains and rivers as well as cities of the Buddha Empire that were very well depicted.

There were green arrows showing the route of the Divine Race, red arrows showed Zhao Hai’s movement.

The people could see a large green arrow plowing through the Buddha Empire with little to no resistance. After reaching the Accra Mountain, this arrow stopped since they were blocked by small red arrows. These small arrows were naturally the undead manning the defensive line.

The arrows moved while the voice explained what was happening. Even ordinary illiterate farmers were able to understand the simple explanation.

Then the monitor changed its display to the Radiant Empire. The voice then said, “While the undead in Accra Mountains detained the Divine Race, mister Zhao Hai amassed another undead army to attack the Radiant Empire. He would kill his way across the entire Divine Race camp!” At the same time, the screen showed a red arrow quickly  moving diagonally across the map, killing from the southeast to the northwest.

After the explanation, the map vanished. Then the display showed Zhao Hai’s attack on the Radiant Empire. “Mister Zhao Hai had already started his attack.”

The monitor showed a close up look of Zhao Hai. He was currently wearing his black robe as he rode on his flying sword. The wind was making his robe and belt wave, making the people look in awe.

Zhao Hai was calm as he paid attention to his front. They had entered the Radiant Empire and the Divine Race shouldn’t be expecting them to attack. Because of this, there was simply no defensive force on the Radiant Empire’s coastline.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t become careless. The entire Radiant Empire had become a large magic formation. Although this formation was used to break the Ark Continent’s barrier, who knows if it had any other uses, so Zhao Hai was being careful.

Zhao Hai was also aware that his actions were currently being broadcasted to the Ark Space. Cai’er already told him about it. This was what they agreed beforehand, its purpose was to improve Zhao Hai’s positive image.

While Zhao Hai advanced, he noticed that there were Divine Race soldiers stationed in a place not far from him. It was only a small town, so there weren’t a lot of people there. On the other hand, there were many Goblins working the field.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite as he waved his hand, leading his army to kill. On the monitor,  Zhao Hai’s army looked like an arrow as it overran the town that the Divine Race had occupied.

Everyone couldn’t help but hold their breath as the looked at the happenings on the screen. When the Divine Race soldiers stationed in the town noticed Zhao Hai’s army, they couldn’t help but panic.

They had no other choice, they were in a small town with little to no defensive strength. There weren’t even any magic cannons on the walls. In fact this place was only a slave town specifically set up by the Divine Race to manage their slaves. Additionally, the Divine Race didn’t expect anyone to attack their base, therefore they didn’t bother placing defensive measures on this town.

Zhao Hai went forward and led the Barbarians to kill into the city while the Winged Pegasus cavalry were going through the Goblins outside the city. Each and every Goblin were startled when the Winged Pegasus picked them up.

These Goblins were unaware that these cavalry soldiers had been turned into undead. They haven’t studied magic nor battle qi, therefore they weren’t so keen on things like these.

Although they were scared of the Winged Pegasus, they still didn’t dare to run. They knew they couldn’t escape no matter what they did. And if they dared to run, then the Divine Race would surely kill them.

All of the undead Winged Pegasus were 9th ranks, they didn’t even need to expend any effort in abducting the Goblins. They simply swept over the Goblins and threw them into the Space. The place where the Goblins were transported to was an ordinary background different from the Ark Continent and the Demons’ Space.

Naturally, the people from the Ark Continent didn’t see this on the monitor. What they were looking at was Zhao Hai and the Barbarians battling against the Divine Race.

The weapon that the Barbarians were currently equipped with were the javelins. Zhao Hai believed that of all the people in his control, the Barbarians would be the ones who can use the javelins at their full potential.

This was simply because the Barbarians were too strong, letting them use bows and arrows would be a complete waste. However, if they use javelins, their attacks would be stronger and more savage compared to before. If he wasn’t afraid of angering the Barbarian Race, then Zhao Hai would’ve already used the undead Barbarians to deal with the Divine Race.

But using them at this time was also good. The undead Barbarians followed Zhao Hai as they attacked the Divine Race’s town. At this time, in the skies of that town were several Divine Race soldiers establishing their Domain.

However, their strength was simply negligible in front of Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai waved his hand as he sent his flying sword to kill the Divine Race soldiers.

The blood red sword was very fast, to the point that only a red streak can be seen. Domains were broken while bloodstains appeared on the chests of the Divine Race soldiers. The bloodstains were getting bigger and bigger. When the Divine Race soldiers looked at their chests, they were shocked. Zhao Hai’s sword just punctured through their bodies, slicing their hearts into pieces. Naturally, it was impossible for them to survive this damage.

When the Divine Race soldiers died, Zhao Hai took them into the Space and then released them in Accra Mountain in order to help in the battle.

The entire process went too fast, those who winked managed to miss it. However, the voice went on to replay and explain what just happened. They even slowed the footage down so that everyone could see the attack.

After seeing Zhao Hai kill the Divine Race soldiers with a wave of his hand, the people couldn’t help but clap their hands. Then after that, they saw the rain of javelins blotting out the sky. It was needless to say but the Divine Race soldiers in the town was obliterated in an instant.

Upon killing the Divine Race, Zhao Hai didn’t leave. Instead, he went to look for detained Goblins and released them.

Additionally, Zhao Hai was also looking through the place. He wanted to retrieve the dried up bodies of the people who were used as a sacrifice by the Divine Race.

Chapter 817: Letting Matters Drift

Zhao Hai didn’t do these things for no reason. He found the Goblins in order to let the people from the Ark Continent know how the Divine Race treated those that they had enslaved. At the same time, Zhao Hai looked for the bodies of the Radiant Empire citizens in order to show the people what the Divine Race did in the Radiant Empire.

All of this was for Zhao Hai to get a good reception among the populace. He wanted the people to think of him well.

Not only would he make himself look good, he would also turn the Divine Race into the evil ones. Only then would the people from the Ark Continent understand what Zhao Hai did for them. In the end, they would worship Zhao Hai and may even think of him as a god.

This was just a part of a long-term plan. But with the Space, Zhao Hai believed that the goal should be reached soon. This was because the Space had an effect on the minds of people.

While Zhao Hai rescued the Goblins, he was also carefully inspecting them. The expressions of these Goblins were neither happy nor sad, even sorrow was absent. They were numb to the surroundings, they had dull and lifeless expressions. All of the people from the Ark Continent who saw this felt their heart tremble.

Especially after they saw the eyes of the Goblins. Their eyes were completely devoid of life, the look on their eyes were quite similar to those that belonged to Zhao Hai’s undead. They simply weren’t the eyes of someone who thought of living.

The Goblins were very short, even shorter than the Dwarves. Because of this, they looked very much like children when standing right next to Zhao Hai. However, they were very malnourished. They looked like figures with large heads and skinny bodies. Comparing them to radishes wouldn’t be too far off.

Upon seeing the Goblins, the people from the Ark Continent couldn’t help but think about their children. If the Ark Continent was conquered by the Divine Race, then the children might look very much like the Goblins; slim bodies with big heads.

After thinking about this, the people couldn’t help but shiver in fright. They immediately stopped thinking about this dreadful outcome. At this point, they couldn’t help but feel grateful towards Zhao Hai. Not only was Zhao Hai fighting the Demons and the Divine Race, he also provided them with safety inside the Space.

After taking the Goblins to the Space, Zhao Hai flew outside the town. The people from the Ark Continent didn’t know what Zhao Hai was doing up until they saw a ravine in the mountain. Inside that ravine was a pile of dead bodies.

Seeing the dried up corpses made the people in the Ark Space call out in alarm. Those with little courage turned their heads away, unable to look directly at the scene.

At this time, the voice came, “Everyone, these corpses that you see belonged to the citizens of the Radiant Empire, the Ocean Waves Dynasty. In order to reach the Ark Continent, the Divine Race used them to carry a blood sacrifice. Not one person in the Ocean Waves Dynasty survived. After the Divine Race arrived, they threw these bodies away as though they were outlaws. You can see the bodies, they were almost all kneeling, praying to their Empire, to the Radiant Church. They prayed that the Radiant God would give them a happy life. But they didn’t expect that they wouldn’t be given a happy life, instead, they were sacrificed!”

When those less courageous heard this, they opened their eyes to look at the kneeling corpses.

The people of the Ark Continent became angry. But this image didn’t stay still for a long time. Zhao Hai used magic to bury the ravine. Then after giving a bow to the dead, he turned around and lead the undead to their next target.

Their attack was focused on speed. And since there weren’t much Divine Race soldiers left, Zhao Hai’s advance went very fast. Every city he met was broken through immediately. He took all the Goblins and magic cannons he came across while eliminating every Divine Race soldier. Zhao Hai also looked for the corpses outside each city and buried them.

After attacking two cities, the broadcast showing Zhao Hai stopped. Now, the people of the Ark Space were back to looking at the Accra Mountains.

Although the battle was still lively, the feelings of the people from the Ark Continent were now heavier, they weren’t as enthusiastic to see the fight as before.

As for what the people of the Ark Space was thinking? Zhao Hai didn’t know. At this point, he was breaking through cities in the Radiant Church and taking everything that can be taken. Nothing was left for the Divine Race.

All the Goblins have been taken away, none of them were left behind. This can be regarded to be damaging towards the Divine Race. After all, without the Goblins, the army would have nothing to eat.

This was also the reason why Zhao Hai cut the broadcast of his actions short. He didn’t want the people of the continent to see him plundering the Radiant Empire. They might see him as a greedy person.

Zhao Hai’s movement was very fast. Although he was met with occasional resistance, they were all reduced to nothing in the face of the blood lightning javelins.

The magic cannons of the Divine Race can only be described as fine. Compared to the crystals used by the Ark Continent, their ammunition was actually worse.

The Divine Race naturally didn’t expect people to attack them. Because of this, their response has been very slow. Moreover, dealing with Zhao Hai’s 20 million army was quite hard. Their only choice would be either asking for reinforcements from the Divine Realm or to make the Third Prince come back.

However, the Third Prince was currently entangled in the Accra Mountains. Even if his army was quick to go back, rescue was still impossible. At this point, asking for reinforcements from the Divine Realm was a more feasible action.

But then again, by the time the reinforcements had arrived, Zhao Hai was already done and had returned to the Space.

Zhao Hai’s action took two days and one night of continuous battles.

After the attack, Zhao Hai had captured about 50 million Goblins, 3200 magic cannons, and various other commodities.

After arranging the Goblins to an ordinary background and counting the inventory, Zhao Hai went to visit the Goblins.

The spirit of the Goblins seem to have gotten better after entering the Space. Their numb expression loosened up. These Goblins weren’t stupid, they were also able to discover that this strange place had a much better environment compared to the Ark Continent, it might even be better than the Divine Realm. Moreover, they couldn’t see any Divine Race around them, only other Goblins.

At this point, the Goblins were already aware that they have been abducted by the people from the Ark Continent. Before coming here, the Divine Race already told them about the Ark Continent. After all, the existence of the Ark Continent wasn’t a secret since the continent’s ascendants always appear in the Divine Realm.

The Goblins didn’t expect that the people from the Ark Continent would be this powerful. They can actually cause trouble to the Divine Race. This was something that the Goblins wouldn’t even dream of doing.

Two days and one night passed by after the first Goblin arrived in the Space. Upon arriving, they were very scared, so they didn’t dare to walk around too much. But after two days, they began to get hungry. Naturally, they would have to look for food. It’s fortunate for them that Zhao Hai had a lot of bread trees planted in this background. After the Goblins discovered that the bread fruits were edible, they immediately ate it until they were full.

These Goblins didn’t know what it felt to be full. Since childhood, they had always eaten little to no food. After the Goblins felt their stomachs bulge up, some of them couldn’t stop themselves from crying.

During the time when they were being pursued by the Divine Race, they hid themselves in the untamed mountains and rivers of the Divine Realm. And since the Divine Realm was somewhat better than the Ark continent, the Goblins were still able to eat. However, ever since they’ve been captured, they had always been eating minimally.

In the background, there were plenty of bread fruits. Zhao Hai hardly used these fruits to feed the people of the Ark Space. This was because the people already had an excess of food while also growing their own. At this point, Zhao Hai doesn’t need to worry about their sustenance.

And if Zhao Hai were to sell these bread fruits to the Space, he would just get a pitifully low amount of gold coins. So even if they were eaten by the Goblins, Zhao Hai didn’t really care.

The bodies of the Goblins weren’t very big and since they had been starved for so long, their stomachs have contracted. They weren’t able to eat a lot so each bread fruit was enough to feed three Goblins.

When Zhao Hai appeared inside the Space, the Goblins were in the process of collecting bread fruits. Upon seeing Zhao Hai appear, the Goblins immediately knelt to the ground.

Zhao Hai looked at the Goblins and said, “You’re going to live here from now on. The Divine Race cannot enter this place. However, since this place is mine I shall be your master. I won’t treat you like slaves but I need you to comply to my orders. As long as you do your job, you can have anything you want.”

Zhao Hai knew that these Goblins weren’t just enslaved for one or two years. If you speak with them as equals right now, then their minds would surely turn blank. Speaking to them in a superior position was the only way for now.

Sure enough, the Goblins immediately accepted Zhao Hai’s condition. Not only were they not disappointed, each and every one of their expressions was showing glee.

The Space’s environment was already very good and since Zhao Hai didn’t have any gold coins right now, he couldn’t make any structures for these Goblins. He only gave an instruction, “As you can see, there are bread trees in this place. You can use those trees to eat and build houses with. I will also place some low ranked magic beasts in this place for you to catch. And if you have anything else you want, you can trade them for the meat and fruits here.” Then Zhao Hai pointed to a place not far away. The ground on that place rumbled before a church like building rose up.

This building wasn’t very big, but it looked very stylish. Zhao Hai looked at the Goblins and then said, “This will be your Divine Palace. If you need something, you can take the bread fruits or your meat there to trade. As long as bread fruits and meat enters that place and you say what you need, it will appear. Understood?” The Goblins nodded, some even gave a shout.

Zhao Hai nodded before his body flashed as it disappeared. He didn’t want to manage the Goblins. Later on when he goes to the Divine Realm, more and more Goblins would arrive. When that time comes, Zhao Hai wanted to see how they develop by themselves.

After the Goblins saw Zhao Hai leave, they immediately stood up. There were several of them who led other goblins and organized parties in order to gather bread fruits.

In any group, there would always be people who will assume the role of a leader. The Goblins weren’t an exception. Some Goblins were born with the talent to lead but since they were enslaved by the Divine Race, they weren’t able to let that talent bloom. But now that they had the opportunity, these Goblins went on to manage their fellow kin. Everyone went on to gather bread fruits then prepared to trade them for other items inside the church.

In fact, factions had already formed. Zhao Hai took a hands-off approach towards the Goblins. This was because the Goblins had their entire civilization and history wiped out. If he were to give them direction, then they wouldn’t be able to regain their original state. Letting them drift on their own was the correct choice.

Chapter 818: Response of the Demon Race

The situation between the Goblins and the residents of the Ark Continent was different. In the case of the Ark Continent’s people, their civilization was completely copied into the Ark Space, allowing perfect preservation of their lifestyles.

On the other hand, the Goblins had a high foundation regarding magical-mechanical civilization. It might even be possible that they were stronger than the Ark Continent. However, that civilization had become useless, it had been destroyed. It may even exist only in tales. In this case, it was almost impossible for Zhao Hai to teach the Goblins about how to regain their civilization.

The reason Zhao Hai gave them the church was to make it clear to the Goblins that even if the Space was convenient, they still needed to work. If they want something, then they would need to exchange it with something else.

It wasn’t that Zhao Hai was stingy, he just didn’t want the Goblins to just eat and sleep. He would have them know that working hard was the way to gain the most.

The church was something that Zhao Hai asked Cai’er to make. In fact, it was just a relay for items to be sent in. As long as the Goblins ask for it, then they would receive the item that they want. No matter what they wanted, Zhao Hai would provide.

Naturally, asking for things would come at a price. For example, if the Goblins wanted an ordinary iron axe, then they would need to trade about a hundred jin of bread fruit,

This price was based on the Space’s shop. Even if the price on the Ark Continent fluctuated, the Space’s shop would never change. Also, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid that the Goblins would ask for advanced items. In their present location, there wasn’t anything they could trade for it.

The most abundant item in the Goblins’ background were the bread fruits, and these fruits were very cheap. Even if they trade the bread fruits of the entire background, the Goblins still wouldn’t be able to exchange for a single crystal stone.

After taking care of the Goblins, Zhao Hai turned his attention towards the battle in the Accra mountains. The fight was still going on and Thunder Yun was still clueless that the Radiant Empire had already been ravaged.

At this point, it was already impossible for Zhao Hai to attack the Radiant Empire for the second time. This was because reinforcements from the Divine Realm had arrived. Now they were ready to face Zhao Hai’s attack.

Also, Zhao Hai was faced with the problem of manpower . Although he had still had a lot of undead, the formidable ones like the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus were unable to be used. If they were used in the battle, then Zhao Hai might anger the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus people.

Zhao Hai had a deep grudge towards the Divine Race, but he held no hatred towards the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus. To be honest, Zhao Hai was even feeling pity towards these two races. It was precisely because of this that when Zhao Hai discovered a peculiarity with the internal command of the Divine Race army, he immediately sent word to only send the minimum amount of troops towards the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus army. Zhao Hai wanted to send a signal that the Ark Continent didn’t have a grudge against them.

It can be said that Zhao Hai had done a successful job. The elite Barbarians and Winged Pegasus hardly made an effort in the battles which made the defense of Accra Mountains much easier.

But because of this action, Zhao Hai didn’t have enough troops to defend against the Divine Race. The people from the Ark Continent had already settled in the Ark Space. If he let the soldiers from the Ark Space help in the battle, then he might incur resentment from their families.

This dilemma caused Zhao Hai to have a headache. But just as he was thinking of ways to solve this problem, a sound came in from his messenger fish. After taking the messenger fish out, Zhao Hai discovered that it was from the Great Demon King. Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he slowly smiled.

After the Great Demon King reached an agreement with the Demon Dragon King, he immediately prepared to leave for the Demon Realm. But before he left, the Great Demon King had something to do first, and that was to wait for the Demon Vultures to come back. As long as they bring back information, then his plan would proceed to the next step.

It didn’t take too long before the Demon Vultures came back to Demon City. Upon arriving, they immediately went to ask for an audience with the Great Demon King. Naturally, the Great Demon King was expecting them, so he summoned one of them to give the report. He also invited the leaders of the other races present in the Demon Army.

After everyone arrived, the Great Demon King let the Demon vulture in. The Demon Vulture had a weary face but he still gave a salute. The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Alright, tell me what you saw.”

The Demon Vulture nodded, and replied, “Your Majesty. When I departed, I started from Demon City, then passed through the Accra Mountains before entering the Lyon Empire. Then after that, I arrived at the Rosen Empire then to Aksu Empire. In all of those places, not a single person can be spotted. Everyone seemed to have moved. And in the Beastman Prairie we managed to see the dark mist of the Underworld. There were also undead frolicking inside the mist.”

Upon hearing this, the Demon present couldn’t help but go into a buzz. They didn’t expect the Ark Continent’s people to have actually moved. Moreover, there was also the presence of the Underworld.

The Demons were generally fearless. But when it came to the Underworld, they couldn’t help but feel a deep sense of dread. This was because the underworld’s creatures were the bane of the Demon Race.

The Great Demon King looked at those present and said, “Silence!”

The room immediately turned quiet, not a single Demon dared to let out a sound. One could see the Great Demon King’s influence here. These people wouldn’t dare to disrespect the Great Demon King.

Seeing that the room had turned silent, the Great Demon King turned to the Demon Vulture and said, “Good job. Now go take a rest.” The Demon Vulture gave a bow before turning around to leave.

The Great Demon King looked at those present and said, “It seems like Mister Zhao Hai didn’t lie to us. I had a long discussion with mister Zhao Hai. He was very sincere when he took me to the place where the people of the Ark Continent migrated to. To be honest, when I went there I thought mister Zhao Hai had deceived me. The place was exactly the same as the Ark Continent. The people lived there peacefully, there were no wars that happened.”

The people looked at the Great Demon King, they didn’t know where he was going with this talk. The Great Demon King continued, “Mister Zhao Hai told me that he didn’t have any hatred towards us, the Demons. He said that we only invaded the Ark Continent because we wanted to live a good life, so he couldn’t hate us. Also, since we didn’t destroy anything in the Ark Continent, he had a good impression towards our lifestyle. Later on, he took me to a place, it was a very good place, much better compared to the Ark Continent. Mister Zhao Hai said that if we are willing, then we can move and live there.”

Although the Great Demon King issued an order for silence, the Demons present couldn’t help but issue a sound of surprise. What the Great Demon King said was too astonishing.

The Great Demon King opened his mouth once more, “You must think why mister Zhao Hai would do this? I’ll explain it to you. The Space actually belongs to mister Zhao Hai, it is his divergent ability. He can open a few spaces of his own and in those spaces he would be a god. That is to say, if the Demons live inside his Space, then we would need to follow him. Do you understand?”

When the group heard the Great Demon King, all of them collectively lost their voice. They didn’t expect things would be like this, all of them were looking at the Great Demon King in shock.

The Great Demon King saw their reactions and said, “Mister Zhao Hai gave me a promise that if the Demons enter the Space, then he wouldn’t suppress us for no reason. He also promised to not interfere with how we do things. He just pitied the state of the Demons and didn’t want us to succumb to the Underworld.”

After saying this, the Great Demon King sighed and said, “In the past, the Demons and the Underworld had some encounters. And each time it was us who suffered greatly. At that time, the battle occured in the Demon Realm, so we can just seal the rift. However, the Underworld connected to the Ark Continent this time. Moreover, the entrance to the Demon Realm had been completely opened, it would be difficult to seal it. This means that the Demon Realm will forever be connected to the Underworld.”

The Great Demon King looked at everyone present in the eye and said, “We managed to repel the Underworld because of the Demon Realm’s barrier. But now that the barrier to the Ark Continent was broken, the Underworld would surely be able to constantly connect to the Demon Realm. For the Demon Race this is truly a great disaster.”

The Demons present weren’t fools, they completely understood what the Great Demon King was saying. If they didn’t migrate, then they would sooner or later be swallowed by the underworld.

The Great Demon King said, “If we enter mister Zhao Hai’s Space, then we wouldn’t need to worry about the Underworld. Moreover, mister Zhao Hai inviting us over isn’t fully because of good intention. The Demons can also provide him with good benefits.”

Chapter 819: Hatred!

The Demons calmed down. Actually, they weren’t that worried about entering the Space. Just like Berry said, the Demons would do anything in order to live in a better environment.

What they were afraid of was having no use to Zhao Hai. If they didn’t have leverage, then that wouldn’t be very good.

If the Demons had no use, then would Zhao Hai still want them to migrate to his Space? That’s impossible, nobody would do that. The Demons would be less than herded magic beasts, they were utterly useless.

So when they heard from the Great Demon King that they could bring benefits to Zhao Hai, they couldn’t help but be moved.

The Great Demon King looked at the group and said, “Everyone should be aware of Mister Zhao Hai’s strength. I’ll be honest to everyone, even if I use my Devil War Chariot, I still can’t be confident in beating him. Moreover, I need to tell everyone that the Demon Realm isn’t the highest ranked plane there could be. There is still a much higher plane in existence.”

Upon hearing the Great Demon King, the other Demons couldn’t help but feel excitement. They were aware that the Ark Continent was a lower plane since it cannot accommodate God-ranks. After someone from the Ark Continent becomes God-rank then they would ascend to the Divine Realm.

They previously thought that the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm were the highest planes since these planes can have God-ranked experts. But now, after listening to the Great Demon King, it seems like there was a higher plane to the Demon Realm. With the Demons unable to sit still, the room immediately buzzed into discussion.

The Demon Dragon King already knew what was coming, so he looked at the other Demons and said, “Silence!”

His voice calmed the other Demons down. The Great Demon King then said, “I already knew some things about the higher realm, however, I didn’t tell you because it is too unbelievable.”

The Demons listened. The Great Demon King had done a lot for the Demons all these years and they knew that he wouldn’t lie to them. Because of this, they eagerly waited for what he would say next.

The Great Demon King looked at the other Demons and said, “The Demon god we believed in is actually a person from that higher realm and he doesn’t even look like the Demon God that we worship. He looked just like this.” Then he took out the illustration that Zhao Hai printed.

The others hadn’t seen this before including the Demon Dragon King. Now they were curious about the image that the Great Demon King took out.

After the group saw the image, the Great Demon King said, “Besides Demon Dragon, nobody in the Demon Realm knew that I had the Eyes of Truth. Upon becoming the Great Demon King, the Demon God appeared for the ceremony. At that time, the Demon God I saw wasn’t the same as the one depicted in our records. His true body was actually this. He turned into the Demon God so that we would worship him. Later on, I started to investigate matters myself. In the end, I discovered that the Demon God statue had a magic formation to collect faith power.”

Everyone blankly stood in place when they heard the Great Demon King. These matters were beyond their understanding. They don’t know what to say.

The Great Demon King sighed and said, “There weren’t a lot of people who knew about this, but there were quite a number who did. In addition to Demon Dragon, the high level God ranks were also aware of it. After we came to know about this matter, the only thing in our minds was how to get rid of this person’s control.”

After speaking this, the Great Demon King’s tone changed, “What had the Demon God given us after all these years? Mister Zhao Hai’s place is incomparably better than the Demon Realm. In the Demon Realm, we would need to wage war with each other just to survive. In this case, why do we still give the Demon God our faith power? We had already given him so much, yet what did he give in return?”

The words of the Great Demon King spoke directly into the minds of the Demons. These Demons had long suffered in the Demon Realm’s environment. Now that they heard the Great Demon King, a great resentment erupted deep within them. Everyone was breathing heavily, their eyes were red!

Demons were unafraid of death. Although they believed in the Demon God, their belief wasn’t so strong because of their constant struggles. They believed in themselves more than the Demon God.

Upon seeing the reaction of his fellow Demons, the Great Demon King knew that this was the crucial time, so he said, “To be honest, my decision to invade the Ark Continent was rooted to the purpose of getting away from this person’s control. However, i didn’t think that after discussing with Mister Zhao Hai, he actually had an encounter with this person!” Then the Great Demon King retold how Zhao Hai met Lu Wei and the process Zhao Hai did to defeat him.

Then the Great Demon King added, “Because of this, I decided that we should move to Mister Zhao Hai’s Space. Mister Zhao Hai is strong and in the future he would definitely become stronger. When the time comes, mister ZhaoHai would ascend to the higher plane and possibly meet with that person. This person had deceived the Demons for many years, this is something we cannot allow. If mister Zhao Hai ascends while taking us with him using his Space, then we can personally take our revenge!”

Upon hearing the Great Demon King, the killing aura of the Demons present had immediately soared. Demons hated cowards, but they hate people deceiving them the most. So after knowing about Lu Wei, the Demons immediately placed him on their kill list. If they can take revenge personally, then they would be happy.

The Great Demon King looked at everyone and said, “Does anyone have anything to say? If you don’t want to enter mister Zhao  Hai’s Space, then I won’t stop you, you can decide for yourself. Mister Zhao Hai also said that even if you go to the Space and don’t worship him, then it would be fine, everyone can make a decision for themselves.”

After the Great Demon King said this, a Demon stood up and said, “Your Majesty, there’s no need to ask that, we need to enter the Space. Not only is the environment good, we can also get revenge in the future.”

Along with him, the other Demons also agreed to enter the Space.

The Great Demon King looked at them and said, “Good, then I will immediately contact mister Zhao Hai. But before entering the Space, we need to help mister Zhao Hai deal with the Divine Race!”

As soon as they heard this, the Demons gave a cheer. Nobody opposed to it. In their opinion, the Divine Race was Lu Wei’s most faithful dogs. Since they couldn’t hit Lu Wei now, dealing with the Divine Race was the next best thing.

The Great Demon King waved his hand and then said, “Alright, everyone should go back. I’ll prepare things here before I go back to the Demon Realm to prepare our people to move to the Space first. All of you shall listen to Demon Dragon and help mister Zhao Hai deal with the Divine Race, understood?”

The group said in one voice, “Yes, Your Majesty!” The Great Demon King nodded as he waved his hand once more, making the other Demons leave. However, he had Demon Dragon King stay behind.

When the other Demons left, the Great Demon King turned to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Demon Dragon, i’ll be leaving everything here to you. I’ll contact Mister Zhao Hai and tell him to contact you as well.”

The Demon Dragon King complied, then the Great Demon King took Zhao Hai’s messenger fish out. The Demon Dragon King looked at the messenger fish curiously. The fish had no redeeming value, it was just a small fish swimming inside a bottle filled with water.

The Demon Dragon King turned to look at the Great Demon King, he didn’t know what the purpose of this fish was. The Great Demon King looked at him and smiled before he turned to the small fish and said, “Mister Zhao Hai, Mister Zhao Hai, can you hear me?”

The Demon Dragon King looked blankly, he actually suspected the Great Demon King to be crazy. Otherwise, why would he shout Zhao Hai’s name to a fish.

While the Demon Dragon King was confused, Zhao Hai’s voice suddenly came, “Your Majesty, I didn’t think you’d contact me this quickly. I hope you have good news for me.”

The Demon Dragon King looked blankly at the fish. It was still swimming inside the bottle, but Zhao Hai’s voice was actually coming out of it.

The Great Demon King responded, “It’s good news, mister. The Demons have agreed to enter mister’s Space. Can Mister take them in now?”

Zhao Hai’s voice came in, “Hahaha, of course, of course they can come anytime. But Your Majesty needs to head back to the Demon Realm to organize your people. I’ll be dealing with the Divine Race so I’m quite busy. After you had things prepared in the Demon Realm, then I shall head there and take your people to the Space.”

Chapter 820: The Demons Want To Send Their Troops

When he heard Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King’s eyes shone as he said, “Mister is fighting the Divine Race? How is it?”

The Demon Dragon King also raised his ear, Zhao Hai laughed and said, “It’s doing very well. I just went to the Radiant Empire and ransacked it. Haha. I’m focusing on the Accra Mountain’s defensive line right now. I want to surround them and eliminate them.”

The Great Demon King’s eyes went brighter, he said, “Can mister have the Demons dispatch our own troops?”

Zhao Hai turned silent. This made the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon king anxiously look at the small fish. After some time Zhao Hai replied, “I’ll be honest to your Majesty. I’m presently low in manpower. At present, I have 20 million strong undead in reserve. However, these undead belonged to the Barbarian and Winged Pegasus clan. Those two races weren’t born from the Divine Realm, they were just like people from the Ark Continent who were conquered by the Divine Race. At first, the Divine Race baited me to attack them in order to draw their elite troops. I didn’t know about this before, but now that i do, I decided to refrain from angering them. Moreover, those two races have a grudge with the Divine Race. At this moment, they weren’t giving their all in attacking my defensive line. This allowed the Accra Mountains to stay put even with the lack of manpower. But even then, I cannot have the Demons send their troops. I believe Your Majesty had taken great efforts to convince the other Demons to enter the Space. If Your Majesty decided to have them send their men, then it’s possible that Your Majesty would be placed in an awkward position. I’ll just hold out and wait for an opportune time to contact the Barbarian and Winged Pegasus armies, I’ll try to get them to our side and gang up on the Divine Race.”

Although Zhao Hai said a lot, he was retelling what he did and the decisions that came with. This made the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King stare. At the same time, they were also moved. They didn’t think Zhao Hai would think about them this far.

The Great Demon King gave a short laugh before he said, “I thank mister for the consideration. But we Demons have a grudge against the Divine Race. Because of this, we would be happy to send our troops over to fight. We will not have any resentment if mister agrees to send us.” Upon hearing the Great Demon King, Zhao Hai replied, “The Demons and the Divine Race had a grudge? Why didn’t I know this? Your Majesty, you really don’t need to send your people. If we can’t deal with the Divine Race now, then it won’t matter. In any case, I’m planning to go to the Divine Realm. “

Then the Great Demon King smiled and expressed his thoughts to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile upon hearing this. He finally understood what the Great Demon King meant by their grudge against the Divine Race. Zhao Hai replied, “That’s true. But you should know about the strength of the Divine Race, this time they had sent their elite troops. To be honest, the Demons would lose against them. But if you really want to deal some damage to the Divine Race, then I would have to ask the Demon Army to come to the Space first and get some weapons for the battle. I have some lethal items that can help. I’m sure you have seen them before.”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Alright, you have my gratitude. However, since I need to return to the Demon Realm, I’ll be leaving the army in the hands of Demon Dragon. If you need something, you can just talk to him.” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Alright, I will open a spatial rift near Demon City tomorrow. I’ll ask the Demon Dragon King to organize the army and enter the Space. After going in, I will hand the weapons over. What do you think?”

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “Good, then that’s settled. Demon Dragon, say a few words.”

Demon Dragon King got close to the messenger fish and said, “Mister can rest assured, everything will be ready by tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Demon Dragon King, we’re old friends, so you have my utmost trust. By noon tomorrow, I will open the spatial rift. At that time, I’ll ask you to send the Demons in.”

Demon Dragon King nodded and assured him once more that they would be waiting. After Zhao Hai left the conversation, the Great Demon King turned to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Alright, this matter is settled. I will not stay here for longer. Demon Dragon, go find the others and tell them our arrangement. Tomorrow, you will be the first Demons to enter the Space. Also, remember that you’re fighting against the Divine Race. Make sure to send the elites, anyone less talented will stay inside the Space. Be familiar with the environment, after all that place will be our future home.”

The Demon Dragon Kin felt uplifted as he gave a nod. Then he asked the leaders of the Demon groups over to the hall.

These people were confused, they just left the hall but then they were called back in. The Great Demon King looked at everyone present and said, “I just talked to Mister Zhao Hai. At this time, he is fighting with the Divine Race. We didn’t have to but I asked Mister Zhao Hai to allow the Demons to fight and deal with the Divine Race. I will be handing the army over to Demon Dragon, does anyone have anything to say?” The Demons immediately became excited when they heard this. A Demon Ogre loudly replied, “I want to see how strong those Divine Race bastards really are. I can’t wait to see their expressions when they see us. Your Majesty, when do we fight?” The others had the same thoughts.

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “Mister said that just sending troops over wouldn’t be good. The Divine Race are all powerful. It would be difficult for our current state to deal with them. Because of this, mister said that if we want to fight the Divine Race, then we would need equipment. Mister Zhao Hai will provide them for us. When the time comes we can use those weapons to deal with the Divine Race.”

The people present all cheered. A Demon Ogre’s loud voice can be heard, “Those javelins from before are quite strong. If we have those, then our power would certainly increase.”

Among the Demons present here, most of them had fought with Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s previous actions had caused so much damage that these Demons had become somewhat afraid of him.

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “Tomorrow at noon Mister will open a spatial rift outside Demon City. You will enter that rift and arrive at the place Mister Zhao Hai allocated for the Demon Race. Not only are you going to retrieve weapons there, you should also get accustomed to the place. I already told Demon Dragon to send only the elites to help deal with the Divine Race. The others need to behave inside the Space. Get used to the place, that is where we will live in the future.”

There was no need for the Great Demon King to say anything more, the Demons were already excited. Although they had heard that Zhao Hai would provide them with a place to live, they still haven’t seen the place so some of them had reservations. Being able to see it tomorrow was good news for them.

The Great Demon King looked at their excitement and gave out a cough. This caused the hall to turn silent, then the Great Demon King nodded, “In the meantime, I shall return to the Demon Realm and prepare the other Demons to move. I want you to remember two things, look at Mister Zhao Hai’s attitude towards us. If he acts very arrogant, then we will not enter his Space. We are Demons, we won’t stoop to a point that people will look down on us.”

The Demons nodded, then the Great Demon King said, “Second thing, if Mister Zhao Hai treated you properly, then you need to help him deal with the Divine Race. We are against the Divine Race, and this fight will reflect on the our reputation. If you lose face for the Demons, then I’ll deal with you personally!”

The Demons gave a loud grunt. Demons were concerned about their face. If they lost face in front of Zhao Hai, then the entire Demon Race would be affected. The Great Demon King might not even need to make a move, the other Demons would immediately deal with the culprit.

The Great Demon King looked at the others and said, “Alright, you prepare for your departure. Remember, I’ll leave everything to Demon Dragon. If there’s anyone who dared to disobey his orders then I’ll give them a good pounding. Especially the Demon Ogres, I have my eyes on you.”

The Demon Ogres didn’t care, they just stood there with smiles on their faces. The Great Demon King couldn’t help but feel at loss, these Demon Ogres were completely hopeless.

The Great Demon King stared at the group before he stood up. Then he turned to the Demon Dragon King and then to the others and said, “Remember, this will be the greatest change that the Demon Race will undergo in our countless years of existence. You cannot make a single mistake. Otherwise, you and I will become the biggest sinners of our race. This is a great opportunity for the Demons to change our lives. Understood?”

The group all gave a their assurance. The Great Demon King nodded before he walked out and got into his chariot. Then he took a hundred thousand people with him to return to the Demon Realm.

The reason the Great Demon King brought this many people was to quell any troubles that would arise in the Demon Realm. Naturally, these troubles didn’t refer to the Demon Race. Instead, it meant the magic beasts of the Demon Realm.

Magic beasts of the Demon realm were also very strong. Once in a while they would attack a Demon and would prompt the Demon race to amass an army just to deal with it.

After the Great Demon King left, the Demon Dragon King immediately gave an order, “Get the supplied ready and prepare to move to mister Zhao Hai’s Space tomorrow.” Then he looked at the busy atmosphere outside, he knew that this would be a sleepless evening.

Zhao Hai stored his messenger fish and smiled. He was worried about manpower, but he didn’t expect the Demons to actually offer their services.

The Accra Mountains was still standing, the Divine Race wouldn’t be able to take it for a while. Also, it would be quite hard for the Radiant Empire to send reports to the Divine Race army. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to send the Demons two days later.

Zhao Hai went downstairs and looked at Lizzy and Megan. In the past few days, the two were working very hard. The Divine Race had turned into maniacs, endlessly attacking the Accra Mountain. Even if they were rotating between shifts, the two still couldn’t help but get tired.

There were several occasions where the Divine Race punctured the defensive line. However, Lizzy and Megan still managed to drive them back.

At this time, Thunder Yun was looking at the Accra Mountains with blood red eyes. He was more and more astonished by the strength of the undead army. Withstanding the Divine Race assault for this many days wasn’t something that an average army could do.

Although the Divine Race were comprised of God-ranks, they can’t possibly fight for so many days in a row, they also need to rest. Because of this, Thunder Yun had arranged a rotation regiment for his troops in order to maximize their fighting potential.

However, the constant fighting wasn’t the one that made Thunder Yun depressed. He had already clashed against the Divine Race twice. But in those two fights, he wasn’t even able to see Zhao Hai’s shadow. This undead army belonged to Zhao Hai and the Ark Continent’s strongest person was Zhao Hai. If he wasn’t even able to see Zhao Hai in those two battles, then this would only mean one thing; The Ark Continent had yet to use its full force. This was definitely a huge blow for the Divine Race’s pride.

At this point, Thunder Yun was about to lose his mind. He looked like a gambler who lost big. His only desire right now was to break through the Accra Mountains’ defensive line.

At the same time, the Third Prince was also driven silly. He sat in his sword carriage and looked blankly at the defensive line. He didn’t say a word, he just looked straight at the mountains as if he had gone crazy.

In the past, the Third Prince expected the Ark Continent to fall in one blow. But now it looks like the opposite was happening. The Ark Continent’s undead were very powerful. They weren’t any less than a Divine Race soldiers. The difference between his expectations and reality was the same difference as the heavens and the earth.

In the past few days, the Third Prince had continuously looked at the repeated rushing of the Divine Race soldiers. He also continuously saw them being driven back. This was a huge blow to his ego, he almost lost all ability to think.

Chapter 821: The Divine Race Will Collapse Soon

The Third Prince was completely scrapped. This was his first time entering a battlefield and he had already suffered a colossal loss. At this point, he didn’t have the ability to command an army.

Naturally, the Generals of the Divine Race were aware of this. In order to save their soldiers from dying in vain and keeping the Third Prince safe, the Generals went to Thunder Yun for help. Therefore, aside from the first few charges and the attack on the Accra Mountain, Thunder Yun took command of every action the Divine Race army made.

Although Thunder Yun’s command token was taken away by the Third Prince and wasn’t permitted to command troops, the Divine Race were well aware of Thunder Yun’s ability. After the Third Prince blanked out, the Divine Race could only rely on Thunder Yun for command.

However, they didn’t know that the stress felt by Thunder Yun was no smaller than the Third Prince. At this time, Thunder Yun was at the point of collapse. Although he was still going on, his abilities were already affected.

In this case, although the Divine Race’s command chain was restored, its overall ability was still completely crippled.

Thunder Yun’s only choice right now was to attack. He can almost affirm that Zhao Hai had already attacked the Radiant Empire. The only thing the Divine Race army could do was to break Accra Mountains’ defensive line and conquer the Ark Continent. Otherwise, the Taurus King would certainly punish him. Even the Marshal won’t be able to do anything.

Thunder Yun knew the moment they started fighting the defensive line that the Divine Race had no easy way out. Zhao Hai certainly wouldn’t allow them to return to the Radiant Empire without the army leaving an arm or two. By the time they return to the Radiant Empire, their numbers would be reduced significantly, and it would be impossible to return within four days. If they were to return, they would take at least half a month. But by that time everything would be too late.

Thunder Yun also knew the implications of Zhao Hai attacking the Radiant Empire. Ever since the Taurus Divines started their conquests, they never experienced an attack on their rear. But now, under the Third Prince’s command, they did. This meant that the Third Prince’s military accomplishments were utterly finished, completely decimated.

At this time, Thunder Yun was only hoping to break through the defensive line as quickly as possible and enter the Ark Continent. This might give them enough recognition from the King to give them lenient punishment.

Three days passed by and the undead were still defending the defensive line. Thunder Yun didn’t know how many attacks they had already launched. However, all of them were useless, they just couldn’t break through the defensive line. This made Thunder Yun’s mood worse and worse. He knew that the longer they get entangled here, the worse it would be for them.

Thunder Yun also discovered that the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus armies weren’t giving their all. However, Thunder Yun didn’t dare to get angry at them right now. No matter what, the two cavalry armies were still attracting attacks from the undead. At this time, only a fool would offend these two armies.

But Thunder Yun remembered this. He was thinking that after they head back to the Divine Realm, then he would harden the suppression on these two races.

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of Thunder Yun’s thoughts. He was at the living room at this time, looking at the Divine Race. Megan was the one in charge right now, Lizzy was taking a rest.

Megan looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “Brother Hai, you came back. Did everything go well?” Although Megan was the one taking control, she doesn’t actually need to give her full focus on the command. After all, the undead were also intelligent. What Megan needed to facilitate was the overall situation, the undead would take care of their own jobs.

Zhao Hai looked at Megan’s weary face, he smiled bitterly and said, “Megan, you’ve been working hard. I’ve already reached an agreement with the Demons. They will dispatch their troops to support us. When that time comes we can finally deal with the Divine Race.” Megan smiled faintly and nodded, “Alright, that would be good. The Divine Race are going frantic. They are only attacking desperately at this point. Unlike the past two days where they were still organized, that time was hard.”

Zhao Hai looked at Megan and said, “Don’t worry, we’ll make sure that the Divine Race suffers. The Demons have agreed to enter the Space. I will pick them up tomorrow and give them some equipment and weapons to deal with the Divine Race alongside the undead.” Megan nodded, “Brother Hai, are you serious about doing a counter attack on the Divine Realm?”

Zhao Hai’s voice became cold as he said, “Why not? The Radiant Empire had millions of ghosts unable to shout their resentment. If we don’t get revenge for them then we would become heartless. Moreover, I want to get more Goblins to the Space.” Megan smiled, then she hugged Zhao Hai while looking at the fight on the screen. Megan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Wouldn’t it be nice if we could live peacefully, looking at the monitor that doesn’t show battles. That would be great.”

Zhao Hai gently patter Megan’s head and said, “It’s not like I don’t want to live peacefully. People just come and cause trouble for us. Don’t forget, the Divine Race aren’t our only enemies, the Underworld is still running around in the north. There’s also Lu Wei. The one we had dealt with before was just his projection. His main body still remained undamaged. I’m afraid we would have to face him as well.”

Megan gave out a sigh. He knew that what Zhao Hai said was right. As their strength was getting stronger and stronger, their enemies were also getting more powerful.

The battle of the day soon passed. The Divine Race were still unaware that the Radiant Empire had already been attacked. They still kept attacking and attacking.

Zhao Hai went back to take a good rest, he left Laura to accompany Megan and Lizzy. The Divine Race also attacked in the evening, making it impossible for Megan to take a rest. Zhao Hai doesn’t want Megan to stay up at night alone, so he asked Laura to join Megan.

When Zhao Hai got up the next morning, he started to prepare the supplies to be given to the Demon Race. These supplies had weapons but also common living materials.

The Demons would enter the Space but Zhao Hai didn’t know what kind of houses they live in. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to keep the present appearance of the background, he also didn’t have enough cash to make significant changes. In addition to the supplies, he also released low level magic beasts in the background.

One could say that there weren’t low level magic beasts in the Space. However, Zhao Hai discovered that he could adjust the levels of purchased magic beasts in the Space. Both long-tailed chicken and blue-eyed rabbits can be turned to either 9th rank or just any ordinary animal with no rank.

On the other hand, beasts like the raging bulls can only have a minimum of 1st rank. In other words, they couldn’t be turned into ordinary animals. Their levels ranged from 9th rank to 1st rank, and lower than 1st rank was impossible.

This function was quite useful. Although the people in the Space had become quite strong, it would be impossible for them to kill 9th rank beasts every day. Having lower level magic beasts would ideal for everyday living.

Noon came as Zhao Hai prepared the supplies. Then he returned to his room and looked at the monitor only to see a properly arranged Demon Army waiting for the spatial rift.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile as he waved his hand and opened a huge spatial rift outside Demon City.

The Demon Dragon King had prepared themselves well; they were already in formation early in the morning. The Demons hadn’t had a wink of sleep last night. This matter was just too important for them. Perhaps, beginning from this day, the Demons would forever discard the brutal environment of the Demon Realm.

Seconds turned to minutes as minutes turned to hours. As noon came closer and closer, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but get more nervous.

Just as the Demon Dragon King was worrying that the spatial rift wouldn’t appear, a huge crack appeared right outside Demon City.

Zhao Hai slowly flew out of the rift. When the Demon Dragon King saw Zhao Hai, he immediately went forward to give his greetings. Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Dragon King and gave a salute, “I apologize for making the Demon Dragon King wait. I’ve already prepared the supplies inside the Space.”

The Demon Dragon King didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this polite. He returned the salute and quickly said, “Mister is too polite. It’s still noon so you aren’t really late.” Zhao Hai gave out a laugh and replied, “Alright. I’ll have to ask the Demon Dragon King to arrange your people to enter the Space. The place where you’ll appear will be your home in the future.”

The Demon Dragon King excitedly nodded. Then he waved to the people behind him and before long a team of Demons entered the spatial rift.

These people were Demon Ogres. They were specifically tasked with the Demon Dragon King to check the place. If the environment was good, then they would go. If it wasn’t, then they won’t.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about this action. After all, nobody would carelessly go inside a mysterious rift. The residents of the Ark Continent only did so because they already trust Zhao Hai. But even then, there were still some twists and turns in convincing the Rulers and Great Nobles. This was even true for the Demon Dragon King. After all, they were enemies before, it would be stupid for them to just go into a place without proper investigation.

Chapter 822: The Demons Enter The Space

The reason why the Demons agreed to migrating into the Space was because of the Underworld’s threat. At this point the Demons had no other choice.

However, the Demons were people of courage and bravery. They wouldn’t just allow Zhao Hai to deceive them. Zhao Hai believed that if he did, then the Demons would forgo anything and attack him.

The Demon Dragon King didn’t have the mind to talk to Zhao Hai right now. He was currently staring at the spatial rift with a nervous expression. He was waiting for the Demon Ogres to come back.

Before long, a Demon Ogre went out of the rift. The God rank Demon Ogre was rushing towards the Demon Dragon King with an elated look, “Demon Dragon, it’s fantastic. Everything inside is so beautiful, much more attractive compared to the Ark Continent. It will be better for you to have a look.” The Demon Dragon King knew how impossible it would be for the Demon Ogres to lie. If they did, then it would be extremely obvious. After hearing the Demon Ogre, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but let out a breath.

At this time, the Demon Dragon King was reminded of Zhao Hai who was right by his side. It was clear from his action that he didn’t trust Zhao Hai. The Demon Dragon King became afraid that Zhao Hai might be offended. Because of this, he had an awkward expression as he turned his head.

However, Zhao Hai was just smiling. There seems to be no problems.

The Demon Dragon King let out a sigh of relief. Then he gave a salute to Zhao Hai and meekly laughed, “Mister, this Demon Dragon asks for forgiveness.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It’s not a problem. I can’t blame you. This is a very important matter for the Demons. Your Majesty, please have your troops enter the spatial rift. I have to be honest, when I say live inside Space, I lied a bit. At this time, there are no structures to shelter you. You need to build everything yourselves. Last time, when I reconstructed the Ark Continent, it cost me a lot. For now, I have no resources left to help the Demons. You’ll have to start everything from zero.”

The Demon Dragon King laughed and said, “Mister, there’s no problem with that. In the Demon Realm, aside from stone houses, we don’t have anything else. For the Demons,  money and other things are completely useless. The most important thing is a place to comfortably live in.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and replied, “Then you won’t be disappointed in the Space. I also left some living materials for you. I believe it wouldn’t take too long before you can build your own cities.” The Demon Dragon King looked at the spatial rift and said, “I believe so too.” Then he waved his hand, signalling the army to enter the Space in an orderly manner.

Zhao Hai calmly looked at the Demons along with the Demon Dragon King. Quickly entering the Space with several tens of millions of people was virtually impossible. Although Zhao Hai’s spatial rift was quite big, it still took some time before all the Demons managed to enter the Space.

Finally, it was Zhao Hai and the Demon Dragon King’s turn to enter the Space. The black surroundings of the spatial rift was quickly replaced by the blue skies of the Space. Upon seeing the the environment, the Demon Dragon King immediately loved it. It was truly beautiful; blue skies, lush grass, it was indeed much better compared to the Ark Continent.

Zhao Hai looked at the Demon Dragon King and then said, “Your Majesty, I’ll be leaving things here for you to manage, I still have things to do. Can I know when the Demons would be ready to deal with the Divine Race?”

The Demon Dragon King recovered from his stupor, he looked at Zhao Haia nd said, “I already arranged them yesterday. Mister, rest assured, we certainly wouldn’t delay.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then took out a messenger fish before handing it over to the Demon Dragon King, “I’ll give this messenger fish to you. If you have anything you need, then don’t hesitate to contact me.” The Demon Dragon King already saw the Great Demon King used the messenger fish, so he already knew how to operate it. The Demon Dragon King nodded before receiving the messenger fish. After that, Zhao Hai’s body flashed as it disappeared.

The Demon Dragon King looked at the messenger fish before he carefully kept it. Then he turned his head to resume looking at the scenery in front of him.

The place was really attractive, more attractive than anything he had seen before. He always thought that the Ark Continent was the best, but now it was clear that the Space was much better.

At this time, a shout was suddenly heard in the distance. The Demon Dragon King immediately went towards the commotion and saw piles upon piles of supplies, it was a group of hills beside one another.

However, these piles only contained commodities, there were no weapons. However, the weapons weren’t placed far, one could see javelins being stacked up on each other.

A Demon Ogre held the javelin and tried to test it. After throwing the javelin, the ground in the distance suddenly bore out a huge hole. The result gained cheers from the crowd.

The Demon Dragon King smiled faintly upon seeing this, he gently shook his head before he said, “Alright, stop playing around. These javelins were left here to be used on the Divine Race. Everyone, don’t forget our purpose here. His Majesty has ordered us to get familiar with the place so that the other Demons can settle down properly.”

The people complied with his order and left. In the meantime, the Demon Dragon King convened the leaders of the Demon groups to discuss the troops to be sent tomorrow.

After the leaders arrived, the Demon Dragon King said, “i already guaranteed mister that we’ll send our troops by tomorrow. What are your thoughts on this?” The other Demons didn’t speak. The Demon Dragon King scanned the group and said, “If you have anything to say, just say it.”

This time, a Demon Ogre opened his mouth and said, “There’s no need to say anything. Mister has given us a good place, the least we could do is help him deal with the Divine Race. We’ll smash those Divines like eggs! They’re running dogs of that bastard, we have to kill them!”

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “Alright, then that’s settled. His Majesty the Great Demon King also gave instructions to only send our elites, so we can’t have everyone go. Since this is the case, then we might as well send the Devil Legion. Each and every one of them had battled through mountains of corpses and seas of blood. His Majesty told me that if they don’t get to kill for some time, then they would go insane. Tomorrow seems to be a good opportunity to send them out. There are ten million soldiers in the Devil Legion less the 100 thousand that His Majesty took with him. I believe they should be enough to help deal with the Divine Race. What do you think?”

The Devil Legion that the Demon Dragon King meant was actually the Death Qi army that Zhao Hai saw. Just as the Demon Dragon King said, the army  was born out of killing and killing. And if they didn’t kill, then they would go insane.

Actually, this was a type of mental disease. They grew up in the battlefield and only knew how to kill. Their affinity for murder had become too great that they were completely incompatible with normal lifestyles.

Nobody expressed any objection. Then the Demon Dragon King continued, “After the Demon Army sets out, the others will proceed to build structures. Mister told me that he had already spent a lot of resources to copy the Ark Continent, therefore he isn’t able to help us. He had already given us this beautiful place, so how could we depend on him on this as well? I’ll lead the army tomorrow but I need people to be in charge back here. Moqiao and Shidak will remain here to take charge.” Moqiao was a Demon who looked more delicate compared to the others. Although he was a God-rank expert, his killing aura was completely different compared to the other Demons.

On the other hand, Shidak was a short Demon. He had a burly appearance and had a fully bearded face. He looked like a large version of a Dwarf.

The two stood up at the same time and gave a salute.

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “Then I’ll leave the Space for you two. Pick a nice place to build His Majesty’s palace. Then as soon as the Space’s map gets figured out, then start allocating places for our brethren.”

The other Demons didn’t oppose to the Demon Dragon King’s plan. The Great Demon King held a high status among the Demons. Nobody would oppose to building his palace first.”

After seeing that everybody had agreed, the Demon Dragon King continued added, “Good. Then let’s have the Devil Legion. The others will have to investigate the Space.”

The Demons simultaneously nodded before leaving. The Demon Dragon King stayed on his seat and looked at the scenery. A great land spanned out as far as the eye could see. The Demon Dragon King didn’t think that a day would come where he would witness such a sight.

The Demon Dragon King took a deep breath, smelling the fragrance of the green grass. The smell was fantastic. The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help himself as he stood up and went out of his carriage to step on the meadow. He felt like he was stepping on a wool blanket. It was soft, the Demon Dragon King was forced to walk carefully.

After walking for some time, the Demon Dragon King came upon a small creek. The water on this creek was very clear. He could even see small fish swimming here and there.

The Demon Dragon King squatted and cupped some water from the creek, drinking it. Sweet! The water was unexpectedly very pleasant. The Demon Dragon King slowly closed his eyes as tears filled his face. This is a good place, this is the heaven that the Demons were always dreaming about.

After some time, the Demon Dragon King stood up and looked all around. There were Demons frolicking everywhere. They too were overwhelmed by a sense of glee. The Demon Dragon King didn’t stop them from roaming around. He can understand what these Demons felt. To be honest, if he wasn’t concerned of his status, then he would’ve joined them as they flew around all over the place.

Chapter 823: Three Continuous Rounds

The Demon Dragon King woke up. He never felt this great after sleeping. His sleep was too serene.

The Demon Dragon King wasn’t sleeping in a luxurious room. Instead, he was lying outdoors, on the ground, with only the grass as his bed.

If ordinary humans slept on the grass overnight, then they would’ve fallen sick by the time they woke up. This would never happen to the Demons. Not to say a meadow, even if they fell asleep on a huge slab of rock, they still wouldn’t get sick. Their bodies were just too formidable, it wasn’t any less compared to magic beasts.

The Demon Dragon King didn’t open his eyes immediately. He just quietly laid there and smelt the fresh fragrance of grass, relaxing his mind from the inside out.

After some time, the Demon Dragon King opened his eyes and looked all around him. He discovered that there were Demons who were still taking walks in all directions. Their faces all wearing warm smiles.

The Demon Dragon King stood up gave an order,”Devil Legion, assemble!” As his voice fell, the resting soldiers of the Devil Legion immediately stood up and quickly assembled themselves into a formation.

The Demon Dragon King didn’t have any reaction. If the Devil Legion didn’t have this simple ability, then they wouldn’t have been the Demon Realm’s most powerful group. The Demon Dragon King went to the front of the Legion and said, “Today we shall be fighting the Divine Race. Javelins will be provided to each one of you. I believe you already knew about the javelins, so be careful when carrying it. Now, go line up!” The Devil Legion immediately readjusted their formation as they took two batches of three javelins each.

After receiving their weapons, the Demon Dragon King gave another order, “Bring your weapons and go eat. Come back after having your meal.” The Devil Legion gave a shout.

The Devil Legion also had its own logistics division. Their meals were the best in the Demon Army. At the very least, they would have magic beast soup to consume.

At this time, Zhao Hai appeared right beside the Demon Dragon King. Upon seeing Zhao Hai, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but stare as he gave  salute to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, were we late?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and shook his head, “Late? No, no. Right, what are they eating?.” Then he pointed at the food that the Devil Legion were eating.

The Devil Legion had meat soup. However, meat wasn’t the main course. Their staple was a type of green grass, something like a vegetable stuffed dumpling.

The Demon Dragon King also looked at the Devil Legion and  nodded, “This is the food most Vile Demons eat. It’s from the Demon Realm’s saint tree.”

When Zhao Hai heard this, he immediately understood. He didn’t think that the Demon Dragon King’s people would actually eat Cai’er’s leaves.

Cai’er’s leaves were indeed edible. Zhao Hai and the others even tried to eat one. However, the taste wasn’t good at all, moreover, it was rough to the throat. Zhao Hai didn’t expect the Demon Army’s most elite troops to eat this kind of food.

Zhao Hai shook his head as he pointed to a distant mountain and said, “There is a bread tree forest over on that mountain. You can eat those. As long as you get the fruits and open them, the pulp could be directly consumed.”

The Demon Dragon King stared, then he immediately had people go and fetch bread fruits over on the mountain. They also saw this fruit yesterday, however, they didn’t know what it was. In the Demon Realm, if you saw a delicious looking fruit, then it was almost always lethal to ingest. There were even fruits too poisonous that it can kill even a God-rank expert. Because of this, the Demons didn’t touch the bread fruits out of habit.

Before long, Demons carrying bread fruits came back. Zhao Hai took one bread fruit and opened it. Just as the fruit was opened, the pulp immediately expanded. Zhao Hai tore a piece of the pulp and placed it on his mouth. Then he nodded and said, “It’s good. However, this one isn’t ripe yet. Make sure to get the ones that are turning yellow. Not only are they bigger, they are also the most delicious.”

The Demon Dragon King also took one bread fruit and like Zhao Hai, cracked it open before eating a piece of the pulp. As soon as the pulp reached his mouth, a sweet fragrance immediately filled his cavity. After eating a few more pieces of pulp, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are you saying that all those fruits are for us?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Yes. Currently speaking, those are the our highest output trees. They can help you pass your initial migration. Later on, I’ll give you some seeds so that you can plant your own crops like bamboo rice, corn, and so on. I believe you’ll come to like them.”

The Demon Dragon King looked gratefully at Zhao Hai. After some time, he bowed his body, intending to kneel. However, Zhao Hai stopped him in time and said, “No need to be overly polite. Since you’ll be living here from now on, then that means we’re now on the same side. You’re my family, so no need to be formal.”

The Demon Dragon King still gave a small bow before turning to the other Demons and said, “Everyone, go and eat these fruits. However, the Devil Legion would have to continue eating their meals. There’s no time left to gather fruits for you.”

After having eaten their meals, the Demon Dragon King gathered the Devil Legion. Zhao Hai looked at the Devil Legion in front of him and couldn’t help but feel the pressure.

The Demon Dragon King went towards Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, they are the most powerful Demons in the army. Each one of them had gone through hundreds of battles and mountains of corpses. They are very powerful. I’ll be leading them to help you in dealing with the Divine Race. But there is one thing about them I need to tell you. They are a murderous group, only suitable for life of battles. They can’t do anything else, and if they don’t fight then they would go crazy. They might get dangerous enough to kill each other.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he immediately understood that these people were completely swallowed by the spirit of murder. However, this was also good. Having these people meant that they were completely unafraid to fight, it meant that Zhao Hai essentially had one undead and one undead-like army in his hand.

The Demon Dragon King became anxious after seeing Zhao Hai stay silent for a while. At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly asked, “Can they ride a horse?”

The Demon Dragon King gawked, then he nodded and said, “They can ride horses. Why did mister ask?”

Zhao Hai replied, “I want to turn them into a cavalry unit. Moreover, their equipment needed to be changed.” Then Zhao Hai waved his hand, making a bunch of equipment appear.

These equipment were divided into several piles. There was a pile for armor, a pile of spears, and a pile of swords. Zhao Hai didn’t bring out some shields, they were too heavy and will affect speed.

Zhao Hai turned to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Have them try it.” The Demon Dragon King nodded as he commanded the Devil Legion to change their equipment.

Zhao Hai was afraid that these people would be unfamiliar with the new equipment. But soon, Zhao Hai realized his mistake. These people were born to fight, so any weapon and armor was completely suited for them. Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that they arranged their weapons in a way for them to easily pull it out. It’s quite clear that they weren’t unfamiliar with these weapons.

Zhao Hai relaxed, then he released a large number of ferghana horses. At this point, everyone was already equipped. They were holding spears on their hands as they rode the saddle. There were two pockets of three javelins, one strapped to each side. Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I’ll leave them to you, Demon Dragon. Just follow me, there’s no need to charge immediately.” The Demon Dragon King nodded and then went to his carriage.

.Zhao Hai looked at the group and smiled. Then without saying anything, he waved his hand and opened a rift in the Space. Then Zhao Hai led the ten million strong Demon Army out.

Zhao Hai and the others appeared not far from the Divine Race’s rear. They were going to start going all out against the Divine Race.

The Demon Dragon King was standing beside Zhao Hai, looking at the Divine Race’s location from time to time. At this time, Zhao Hai was also standing beside the Demon Dragon King. This was the Demon Dragon King’s intention. Since Zhao Hai wouldn’t look good if he was just flying on air, he invited him over to stand in the carriage.

Zhao Hai didn’t reject the invitation as he stood on the black dragon carriage. They could see the Divine Race fighting in the distance. These Divine Race soldiers looked like they were in a trance. The only thing in their eyes was the Accra Mountain’s defensive line. They didn’t even notice the ten million Demons appearing behind them.

Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race army as he turned to the Devil Legion behind him and said, “Demon Brothers. Before you are the Divine Race. All of them look at themselves as sacred while seeing all others as beneath them. But under their sacred facade is a ruthless and cold blooded nature. Their cruelty is incomparable to any other. They used a hundred million people for their blood sacrifice and broke the barrier of the Ark continent, changing the laws of the heavens and the earth. In turn, this caused the Underworld to appear on the Ark continent. Most importantly, they are running dogs for that immortal cultivator. Although they knew about him, they were still willing to devote their lives to that person. They are a race bent on conquest, offering everything for that immortal cultivator!”

Although Zhao Hai’s voice wasn’t that loud, all ten million Demons in the Devil Legion all heard him. And even if they didn’t make any sound, their reaction was obvious by the appearance of killing intent in their gazes.

Zhao Hai looked at them and then continued, “You are the Demon Race’s most elite soldiers. Today, it’s time for you to show your strength. Let the Divine Race know that they aren’t the most powerful. Let them know of the Demon Race’s strength. Follow me. Kill everyone!!!!”

After speaking this, a blood red spear appeared on Zhao Hai’s hand. This spear wasn’t a transformed blood ghost staff. Instead, it was actually the Beast God’s Spear.

Ever since the Beastmen entered the Space, they had given Zhao Hai their Beast God’s Spear. This was also true for the Elven Bow and the Iron Hammer. These three artifacts already submitted to Zhao Hai. In addition to these three, there was also the three artifacts from the Radiant Church. However, since he can’t use everything, Zhao Hai just took the spear and handed everything else to Laura.

As Zhao Hai’s voice fell, the Devil Legion chanted in one voice, “Kill! Kill!” Not only the Devil Legion, even the Demon Dragon King was feeling his insides turning hot.

Zhao Hai turned around and then pointed his spear towards the Divine Race and shouted, “Kill them!!” Then the black dragon carriage started to move, directly approaching the Divine Race’s rear.

Among the Divine Race army, some of them who were resting had started to notice Zhao Hai. They hurriedly set up their formations and prepared to block Zhao Hai’s advance. At the same time, the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus were ordered to attack the left and right sides of the Demon Army while the Divine Race kept the Accra Mountains’ defensive line busy.

One couldn’t deny the quality of the Divine Race army. Achieving this shift in formation was not easy. However, they were unfortunate to have traitors among their numbers.

The Divine Race wanted the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus to keep the Demons at bay while Thunder Yun attacked the defensive line. However, the Divine Race never expected the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus to go away after seeing Zhao Hai’s attack. They didn’t even take the effort to confront the enemy.

This huge betrayal caused the Divine Race army to almost spit out blood. But what they needed to do right now was to block Zhao Hai’s attack. If they cannot block Zhao Hai’s attack on the rear, then the Divine Race army would collapse. Even if the Deity came, their situation would still be unsalvageable.

However, the Divine Race seemed to forget that Zhao Hai still had blood lightning javelins. After nearly entering firing distance, Zhao Hai loudly said, “Prepare the javelins!” Along with his order, the Demons immediately took two javelins, one for each hand.

When they arrived at their firing distance, Zhao Hai immediately ordered, “Send three continuous rounds their way!” Then after that, the Demons immediately threw two javelins on each of their hands, then they took another two out and then threw it, then another two……”

Chapter 824: Attacked By Their Own Weapon

Three waves of never ending javelins came flying out. Since each Demon threw javelins in each hand, each of  them threw six javelins overall.

The javelins thrown out by the Demons went farther than any average 9th rank, about 1,100 meters. However, this 1,100 meters was too close for the 9th rank ferghana horse.

As the matter stands, busting out three batches of attacks in that time frame would certainly need fast actions. But one could see that the javelins that were thrown this way had the largest effect on the enemy.

While throwing the javelins, Zhao Hai didn’t decrease their speed as they went forward. Fortunately, those following Zhao Hai were the elites of the elite. Otherwise, Zhao Hai’s demands wouldn’t be met at all.

After three rounds of attack, Zhao Hai and the others were already in front of the Divine Race army. Their javelins had blasted out an opening for them to penetrate through.

It was needless to say but every time Zhao Hai waved his spear while he was on the black dragon carriage, a Divine Race Soldier would die. The Demon Dragon King beside him didn’t idle and also took his weapon out. His weapon was a sword and with the two acting as the tip of the arrow, the Demon Army went straight through the Divine Race army. At this point, the defending Divine Race thought that if Zhao Hai continues to go forward, then their army would be cut in half. When that time comes, then they would be subjected to more lethal attacks by the undead on the defensive line.

Zhao Hai didn’t just attack randomly. His target was very clear, it was the sword carriage. Zhao Hai wanted to control the sword carriage more than anything else.

The ten million Demon Army, with Zhao Hai as the tip, went straight towards the sword carriage. The sword carriage was originally surrounded by cavalry. But as the battle got intense, the cavalry soldiers also participated. At this time, the defensive power of the sword carriage had dropped.

If there was a capable person inside the sword carriage, then everything would be fine. After all, the sword carriage itself was a Domain Weapon. However, the one sitting inside the sword carriage right now was the blank-headed Third Prince. Even if the sword carriage was a good weapon, it was completely useless if there’s nobody to wield it.

At this time, Thunder Yun was commanding the battle on the frontlines. He wasn’t expecting Zhao Hai to suddenly attack them from behind them and go straight towards the sword carriage.

Around Thunder Yun were about 100 thousand Thunder Clan people. Of those attacking the Accra Mountains, Thunder Yun trusted the Thunder Clan the most.

When Zhao Hai’s attack came, Thunder Yun was stunned. And when he decided to react and return to block Zhao Hai, it was already too late. Zhao Hai was currently by the sword carriage, Thunder Yun simply couldn’t catch up.

At this time, Zhao Hai was killing his way to the entrance of the sword carriage. The carriage door was currently closed. Zhao Hai carefully inspected the door and discovered that it actually slides open. Zhao Hai pulled his blood ghost staff out and transformed it into a sword. He slid the sword to the opening of the door and slowly made it expand. Before long, the sword carriage door slowly opened up.

And just as the door slid open, a sword light suddenly came towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai didn’t move his body as he crystallized himself, allowing the sword light to hit his face.

Clang! The sword was repelled. Zhao Hai looked at the carriage and saw that a maid was the one who attacked him. The maid was looking at Zhao Hai with complete shock.

Zhao Hai also found out that the maid wasn’t too high level, only 9th rank. Such strength simply cannot pose a threat to him. Zhao Hai looked at the maid before his body flashed inside the sword carriage. The inside of the carriage wasn’t small. And unlike the Great Demon King’s carriage, the decoration inside the sword carriage was very luxurious.

Inside the sword carriage were the several maids, all had swords on their hands as they looked fearfully at Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai gave a faint smile as he waved his hand, making undead appear. These undead knocked the maids out and brought all of them into the Space.

At this point, there was only one person other than Zhao Hai left inside the carriage, it was the Third Prince. The prideful and high-spirited Third Prince can no longer be found. Instead, a dull and pale faced youth was present.

Zhao Hai looked at the Third Prince and wondered whether he could take the Third Prince to the Space. Who would’ve thought that Zhao Hai would actually succeed. The Third Prince didn’t even make a single move to resist, his transfer to the Space went smoothly as can be.

Zhao Hai knew that the Space couldn’t just absorb any intelligent life. Someone with intelligence needed to be willing in order to be taken into the Space. If the person resisted, then the Space couldn’t take him.

It seems like the Third Prince had completely lost his mind. There seems to be no thought of resisting present in his brain. This was out of Zhao Hai’s expectation.

However, this wasn’t the time for Zhao Hai to wonder about this. Zhao Hai proceeded to inspect the sword chariot. This sword chariot was a Domain Weapon, it would be a pity if it remained unused. Zhao Hai waved his hand and took the Domain Weapon into the Space.

Zhao Hai wanted to see if the Space had anything to say about the sword carriage. If it did, then that would be great. If it didn’t, then it wouldn’t be a big deal if Zhao Hai couldn’t use it.

The sword carriage didn’t disappoint Zhao Hai. As it entered the Space, a prompt quickly came, “Exotic item detected. Weapon suitable for energy transmission. Low Grade. Host can use item with his Domain. After establishing a Domain and turning it into Human shape, then the weapon can be used immediately.” Zhao Hai stared, but he immediately took the sword carriage out as he established his Domain. Before long, a  giant Zhao Hai appeared. Then that giant Zhao Hai held the sword carriage. The sword carriage lit up as its miscellaneous parts disappeared. At this time, a giant Zhao Hai holding a white sword can be seen. Every sweep of this white sword killed batches of Divine Race soldiers.

Thunder Yun paled upon seeing Zhao Hai wield the sword carriage. Thunder Yun already knew that they were finished. God-ranks with Domain Weapons were terrifying people, they were on the border to being invincible Only another person with a Domain Weapon could take them on. Otherwise, people would just throw themselves to their deaths.

Thunder Yun knew that they were already done. However, he didn’t want Zhao Hai to have it easy. He was currently like a trapped beast that wanted to make one last attack.

Thunder Yun turned his head to the Thunder Clan people and ordered, “Prepare your thunder-strike! Target is Zhao Hai!” The Thunder Clan complied as they prepared their totems, went into their formation, and started to mutter their spells.

However, Thunder Yun soon found out that something wasn’t right. He had ruled the Thunder Clan for a long time, so he was very familiar with their various attacks. From the looks of it, the Thunder Clan were indeed using their divergent abilities. However, it wasn’t the lightning-strike that Thunder Yun asked for!

As Thunder Yun was puzzled, a network of thunder and lightning started to form. Thunder Yun gawked, he immediately berated the Thunder Clan. however, it was too late. The Thunder Clan immediately unleashed their attack. But instead of Zhao Hai, their target were the defending Divine Race soldiers!

Right, the one they attacked wasn’t Zhao Hai, but the Divine Race who were resisting his advance. These Divine Race soldiers didn’t expect the Thunder Clan would attack them. Nobody was even able to set up their defense as a large number of Divines were turned to ash by the blanket of lightning.

Thunder Yun saw this and his mind turned blank. At this time, Barbarians and Winged Pegasus soldiers appeared in the distance. Then the two armies went on and launched an attack on the Divine Race army.

Thunder Yun was dumbstruck by the sudden attacks. He looked at the Thunder Clan, the Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus soldiers with a confused expression. He didn’t know what they were doing.

But at this moment, Thunder Yun suddenly discovered a peculiar figure among a team of Thunder Clan soldiers. This person’s stature was slightly smaller compared to his peers. Thunder Yun felt that this person was familiar. In the end he found out that this was none other than his personal bodyguard, the person he trusted the most, Fei’er!

After seeing Fei’er, blood rushed to Thunder Yun’s head. Thunder Yun understood that Fei’er had come back a long time ago, only waiting for this opportune moment to attack.

Thunder Yun’s guess wasn’t wrong. Fei’er indeed came back a long time ago and was truly waiting for this moment. Fei’er was supposed to head to the Marshal’s office and inquired about the situation. And once Fei’er came back, then Thunder Yun could resume his authority as the commander of the Divine Race army. If Fei’er stuck to his duty, then the Divine Race wouldn’t have been plunged into their current situation.

However, Fei’er didn’t do his job. He went to the Divine Realm but he actually contacted the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus races. After talking to the two races, he immediately returned to the Ark Continent and secretly rejoined the Thunder Clan army. He had the Thunder Clan secretly prepare and wait for the best moment to make a fatal attack on the Divine Race.

Thunder Yun’s bloodshot eyes looked at Fei’er as he shouted, “Fei’er, you dared betray me? Who gave you the courage!?”

Fei’er looked at Thunder Yun and replied, “Thunder Yun, I didn’t betray you. I wasn’t loyal to you in the first place. In the past, the Divine Race had slaughtered our race to seize the Thunder Continent. The Thunder Clan had always been waiting for an opportunity for revenge. I only came by your side to spy on the Divine Race.” Thunder Yun at Fei’er and muttered, “So you didn’t really surrender…”

Chapter 825: Discussing A Cooperation

Fei’er’s voice turned cold as he said, “Correct. My Thunder Clan and your Divine Race has a very deep enmity, so how can we just become loyal to you? This time, I also rallied the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus to move together with my Thunder Clan to rebel against the Divine Race!”

Thunder Yun, with blood red eyes, berated, “What gall! Aren’t you afraid of the Divine Race completely eradicating you race?”

Fei’er smiled faintly and then pointed at the enlarged version of Zhao Hai and said, “Zhao Hai gave us courage. Although he isn’t that strong, but with our three races, we should be able to deal with you Divines.”

Thunder Yun gawked, then he turned his head to the rampaging Zhao Hai. For a while Thunder Yun didn’t know how to retort. Zhao Hai’s attacks were very damaging to the Divine Race.

However, it didn’t take a long time before Thunder Yun looked at Fei’er and said, “Why would the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus ally themselves with Zhao Hai? Zhao Hai has killed no small amount of their people.”

Fei’er sneered, “The Divine Race killed more of their people compared to Zhao Hai. Moreover, since Zhao Hai killed their members, that also demonstrated his strength. And did you forget? To the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus Clans, becoming undead isn’t a bad thing. For them, it’s just another form of being alive. Although they will not volunteer to become undead, they would still regard undead as another alive person.” Thunder Yun stared, then his expression became ugly to behold. The belief of the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus Races was very strange. Just like Fei’er said, becoming undead wasn’t a disgraceful thing to them, it was just another form of a person. Because of this, Zhao Hai turning their clan members into undead didn’t offend the two races.

Fei’er knew this point, therefore he invited the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus people into an alliance. In the past, Zhao Hai thought that using the undead Barbarians and Winged Pegasus would cause the two races to hate him. But in the end, the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus people hated the Divine Race more than him. Additionally, Zhao Hai didn’t heavily attack the two armies during the war. One could say that the hatred those two held for Zhao Hai was very small.

Zhao Hai didn’t know that the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus had such traditions. Because of this, he didn’t use the undead he gained from eradicating the two armies from before. This caused him to lack manpower.

Thunder Yun looked at Fei’er. At this time, Fei’er didn’t have his docile appearance. The current Fei’er was now fully expressing his hatred towards the Divine Race. This wasn’t something that Thunder Yun had seen before.

There’s no need for Fei’er to say anything else, however, he couldn’t help but look at Thunder Yun and said, “You Divines had always killed your way into every place you came into. But who would’ve thought that you would stumble in the Ark Continent? Hahaha. I didn’t expect this opportunity to come this soon. I have to be impolite, my master. Everyone! Kill!”

The Thunder Clan people immediately launched an all out attack against the Divine Race. They controlled their net of lightning to sweep the surrounding Divine Race soldiers. The situation on the battlefield turned into the Divine Race versus the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, Thunder Clan, Undead, and Demons. At this point, the Divine Race was left with nothing to do but resist.

Zhao Hai saw this and removed his Domain. Then he regained the Sword Carriage form as he sat inside to look at the battlefield.

The Divine Race soldiers already knew that they had no hope of winning today. However, the Divine Race still pushed on, nobody surrendered. They were going all out in resisting the attackers. There were some people who stayed and fought and there were also people intending to break through the encirclement and head towards the Radiant Empire.

From the very beginning, the battle had always leaned on one side. With the pressures that was brought by battling against the Accra Mountains, the soldiers were still exhausted despite their method of taking rests. At this time, their fighting strength was completely far from their original. With them being assaulted by these many groups, how could it be possible for them to block?

The fight started from the day and went on to the night. When it was finished, all of the Divine Race soldiers were eliminated. The total number of undead that Zhao Hai gained reached about 30 million. However, there were still people who managed to run away. After all, the groups didn’t discuss their plan to kill the Divine Race. This left them with problems when it came to the encirclement.

The fight had ended, but the current situation was now strange. The Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and Thunder Clan people were grouped up as they stared at the undead army and the Demons. In the fight, the Barbarians and the others had discovered how strong the Demons and the Undead were. And after seeing Zhao Hai wield the Domain Weapon, they couldn’t help but have their guard against him.

At this time, Zhao Hai had the sword chariot go in between the two groups before receiving it to the Space. Then Zhao Hai flew to the three allied races. At the same time, Fei’er, along with two representatives from the other two races, also flew forward. When the two parties were fifty meters apart, they stopped and stood in place.

Zhao Hai looked at the three people opposite him and then smiled, “Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and Winged Pegasus friends. Let this Zhao Hai thank you for the help.”

Fei’er inspected Zhao Hai. This was the first time that he had seen this person. During the time when he accompanied Thunder Yun, Zhao Hai didn’t appear. Fei’er was only able to recognize Zhao Hai by the portrait that was circulated among the army.

Fei’er gave a salute to Zhao Hai and said, “I have seen mister Zhao Hai. We should be the ones to thank Mister for the help. If Mister wasn’t here, then it would be impossible for us to deal with the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai inspected Fei’er as well. He knew who Fei’er was. He saw him everytime Thunder Yun was seen on the Space’s monitor. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Mine and your situation are the same. Nobody owes anyone anything.”

At this time, the Barbarian representative opened his mouth, “Mister, we’ve heard from the Divine Race that you have turned our clansmen into undead. Is that true?” Zhao Hai looked at the Barbarian, he couldn’t deny it so he just nodded and said, “Yes. At that time we were enemies. So I treated them as such, there no need for me to hold back.” The Barbarian looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, can you take our clansmen out? We want to see them.”

Zhao Hai looked strangely at the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus. These two had their people turned into undead, but why were their expressions too calm?

However, he knew that it was useless to think of it at this time. He didn’t stall for a moment before he nodded and waved his hand. Before long, the undead Barbarians and Winged Pegasus appeared behind Zhao Hai. These people weren’t in their skeleton form, instead, they were in the zombie appearance. In any case, the Space’s zombies looked more pleasing to the eyes.

The Barbarians and Winged Pegasus looked at their undead brethren and nodded. They didn’t say anything more.

When Fei’er saw Zhao Hai’s confused expression, he explained, “Mister, please don’t be confused. The Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus believe that being turned into undead is another form of survival. Because of this, they don’t hate Mister for turning their people into undead.” Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think the two races would have this idea, it truly expanded Zhao Hai’s perspective. Zhao Hai gave a small bow to the two races and said, “At that time, this Zhao Hai didn’t know your plan so I regarded them as my enemies. Let me offer my apologies.” Fei’er waved his hand and then asked, “Mister, do you have any plans? Are you going to defend the Ark Continent and drive the Divine Race away?”

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and said, “The Ark Continent is already hopeless. The Underworld creatures had already appeared. Defending the Ark Continent would be useless. Moreover, the Ark Continent has an unresolvable hatred with the Divine Race. Naturally, we won’t let that hatred go. I plan to attack the Divine Realm.”

Fei’er gawked, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would actually attack the Divine Realm. He actually planned to convince Zhao Hai to do so, but it seems like that plan was already useless. Fei’er then replied, “That’s great. How about we discuss about cooperation?” Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er before he nodded and waved his hand, making the sword carriage reappear. Then he said, “I’ll have to invite you inside to discuss. Demon Dragon King, you come in as well.” The Demon Dragon King standing behind Zhao Hai nodded and followed Zhao Hai to enter the sword carriage door.

Fei’er and the two others didn’t hesitate and followed as well. The Barbarian and Winged Pegasus representatives jumped down from their mount before entering the carriage.

Although the sword carriage had gone through war, it wasn’t actually damaged. As the group entered the carriage, they discovered several women cleaning inside.

These women were no other than Laura and the others. Since Zhao Hai had taken the maids and the Third Prince away, there was now nobody who can maintain the place.

After the group entered the carriage, Zhao Hai immediately introduced Fei’er and the others to his wives. As a greeting, Laura and the others offered the visitors some drinks.

When the group settled down, Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and said, “I am Zhao Hai. And I think you already knew him, but he is the Demon Dragon King, the representative of the Great Demon King.” Then Demon Dragon introduced himself.

Fei’er nodded and said, “I am Thunder Clan’s Fei’er, Thunder Clan’s representative.”

The Barbarian then said with his deep voice, “Barbarian Shan.” Then the Winged Pegasus said, “Winged Pegasus Yue.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Since we already have made our introductions, can you tell me why you suddenly started to fight the Divine Race?”

Chapter 826: Counter-attack Plan

Fei’er then said, “Ever since the Divine Race had conquered us, our races had been secretly accumulating strength. We were already prepared to deal with the Divine Race. However, the Divine Race is too strong. With our own strengths, we wouldn’t be able to overthrow the Divine Race’s rule. So we still didn’t make our move.”

Then Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “We initially didn’t think about cooperating with Mister. After all, Mister is from the Ark Continent. Everybody knew that the Ark Continent was a lower realm, incapable of making God-ranks. The one we wanted to cooperate with in the beginning was actually the Demon Race.”

Zhao Hai and Demon Dragon King nodded, they could understand Fei’er’s decision. Just as Fei’er said, the strength of the Ark Continent is just too low, they didn’t even have a single God-rank expert. However, who would’ve thought that a monster like Zhao Hai would appear.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Fei’er and said, “But how come you knew about the Demons? We don’t know about you.”

Fei’er replied, “From the Divine Race. The Divine Race hated the Ark Continent, however it was not easy to deal with the continent since it doesn’t allow the entry of God-ranks. Since the continent also had 9th ranks and it would be very expensive for the Divine Race to send their own 9th ranks, the Divine Race decided on using a magical formation to change the laws of the Ark Continent before coming in and eliminating the continent’s people.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he was already aware of this point. Then Fei’er continued, “However, this magic formation isn’t easy to set up. It’s possible that the Divine Race had already acquired this formation a long time ago. However, since it needed a lot of blood sacrifices, the Divine Race had never used it. Nevertheless, the Divine Race still continued to amass information about the Ark Continent. It was from that information that we knew about the Demon.” The Demon Dragon King nodded, it wasn’t surprising. In the past battle, the Demons also arrived. It would be completely normal for the Divine Race to know about the Demons.

Then Fei’er looked at the Demon Dragon King and said, “From that information, we had inferred that the Demons were strong. At the very least, much stronger compared to the Ark Continent. Because of that, we decided to cooperate with the Demons in dealing with the Divine Race. We’re confident in this proposal because we knew how greedy the Divine Race could be. With their knowledge of the Demons, it would be impossible for them to not think about conquering the Demon Realm. They certainly wouldn’t let the opportunity to expand go.”

Zhao Hai and the Demon Dragon King kept silent. They saw how the Divine Race does things. They were tyrannical and overbearing, they want each and every other plane to submit to them. What Fei’er assumed wasn’t at all strange.

Fei’er then looked at Zhao Hai and said, “But how could we imagine a powerful person like Mister to appear in the Ark Continent? You actually managed to block both the Demons and the Divine Race. To be honest, Mister’s strength made us very surprised.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and kept silent. Zhao Hai was a little proud about his strength. Then Fei’er continued, “When the Third Prince arrived in the Ark Continent, our plan went on a positive turn. The Third Prince immediately relieved Thunder Yun of his authority, this made Thunder Yun restless. Thunder Yun immediately sent me to gather information about the Divine Realm’s state. However, I didn’t immediately go to the Divine Race there. I went to the Barbarian and Winged Pegasus camps and told them to conserve their strength and not fight with Mister too much. Then later on, after I arrived at the Divine Realm, I discovered that there was no problem at all. All of this fuss was needlessly caused by that idiotic Third Prince. He thought of himself as clever and decided to use this opportunity to flaunt his useless talent.”

Zhao Hai and the Demon Dragon King were earnestly listening to Fei’er’s words. Upon hearing the last part, they looked confused. Fei’er saw their reaction and said, “I know the Third Prince. He didn’t have any good reputation in the Divine Realm aside from being favored by the King. He is not good in command and was someone who doesn’t receive criticism well. With him commanding the Divine Army only meant that they were not a match for Mister. This time, the Divine Race had sent around a third of its total army to the Ark Continent. If this army were to be eradicated, then it would be a huge damage to the Divine Race. Because of this, I made a secret visit to the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus to tell them about helping you. With your army blocking the Divine Race, we can get into an alliance and clean the Divine Race out.”

Zhao Hai nodded, just like Fei’er said, it was really a good opportunity to deal with the Divine Race. For the Divine Race to send a third of their army only meant that they really regarded this conquest with importance. Now that the army has been annihilated, the Divine Race should be suffering from huge damage.

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, now is the weakest point of the Taurus Divines and the best opportunity to attack. While Mister leaves the Ark Continent, our races would also leave our respective planes. We’ll besiege the Taurus Divines together. I believe we could completely wipe them out.”

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er with his knitted eyebrows and said, “But you must know that the Taurus Divines aren’t the only Divines in the Divine Realm. Altogether, there are 13 continents. Aside from the three controlled by foreign races, the other are all controlled by the Divine Race. If we attack the Divine Realm, then it’s possible that it wouldn’t be the Taurus Divines we’ll be facing. It’s possible that the Divines from the other continents would also give reinforcement. We are already troubled by a third of a continent’s army, not to say ten continents. Can we really block this? Did you have plans to deal with it?”

Fei’er stared, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai would already know about the state of the Divine Realm, he even knew about the 13 continents. However, this was still within Fei’er’s accepted range, so he nodded and said, “We’ve thought about it. Rest assured, the Divine Race isn’t as unified as it would seem. They also get into war with each other. If this wasn’t the case, the three foreign controlled continents wouldn’t have survived up until this point.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Please continue.” Fei’er gave a nod, “If we talk about the strength of the Divine Race, then we need to start talking about the Divine Realm’s structure. Of the 13 continents of the Divine Realm, the one placed at the middle is called the central continent. Surrounding the central continent are five continents arranged in a star-like manner. These five continents are the Leo, Gemini, Scorpio, Capricorn, and Cancer continents. The other seven continents surrounded these five continents namely; the foreign controlled continents, Aries, Virgo, and Libra, and the other four continents, the Taurus, Aquarius, Pisces and Sagittarius continents. However, despite being ruled by the Divine Race, these four continents aren’t harmonious with each other. Because of this, its possible that they won’t send reinforcements if we come and attack the Taurus continent.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows and then said, “It would be great if they don’t send troops. However, what do we do if they send reinforcements?”

Fei’er replied, “We have thought about this. Our Thunder Clan would send for the three foreign races to provide us with support. When that time comes, we shouldn’t be worrying about the other continents.

Zhao Hai was still frowning, “That wouldn’t be good. If we dealt with the Taurus Divines by ourselves, then the other Divines might not look too much into it. However, if the three foreign races were involved, then the situation would turn different. The Divine Race and the foreign races have always been enemies. If the foreign races send troops, then the other Divine would certainly do the same. When that time comes, the situation would be more difficult than imagined.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Fei’er couldn’t help but stare. Then his complexion changed as he lowered his head to think. What Zhao Hai said made sense. If they dealt with the Taurus Divines by themselves, then the other Divines might not look at it as significant. In any case, the other continents didn’t like the Taurus Divines. But if the Taurus Divines were to be attacked by the foreign races, then the other continents would find an excuse to send their troops. After all, that would essentially be an open invitation to conquer the Taurus continent.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and said, “We need to deal with the Divine Race without the help of the three races. Once we take control of the Taurus continent and have a stable foothold in the Divine Realm, contacting the three races wouldn’t be a big deal. Moreover, don’t forget that I can make undead out of those we killed. The more we kill, the stronger my army would be. When the time comes, my undead would have the same strength as the entire Taurus continent’s military strength. In addition to your races, we should be able to take firm control of the continent.”

Fei’er nodded, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “What Mister said is right. It seems like we thought too simply about this matter. Alright, we’ll go according to Mister’s plan. We will not contact the three races. However, this also means that the pressure on us would be greater, Mister should be prepared.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh and said, “I already expected this before. And now that I have your cooperation, our pressure should be lighter. The Ark Continent already has everything settled along with the Demons. The problem is with your three races. If your people are unable to endure, then it would be great for your race.”

Fei’er had a serious expression as he replied, “There’s no need for Mister to be worried about this. We are safely settled.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “That’s good. However, the date of our action needs to be pushed back. I still have things to deal within the Demon Realm. After I’m done, we can begin our move. What do you think?”

Fei’er knit his brows and said, “Do we need to wait for long? We should start the early. Although we had practically wiped out the Divine Race army here, there were still some people who managed to escape. They would surely go back to the Taurus continent and report everything, allowing the Taurus Divines time to prepare. Perhaps they might even withdraw their troops from the Ark Continent and deal with our three races. That wouldn’t be good for us.”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and then said, “We can still attack the Divine Race as usual, but I just have things to deal with myself. I won’t take long, just a few days. However, I can send the undead and the Demon Army to help you deal with the Divine Race in the Radiant Kingdom. What do you think?”

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So essentially, Mister would be the only one not present?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, only me. And I would only take a few days, I can finish this matter very quickly. I will come back as soon as I’m done. In the meantime, the undead and the Demon Army will accompany you.”

Fei’er nodded, “But Mister still needs to return quickly. You’re the only one who has a Domain Weapon on our side. On the other hand, the Divine Race had quite a number of Domain Weapons. Without you, we won’t be able to deal with the Divine Race army that easily.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I’ll return as soon as possible. When are you planning to attack the Radiant Empire? ”

Fei’er thought for a moment before he said, “We just passed through a battle, the army needs to recuperate. I think we need two days before we can attack the Radiant Empire.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, but from what I can see, you can advance towards the Radiant Empire while you recuperate. This can save you a lot of time. Perhaps I’ll be finished with my matters after you arrive.”

Fei’er nodded, “Alright, then we’ll start our trip now. However, I need to ask Mister for some help with supplies. In the past, our supplies were provided by the Divine Race. Now, we wouldn’t have anyone providing us with food.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “That wouldn’t be a problem. Look for a big city along the way and rest there. I’ll be sending the supplies shortly.”

Chapter 827: Broadcasts?

Although Fei’er didn’t quite understand why Zhao Hai was so confident, he was sure of one thing, that Zhao Hai was very strong and that he wouldn’t make any jokes about important matters. Because of this, Fei’er just nodded and didn’t say anything else.

However, the Demon Dragon King knew why Zhao Hai can assure such a thing. Yesterday, they just entered the Space from Demon City, but now they came out of the Accra Mountains. Only a fool wouldn’t note that the Space can teleport people.

What moved the Demon Dragon King the most was Zhao Hai’s statement about the matter he needed to handle. Now that nobody was left in the Ark Continent, the only thing Zhao Hai needed to do was head to the Demon Realm and take the Demons to the Space.

Fei’er smiled at Zhao Hai and nodded, “Alright, then we’ll be depending on Mister from now on. Since Mister has something to process, we’ll say our farewells for now. We’ll rest for the night and then proceed towards the Radiant Empire tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good. Right, I will also let the undead deliver you something. After all, you need to eat in order to have a good rest.”

Fei’er was moved, he stood and gave Zhao Hai a bow, “Thank you Mister. Since we also need to settle our troops, then we’ll be taking our leave.” Zhao Hai also stood up, he smiled at them and said, “There’s no need to be polite, aren’t we allies?” The three bowed to Zhao Hai once more before turning around to leave.

After waiting for Fei’er and the other two to leaves, Zhao Hai turned his head to the Demon Dragon King and said, “I’ll have to ask you to lead me to the Demon Realm. In the meantime, have the Demon Army enter the Space and recuperate. The most important thing for us right now is to take the other Demons to the Space.”

The Demon Dragon King gave Zhao Hai a salute and said, “Thanks Mister.”

Zhao Hai waved his hand an said, “Don’t be too polite, there’s no need for ranks between us. I’ve already ordered someone to take care of your food once you return. Have everyone take a good rest. Right, what are our casualties?” The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “From our tally, there are 544 thousand injured while about 650 thousand were killed. And since you requested it, they didn’t opt to explode themselves.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Although blowing themselves up causes huge damage, they won’t leave anything behind in the end. I want to pay respects to their sacrifice by burying them.

Zhao Hai still had his Chinese personality in him. Although he didn’t admire being buried in the earth, he still wanted to leave a body behind after he died. Even if he was cremated, that would still be good. At the very least, he didn’t want to only leave his clothes behind.

The Demon Dragon King shook his head and said, “Mister, if it’s possible, please turn the dead Demons into undead. It would be a great honor for them if you do that. Being buried in the ground would just turn them into a joke.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the Demons would have that custom. He frowned as he asked, “Won’t you explode yourselves before being defeated?” The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “If we are defeated, then we would blow ourselves up in order to die with the enemy.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he said, “If I turn your people into undead, then you won’t get offended?” The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “We won’t. Mister can rest assured. Being able to fight after dying is a dream for a Demon. But since we don’t want to die under the hand of our enemy, we just blow ourselves up. Only when we have a formidable lich with us would we refrain from killing ourselves.”

Zhao Hai found that he was unable to make sense out of the Demon Dragon King’s words. In his mind, being turned into an undead was blasphemous to the body. But it seems like it was a good thing for the Demons. Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Alright, then I’ll be turning those killed into undead. I’ll leave it to you to arrange the Devil Legion.” Then the Demon Dragon King nodded before he turned around and left.

Although the Demon Dragon King had already left, his words were still resonating inside Zhao Hai’s mind. At this time, the Space’s residents were getting more and more multiracial. There would be races whose customs and manners were unique to Zhao Hai. Since these people had their customs weaved into their society, Zhao Hai changing it would only cause dislike. Because of this, Zhao Hai needed to be sensitive to such matters and respect these peoples’ beliefs.

Although the Space can slowly transform a person’s thoughts and make them loyal to Zhao Hai, a process was still needed in order to do so. Moreover, Zhao Hai was afraid that if he were to gain their dislike then it would be very difficult to gain these people’s loyalty.

In fact, Zhao Hai didn’t guess wrongly. If he changed the customs of the Demons, then he would definitely earn their dislike. In that case, if the Space wishes to make them loyal to Zhao Hai, then it would take a very long time. A person needed to have good sentiment towards Zhao Hai in order to be influenced. But if that person was Zhao Hai’s enemy, then the Space would find it very difficult to change his mindset. The only quick way to do so was to turn that person into undead.”

After the seeing that the Demon Dragon King had left, Laura and the others walked over and sat beside Zhao Hai. Laura then said, “Brother Hai, can we really stage an attack on the Divine Realm?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This would be the best opportunity to do that. If we give up, then we would be jeopardizing the plans painstakingly made by the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and Winged Pegasus. In any case, having them on our side would make it easier to fight against the Divine Race.”

Laura nodded and said, “I think this matter is going on too quick. With Fei’er and the others added to the mix, our plans seem to have been pushed forward.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and said, “Those fellows are crazy for revenge. It’s fine, we can still cooperate with them. After all, their fighting strength isn’t that weak. With our strength added, not to say the Taurus Divines, even if the other races sent their troops, it would be hard for them to eradicate us.”

Laura smiled and said, “Your being too polite. They can’t destroy us at all, it’s basically impossible. Just you alone can turn the Divine Race into turmoil. Right, Brother Hai, what happened to those you captured? The Third Prince seems to have gotten retarded.”

Zhao Hai knit his brows and said, “I had them placed on a small island near the Ark Space. There’s no need to provide them with food, the island should be enough to sustain them. Let them stay there for a while as they think about their current situation.”

Laura didn’t comment anything more. After all, those people had zero ability to rebel. Also, there’s no reason for Zhao Hai to kill them. Moreover, the Third Prince had already turned stupid from the mental impact he just received. If the maids weren’t there to take care of him, then he would’ve already died of starvation.”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Alright, let’s return to the Space and deal with post-war matters. Right, had the final battle been broadcasted?”

Laura knit her brows and said, “We didn’t. It’s because we were fighting alongside the Demons. What, do we have to show it?”

Zhao Hai thought for a short moment and said, “Show it. In any case, we can’t hide this matter. After showing the scene, tell the people that we have defeated the Divine Race and also subdued the Demons.”

Laura frowned and said, “If we do it like that, then let’s have Cai’er broadcast the state of the Underworld as well. This way, people wouldn’t think that we were cheating them into living inside the Space.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he understood why Laura proposed that action. The people had indeed transferred to the Ark Space, however, they still remember their life on the continent quite fondly. If they think that there’s no need to defend the Ark Continent, then they might develop some ideas. They might assume that Zhao Hai was exaggerating and just lured them into the Space. After all, Zhao Hai managed to smoothly eliminate the Divine Race while drawing the Demons on his side. If it was hard, then things wouldn’t have been that easy.”

Zhao Hai returned to the Space and thought about his recent victory. Altogether, he had amassed 30 million undead Divine Race soldiers. Adding on his current undead, Zhao Hai now had about 70 million undead in his command.

Originally, Zhao Hai’s undead should be more than this. However, the Divine Race’s attacks were too fierce, some undead were forced to use blood lightning beads to blow themselves up. With this method, Zhao Hai would only have a net loss since all bodies would be vaporized by the explosion.

But in the end, Zhao Hai still managed to reap great harvests. This elevated Zhao Hai’s military strength. Don’t forget, a lot of God ranks were present in the army. This caused Zhao Hai to have more God-rank undead compared to before.

However, Zhao Hai held great regret for not capturing Thunder Yun and turning him into undead. This was because Thunder Yun received Fei’er and the Thunder Clan’s final attack, turning Thunder Yun straight into ash. In that state, it would be impossible for Zhao Hai to turn him into undead.

Although he felt pity about this, Zhao Hai still had other matters to think about. He first went to the Space to prepare the food for Fei’er’s people. But since doing this would take a lot of time, Zhao Hai handed the matter over to Laura and the others. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was currently inside the Demon Race’s background.

Chapter 828: Choosing A Place

The Demon Dragon King brought the Demon Army back to the Space. Naturally, they wouldn’t do so in front of Fei’er and the others. Instead, Zhao Hai opened a rift right behind the Accra Mountains to make it seem like they entered the defensive line.

After entering the Space, the Demon Dragon King’s group immediately smelled something nice. The Demon Dragon King turned his head to see  many large pots on top of fires boiling meat soup. The soup’s fragrance filled the entire place.

The Demon Dragon King gawked. At this time, Moqiao and Shidak arrived by the Demon Dragon King’s side. They gave a salute before Moqiao said, “Demon Dragon, we apologize. While you were fighting outside, we already ate first. These things are prepared for you.” The Demon Dragon King looked at the large pots and smiled, “That’s a lot of meat. Did Mister send them to you?”

Shidak smiled as he nodded, “Mister sent it to us. Demon Dragon, aside from those Bread Fruits, there are also plenty of magic beasts. Those magic beasts aren’t strong, however, they reproduce very fast. They can certainly provide enough food for us. This Space is indeed very good.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, then he said, “This Space is naturally good. Otherwise, His Majesty wouldn’t have agreed to Mister Zhao Hai’s proposal. Once all of the Demons move here, we would enjoy blissful lives.”

Moqiao agreed, then he said, “We’ve made a more thorough investigation of the Space. Everything inside is very good. It has green grass, clear waters, magic beasts, and even more bread fruits. Even if all the Demons make it here, there won’t be any shortage of food. With all of the things here, it would be impossible for us to become hungry.”

The Demon Dragon King stayed silent, then he looked towards the Devil Legion and said, “Those wounded should get yourself treated. After that, you come out to eat before taking a good rest. We still have to fight in the next few days.”

The soldiers from the Devil Legion complied as they turned around and got treated. Those who weren’t injured went to a riverbank and washed themselves and their garments.

In the Space, these people could fully relax themselves. They wouldn’t need to worry about being attacked. For the Devil Legion, this was a very rare experience.

The Devil Legion being killing gods wasn’t false. These people were battle maniacs and were constantly fighting everywhere. Because of their special state, their  mindsets were cold and were always alert to their surroundings.

But in the Space, they had found themselves to feel strange. Here, besides their clansmen, there were no other enemies nor any strong magic beasts to threaten their existence.

Actually, they weren’t aware that the Space also had a slight healing effect. This healing also affected their battle addicted minds.

However, since the illness that the Devil Legion suffered was very serious, the healing would need a very long time before effects can be seen. Because of this, the Demon Dragon King didn’t particularly notice it. The Demon Dragon King also went towards the river to wash his face before going towards a pot close to him. He took a taste of the meat soup before turning to Moqiao and said, “Moqiao, your people are really good at this. The soup tastes very good.”

Moqiao took a bread fruit and then said, “This is completely because of the materials Mister gave us. Moreover, in this Space, the pile of commodities didn’t only appear here. There were also piles on many other places. With this amount of supplied, we could fully re-establish our homes.”

The Demon Dragon King took a bite of the bread fruit pulp and took a sip of the meat soup. After chewing for a moment, he said, “As I thought, Mister is quite thorough. Although we are presently united, it is still impossible for all Demons to live with each other. In the end, we would need to live in different places. Now that there are supplies in various places, our people would have their own place to choose from. Right, you still need to take charge of the people here. In two days, I will be bringing Mister with me to the Demon Realm.”

Moqiao nodded, then he said, “I have already sent people from different races out today and let them choose a place for their people. If they like it, then they can settle down. It would be much better for them if they get to know of their environment before the rest of their people come in.”

The Demon Dragon King placed his  soup bowl down, he knit his eyebrows and said, “Right, will this cause any conflict? What if two races decide to live in the same place?”

Moqiao smiled and said, “It will be fine, there won’t be any problems. In the Demon Realm, people only went to war with each other because there isn’t anything much in their own domains, so they wanted to claim a better place for themselves. However, things are different in the Space. Everywhere is abundant in resources. Moreover, there are also different strong points in each place. Take this place for example, this place has a lot of Bread Fruits, however there aren’t a lot of magic beasts here. On the other hand, places up in the north don’t have a lot of bread fruits but they are abundant in grass, allowing a lot of magic beasts to thrive. Everyone has their own customs, so they would naturally pick different places.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded, then he let out a long sigh and said, “It seems like the Demons have found their dreamland. Right, in the next few days, Mister Zhao Hai will dispatch troops to make an attack on the Divine Realm.

Moqiao stared and said, “That fast?”

The Demon Dragon King smiled and said, “It’s not that fast. Mister Zhao Hai is working with other people this time so he doesn’t need that much soldiers and we also won’t lose anything.”

Moqiao smiled and said, “That isn’t what I’m worried about. I think Mister Zhao Hai is working too hard. Think about it, hasn’t he been idle every since we arrived in the Ark Continent? If he wasn’t fighting with us, then he would be fighting the Divine Race. And now that the Underworld had come, he became even more busy.”

The Demon Dragon King replied, “How could he not be busy? After all, he is fighting for the Ark Continent. Now, he is faced with the three big races from the Divine Realm, the Thunder Clan, the Winged Pegasus Race, and the Barbarians. They wanted to attack the Divine Realm and pull Mister Zhao Hai in to participate. And don’t forget, Mister has a big enmity with the Divine Race. He certainly wouldn’t let this opportunity go.”

Moqiao nodded and didn’t speak anything more. The Demon Dragon King took a few munches of his food before he said, “His Majesty made the right decision to send the Devil Legion. Otherwise, we would have lost face for the Demon Race. There’s no need to say about how strong Mister’s undead were. And now there is the Thunder Clan, the Winged Pegasus, and the Barbarians, they’re more formidable than we thought. If we sent our other soldiers, then we wouldn’t have any face left to show Mister Zhao Hai.” Moqiao smiled bitterly and said, “It seems like we have underestimated the Divine Realm. We thought that they were on our level, but now it seems like they are far stronger than us.”

Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “That’s true. In the beginning, we thought that the Divines are our equal. As it turns out, those who came to the Ark Continent only belonged to one continent out of 13 continents in the Divine Realm. Among those 13 continents, three of them are controlled by foreign races while 10 of them remained under the control of the Divine Race. The ones attacking the Ark Continent is merely a branch of the Divine Race, the Taurus Divines.”

Moqiao didn’t expect this, his complexion changed as he knit his brows and said, “Did Mister know about this?”

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “He knows, and it seems like he had known for a long time.”

Moqiao frowned, his brows became tighter as he said, “Mister is already aware of this yet he still wants to attack the Divine Realm? This is totally unlike his character.”

The Demon Dragon King smiled faintly and told Moqiao the reason. After talking, the Demon Dragon King added, “Because of this, we need to have our people move as soon as possible. We can’t have them drag Mister for long.”

Moqiao nodded and said, “So it was that. It’s surely a good opportunity. However, it would be impossible for Mister to take the entire Demon Race in a short period of time.”

The Demon Dragon King shook his head and said, “It should be possible. I think Mister already has an idea on how to proceed. The Space is a mysterious thing, I don’t believe it would have no solutions.”

Moqiao nodded, “Demon Dragon, have you sent a letter to his Majesty? At the very least he should know about the current situation.”

The Demon Dragon King knit his brows and said, “I still don’t have  a fast way to do so.”

At this time, a voice suddenly sounded out, “What’s wrong? You want to send word to the Great Demon King?”

Both Moqiao and Demon Dragon turned their heads to see Zhao Hai standing behind. The two immediately gave Zhao Hai a salute before Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Be at ease. I came here since I saw some food. I haven’t eaten yet so I want to try some. Right, Demon Dragon, this is for you. You can use it to contact His Majesty at any time.” Then Zhao Hai took a messenger fish and gave it to the Demon Dragon King.

The Demon Dragon King was also aware that Zhao Hai didn’t like too much politeness, so he received the messenger fish and thanked Zhao Hai before turning back. Then Zhao Hai took a bowl of meat soup for himself before he sat down and made conversation with Moqiao. Although Zhao Hai was being casual, Moqiao still felt pressure. After all, Zhao Hai was their benefactor, he couldn’t just act casually all of a sudden.

There are differences in one’s status no matter what each party says. People talking to their equals would naturally be more casual and might even develop friendship with each other. However, when one with superior status converses with average people, an intangible pressure can still be felt no matter how casual the superior person acts.

Chapter 829: Environmental Awareness

Fei’er was currently sitting with his people, surrounding a heated metal pot. Their meal was the same as the Demons, meat soup and bread fruit. All these things have been sent earlier by the undead.

Although these things looked ordinary,  Fei’er didn’t think so. Where was this? This was the frontline. There might not be any problems having pots in the frontlines. However, how could an army acquire fresh meat at a place like this? Moreover, it was nice and warm. Wasn’t this strange?

Additionally, Fei’er had a certain understanding of Zhao Hai in the past few days. He managed to block both the Demons and the Divine Race. And not only did he destroy the Divine Race army, he even got the Demons for himself.

To be honest, when Fei’er saw Zhao Hai leading the Demons to battle, his heart couldn’t help but stop.

The Demon Race, that was the Demon Race! Fei’er was  planning to propose an alliance with the Demons before they deal with the Divine Race. In his opinion, the Demons had the strength to oppose the Divine Race. And now, that same Demon Race has actually been subdued by Zhao Hai. This was too inconceivable.

Fei’er can only use one sentence to describe Zhao Hai’s abilities, flipping the hand to gather clouds, and covering it to stop the rain. This was precisely because Zhao Hai had this ability that Fei’er decided to ask Zhao Hai for cooperation. He believed that with Zhao Hai’s abilities, then there won’t be any problems in dealing with the Divine Race.

Fei’er looked at the distant Barbarians and Winged Pegasus. In the past, these people haven’t even heard of each other. But now, they were all solid allies. They were one in their goal, and that was to no longer be under the control of the Divine Race.

Fei’er was aware that this goal wasn’t easy. He knew a lot about the Divine Race, so he knew how hard it was to escape from the Divine Race’s grasp. The Taurus Divines alone can exterminate the Barbarians, the Winged Pegasus, and the Thunder Clan. But although the Taurus Divines had this ability, it still wasn’t the strongest continent in the Divine Realm. There were still stronger Divines, and any one of them can eliminate the Thunder Clan many times over.

Because of this, not only do they need to pay attention to the Taurus Divine, they also need to listen for the movements of the other continents. Even if they managed to deal with the Taurus Divines, the other continent could still attack and subdue them.

Because of this, Fei’er thought about having an alliance with different races. This would allow them to have a proper foothold in the Divine Realm and hopefully deter the other continents from sending reinforcements.

However, Zhao Hai had exposed a major flaw in this plan. If the three races got into an alliance, then they would definitely attract the attention of the other Divines. When the time comes, the Divines would send troops to exterminate the three races.

After thinking about this, Fei’er couldn’t help but break into a cold sweat. However, he still sent word back to the clan to have them prepare according to the original plan. This was done in the hopes that they would have enough time.

Because of this, he settled on inviting Zhao Hai. Fei’er thinks that cooperating with Zhao Hai was the best  decision.

But in the end, Fei’er still needed to ascertain Zhao Hai’s ability. Although he wasn’t aware about what Zhao Hai needed to do in the next few days, Fei’er knew that it must be related to the Demons. Fei’er wanted to see how Zhao Hai delivers on his promise. If Zhao Hai does a good job, then Fei’er would fully cooperate with him. If Zhao Hai had problems in feeding them, then Fei’er would have reservations in their cooperation.

Although Fei’er’s status wasn’t the member with the highest status in the Thunder Clan, he is after all the person next in line to be the leader. Actually, this status was brought about by Thunder Yun. With the loyal Fei’er acting as the leader of the Thunder Clan, Thunder Yun would have more power over them.

Unfortunately for Thunder Yun, Fei’er was an actual bomb placed beside him. Fei’er was truly the person next to be the Patriarch. When Thunder Yun administered the position, the Thunder Clan immediately agreed. This turned the Thunder Clan into obedient people in front of Thunder Yun. This caused Thunder Yun to have the Thunder Clan as his personal guards.

Fei’er being the next in line to be patriarch wasn’t because of his strength. Instead, it was because Fei’er was intelligent. Because of this, the Thunder Clan sent him to be by Thunder Yun’s side.

It was precisely because of this status that Fei’er still had some pull in the Thunder Clan. Otherwise, the Thunder Clan wouldn’t have agreed to cooperating with Zhao Hai.

At this time, the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus people also have their own thoughts. Although they have a custom of thinking of their undead brethren to be the same as alive, they were still a bit angry at Zhao Hai. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have sent their elites to the Ark Continent.

However, this small hatred wouldn’t hinder their cooperation with Zhao Hai. The current matters was more important than past grudges. Most importantly, their hatred for the Divine Race completely dwarfs Zhao Hai’s action.

Zhao Hai didn’t know about any of these. After spending some time with the Demons, Zhao Hai returned to his villa and looked at the monitor. At this time, the Thunder Clan and the others were resting. Zhao Hai closed the monitor and then looked for Laura and the others only to find out that they were busy as well.

Presently, the Space had a lot of commodities. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of supplying the Demons as well as the Thunder Clan and the others. After all, if this can move their hearts, then why not?

The matters that Laura and the others were busy with weren’t a lot. They just need to send supplies to the Demons and the others, they didn’t need to worry about the Divine Race.

After seeing that Laura and the others were almost done, Zhao Hai turned around and headed to the kitchen to prepare some food.

Zhao Hai hadn’t gone in the kitchen for a long time. Back on earth. Zhao Hai was a greedy eater. Not only did he like to eat, he loved to cook as well.

At that time, his job was at home writing drafts. This gave him a lot of free time. In order to relax himself, he would cook. This allowed his cooking skill to be good. Naturally, he couldn’t compare with those great chefs, but even so, his home cooking was still acceptable.

After he finished cooking, Laura and the others were also done with their work. When they saw that Zhao Hai had prepared food for them, they were startled. Zhao Hai looked at their reactions and then smiled, “Alright, no need to be shocked. Come over and eat.”

Laura and the others immediately went to washed their hands before sitting on the table. Although Zhao Hai’s dishes weren’t as delicious as Meg’s, they were still quite good.

After seeing their faces, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile bitterly. He always thought that he had been unfair to his wives. Fortunately, they didn’t blame Zhao Hai. Otherwise, Zhao Hai  wouldn’t have known what to do. If they became angry at him, then Zhao Hai would have no other choice but to hole up inside his room in the Space.

After the group ate, they went to sit inside the living room. Zhao Hai looked at the others who were rubbing their bellies and said, “My food isn’t that good. There’s no need to eat that much.”

Laura and the others rolled their eyes as they decided to not respond. At this time, Cai’er cam flying in and said, “Young Master, today’s events have been broadcasted to the people in the Space. There was a huge reaction but nobody blamed you. Do you also want to broadcast what happened next?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment and said, “Show it. Let them know about our current situation. Right, in addition to the plan, tell them that I would be going to the Demon Realm tomorrow. Tell them about the Demon Realm’s situation to let them know how bad the environment was.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai in confusion, she said, “Brother Hai, do we need to do this? You really don’t need to say good things about the Demons.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s not like I want to praise the Demons, I just want the people to know the state of other places aside from the Ark Continent and the Space. Later on, when we go to the Divine Realm, we’ll also broadcast our trip. There are too many people in the Space and there really isn’t anything else  to do. At the very least, we can provide them with something to pass the time.”

After thinking about it, Zhao Hai ruminated about the idea of televisions and movies. Those two were good avenues for propaganda.

Laura and the others didn’t think that this was bad, instead they thought that it was too troublesome. But since Zhao Hai wanted to push through with this plan, they didn’t oppose.

The group was somewhat tired today so they rested early. What they don’t know was the fact that their broadcasts had kept people up all night.

Just as Zhao Hai said, people in the Ark Space lacked things to do. And with Zhao Hai’s battles being better than any movie, the people naturally would be hooked to it for a long time.

After the battle ended, the projection showed Zhao Hai and Fei’er’s negotiation.

Then the projection changed and showed the Beastman Prairie. The dark mist and undead could be distinctly seen. This also gave the people understanding about why Zhao Hai took them to the Space.

It can be said that the influence of this broadcast was huge. This made all of the races in the Space have an understanding about the Divine Race and the Demons, especially the Divine Race. These people didn’t think that the Divine Race would be this formidable. Moreover, there seems to be more than ten continents in the Divine Realm.

With how the broadcast was shown, the people were able to understand Zhao Hai’s position. This ignited a sense of gratitude towards Zhao Hai.

When all of the content was done, the sky was already turning bright. The people felt dizzy so they immediately went to sleep. However, the contents of the broadcast was still replaying in their mind.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai woke up. He had breakfast in the villa before asking Laura and the others to take care of the food for Fei’er and the others. At the same time, Zhao Hai went to the Demons and prepared to head towards the Demon Realm with the Demon Dragon King.

To be honest, Zhao Hai was very curious about the Demon Realm. Although Cai’er already provided him with ample information, Zhao Hai was still very interested in seeing it for himself. He wanted to see what the environment really was.

By the time Zhao Hai arrived at the Demon Space, the Demon Dragon King and the other Demons were already up. While the Demon Dragon King was waiting for Zhao Hai, the other Demons were actually busy with other matters.

After seeing Zhao Hai arrive, the Demon Dragon King immediately went forward and gave a salute, “Mister, you came. When do we leave?’

Zhao Hai looked at the busy Demons and smiled, “We can leave immediately. Right, if there’s anything you need, then don’t forget to tell me. I will certainly find a way to provide.’

The Demon Dragon King looked grateful as he said, “Thanks mister. If it’s possible, we would like to ask for some stones. Can you provide us some?”

Zhao Hai stared, he looked puzzled at the Demon Dragon King’s request. He looked at the Demon Dragon King and said, “Stones? You want me to give you stones? There are a lot of mountains in this Space and there are stone deposits there, you can just take it for yourselves.”

The Demon Dragon King embarrassingly replied, “Mister, to be honest, the place is so beautiful that we are afraid to damage it. If we mine the mountains, then the trees might die. We, we can’t do that.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare blankly before smiling bitterly. It seems like the Demons were really affected by their bad environment. Now, it seems like they were completely concerned in preserving their new place. But this is also good, it means that they wouldn’t destroy the Space.

After seeing that Zhao Hai didn’t respond, the Demon Dragon King thought that Zhao Hai had gotten angry, so he quickly said, “It’s alright if mister can’t do it. After we return to the Demon Realm, I can have the Demons harvest some stones there and then bring them back to the Space.”

When he heard the Demon Dragon King, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, then he said, “That’s also fine. How about this, since I have a lot of idle undead, I can have them help you gather some stones. What you said is right, the Space is indeed beautiful, it would be great if it doesn’t get destroyed.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai’s reply, the Demon Dragon King happily agreed. After their conversation, the Demon Dragon King immediately brought Zhao Hai to the Demonic Abyss before they flew towards the Demon Realm.

Chapter 830: Poisonous Grass Is Also Useful?

It was a blood red world!

The sky was red, a deep shade of red, looking like viscous blood. Naturally, since it was daytime, the sun was also up. However, this sun looked like it was wrapped in red film. The light that the sun projected was a faint dark red, it was completely different compared to the daylight in the Ark Continent.

Besides this dark red sky, there was also a reddish black land. It looked like deserted landscape. There were some low lying plants here and there. Although they had green leaves, the shade of green wasn’t something normally seen in plants.

Although the grass looked like the ones in the prairie, Zhao Hai could feel that the grass were clumps of poisonous snakes growing out of the ground, looking for an opportunity to bite.

Aside from the grasses, one could also see some stones and sandy soil. The Demon Realm looks like there was nothing inside it. Even if one could see some trees, they weren’t tall enough nor big enough to be described as so. The entire atmosphere exuded a depressing feeling.

At this time, the Demon Dragon King lightly sighed before he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, just a few words of advice. Don’t underestimate the grasses of the Demon Realm. Some of these poisonous grasses hold poison that can even kill God-rank experts.”

Zhao Hai turned to the Demon Dragon King with a puzzled expression. The Demon Dragon King continued, “In the Demon Realm, almost all plant life is poisonous. The only difference between their poisons is the intensity. The reason why we eat the seven colored vine in the Demon Realm was because it had the least toxicity out of all the plants here. And although two grasses looks similar, one could be virtually harmless while the other can kill you instantly.”

Zhao Hai stared before he gave out a sigh, “No wonder the Demons wanted the Ark Continent, the environment is indeed terrible!.”

At the same time, the conditions of the Demon Realm was also broadcasted to the people in the Space.

At this point, the people in the Space were already used to looking at the broadcasts every day. The contents of the broadcast today startled them. They have never seen an environment like this. The people in the Space thought that the display was showing hell.

However, after the voice came, they understood that this wasn’t hell, instead it was actually the Demon Realm!

Now, the people in the Space already knew about the Demons being allied with Zhao Hai. For the people in the Space, this was exciting news.

They didn’t have much dislike of the Demons. This was mainly because in the battle against the Demons, Zhao Hai was the one doing the most fights, the losses to the Ark Continent wasn’t very big.

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of this as he and the Demon Dragon King flew forward. There are only the two of them, there were no escorts.

Zhao Hai looked all around the Demon Realm and saw that the overall situation was quite similar. They even saw one or two Demons who wanted to attack them. Fortunately, those Demons weren’t able to fly, otherwise, things would be annoying.

Their speed wasn’t fast, as Zhao Hai was looking around, he turned to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Where do you live?” The Demon Dragon King replied, “The capital. That is the Demon Realm’s biggest and most fortified city. Most importantly, sealed below the city is the largest spatial rift between the Demon Realm and the Underworld.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “How long does it take for us to reach the capital?”

The Demon Dragon King quickly replied, “It wouldn’t be long, about two hours. If we go slow, we would arrive in four hours.”

Zhao Hai hesitated for a moment before he waved his hand. Before long, a big hand appeared and grasped a clump of grass then sent it to the Space.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai in confusion, he didn’t know what he was planning to do. Actually, Zhao Hai just wanted to see how different this grass was compared to ordinary ones.

Just as the grass entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Fierce toxin detected. Dark attribute grass. Not suitable for growing in the Space. Not suitable for growing in ordinary backgrounds. Suitable for growing inside Hell background. Helpful in improving Hell background.”

Zhao Hai was stunned when he heard this prompt. He didn’t really think that this place would grow in the hell background. This was a surprise for Zhao Hai.

The Demon Dragon King looked at Zhao Hai and discovered a smile on Zhao Hai’s face. The Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but ask, “Mister, did something good happen?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Something good arrived. Right, can you have the other Demons help me in collecting plants and magic beasts from the Demon Realm? It doesn’t matter if they are poisonous or not. Moreover, they need to be alive.”

The Demon Dragon King stared blankly, then he asked, “Why does Mister want to collect these things? Do they help you with something?” Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Right, they have some use to me. Moreover, if those poisons are used well, then I might be able to make good medicine. So what do you think? Can you help me?”

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “No problem. When we see His Majesty, we can ask those who will go to the Space to bring some plants and beasts along with them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Right, plants and magic beasts. However, there’s no need to go out of their way. We don’t want them to be hurt by aggressive magic beasts or get poisoned by plants.” The Demon Dragon King smiled and said, “Mister, rest assured, nothing bad will happen. We Demons have lived in the Demon Realm for so many years. Unless it is a large beast tide, they won’t pose a threat to us.’

Zhao Hai nodded, “Good, then it’s settled. Let’s go and see His Majesty, I want to see how far the migration has progressed. After all, our time is too short.” The Demon Dragon King smiled and said, “There’s shouldn’t be any problems. With His Majesty in charge, the whole Demon Realm should already be prepared.” Zhao Hai smiled and didn’t say anything else. After that the two accelerated their flying speed.

While on their way, Zhao Hai also encountered small settlements. These settlements weren’t very large. It seems like they house about a thousand to a hundred thousand people. Although these places were small, their walls were very thick and high. All of them seem like fortresses. The Demon Dragon King pointed at those small towns and said, “Almost everyone in the Demon Realm lived in places like these. Since there are a lot of magic beasts in the Demon Realm, one would certainly meet groups of them in the wild. If one doesn’t live in places like these, then they would have a very small chance of surviving.”

Zhao Hai nodded and gave a slight smile. To be honest, the Demon Realm was really the worst place he’s ever seen. He was even sure that the air was poisoned. It was only because the Space had an antidote that it didn’t bother telling Zhao Hai about the toxicity in the air.

At the same time, Zhao Hai also understood why the Demons grew up the way they were. It was due to the bad environment. In order to suit their environment, they needed to adapt.

Survival of the fittest! This was the rule of nature. And this rule was completely driven into overdrive in the Demon Realm. The Demons needed to undergo through generations of evolution just so they could survive. In the end, they arrived at their current appearances.

Two hours after they sped up, Zhao Hai could finally see a giant city in the distance. This city was no worse than any capital in the Ark continent. With dark red stones being used to construct it, the city looked very majestic.

While the two haven’t even arrived at the capital, they could already see the Devil’s chariot outside the city. Zhao Hai immediately knew that this was the Great Demon King coming to welcome him. The two immediately headed for the chariot to give their greetings. Before long, Zhao Hai can see the Great Demon King waiting for him.

Upon seeing Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King laughed and said, “I didn’t think Mister would deal with the Divine Race this quickly. This calls for celebration, Mister, please come inside.” Zhao Hai wasn’t overly polite, he immediately entered the chariot after giving a salute. The Demon Dragon King also quickly went after them.

Zhao Hai entered the chariot and saw that the decorations inside were still the same. There was still the small table with dishes and a pot of liquor.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then sat at the small table along with the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King. After everyone has settled, the Great Demon King looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister had just defeated the Divine Race army, but you still chose to come here. I have to thank Mister for this.”

Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “It’s nothing. In any case, the others still needed some time so I just chose to come here. Right, has everything been prepared?” The Great Demon King smiled and said, “Almost ready, as long as Mister opens the spatial rifts, the Demons can immediately move to the Space.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then he said, “Right, I have something to trouble Your Majesty. I want to collect plants and animals from the Demon Realm. I hope Your Majesty an assist me with this.”

The Great Demon King stared, then he knit his eyebrows as he replied, “Does Mister know the specific things he wants?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Not too many requests. First, they need to be alive. Second, the more varieties the better. Naturally, there’s no need gather those that are dangerous to acquire.”

The Great Demon King relaxed and said, “This is easy. When can Mister open the spatial rift?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I can open it any time. I just saw some Demons going towards the capital. How about this, I’ll open a spatial rift here and have those Demons enter. Then after that, I will leave my blood ghost staff behind. Your Majesty can carry my staff to the different cities. As long as you go there with the staff, then I would be able to open my spatial rifts. With this, everyone shouldn’t be subjected to dangerous migration paths.”

The Great Demon King gawked, then he nodded and said, “That would be best. Mister can open the spatial rift right now, I will immediately have the Demons enter the Space.”

Zhao Hai didn’t object, he nodded before he waved his hand and opened a huge spatial right just outside the capital.

Chapter 831: Unknown Future

The Great Demon King didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this fast. He stared for a moment before he laughed, “Alright, mister moves very quick. Then I will have to be impolite. Mister, please stay here for a moment while I arrange my people.”

When the Great Demon King stood up, Zhao Hai did the same as he said, “Your Majesty, I won’t be staying here for long. I have to go back to the Space and arrange some things. I’ll leave my blood ghost staff here so you can take it with you. Just use the messenger fish to contact me and I’ll immediately open a spatial rift. Demon Dragon can stay here with you. There won’t be any battles in the next few days, he can help you relocate the other Demons.”

The Great Demon King looked at the staff in his hand. The staff was currently in its skeleton form, it wasn’t a staff used by most people. However, the Great Demon King knew the significance of this staff to Zhao Hai. Being handed the staff moved the Great Demon King’s heart.

The Great Demon King nodded and said, “That would be best. Since mister has something else to do, then I won’t hold you here for long. Me and Demon Dragon can take care of everything here.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Then I’ll bother Your Majesty with this. The Space has been prepared, your Majesty can rest assured.” The Great Demon King gave another thanks. Then Zhao Hai left the chariot and then flashed back to the Space.

The reason why Zhao Hai left quickly was because he needed to talk with Fei’er and the others. No matter what, they were still allies, being in constant contact with them would be good. This way, they would have better coordination in the future.

Originally, Zhao Hai wanted to take his time in the Demon Realm. And since he didn’t want to reveal a lot of things, he didn’t think about handing the blood ghost staff over to the Great Demon King.

However after further thinking, all of the Demons would enter the Space, so handing the blood ghost staff over to the Great Demon King would be more than enough. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to give the blood ghost staff to the Great Demon King so that he can leave and contact Fei’er and the others.

Just as Zhao Hai entered the Space, Laura and the others were currently looking at the monitor. The image displayed on the monitor was the state of the Demon Realm. To be honest, they didn’t think that the Demon Realm would be as bad as this.

After they saw that Zhao Hai had come back, Laura and the others immediately went forward to greet him. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you’re back? Didn’t you that you would stay in the Demon Realm for a couple of days?”

Zhao Hai replied, “There is no need for me to be there, I couldn’t offer further help in transferring the Demons. It would be better if I get in touch with Fei’er’s group instead. Right, I also left the blood ghost staff to the Great Demon King.”

Laura stared, then she nodded and said, “Leaving the staff with the Great Demon King is also good. In any case, the staff could map the Demon Realm.’

Zhao Hao nodded, then he asked, “How are Fei’er and the others doing? Did anything significant happen?”

Laura shook her head and said, “Everything is very normal. We’ve already sent them their meals, they ready to eat.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he sat on the sofa and let out a long breath, “How about the Ark Space? The people have seen the condition of the Demon Realm, what response did they have?”

Laura smiled and then said, “There’s no excessive reaction. People seem to not be very disgusted by the Demons. They just look at the Demon Realm as though it was a story.”

Zhao Hai felt relied, he said, “It’s good that they aren’t angry. I thought I need to spend some time to improve their view towards the Demons, it seems like there’s no need for that. Right, send me outside, I want to have a chat with Fei’er.”

Laura nodded, then Cai’er waved her hand as she sent Zhao Hai to a city in the Buddha Empire. It wasn’t a big city so it couldn’t house several tens of millions of soldiers. Majority of the army rested outside the city. Still, there was no problem regarding food. As for Fei’er and the others, they took their rest inside the city.

Zhao Hai directly appeared in the city, causing the attention of the surrounding soldiers to focus on him. After they saw Zhao Hai, one of them immediately went to Fei’er to report.

Zhao Hai didn’t block them as he just waited there in place. Before long, Fei’er came, Shan and Yue were absent.

However, Zhao Hai can also understand why this was the case. He killed so many people from those two races. Although the custom of those people saw the undead as another form of life, a thread of hatred was still present. Therefore, it was an appropriate move if those people don’t meet him.

At this time, Fei’er arrived by Zhao Hai and gave a salute, “I didn’t think mister would see us today, wasn’t mister quite busy?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I found some time to visit. Let’s go in and talk” Fei’er nodded and led Zhao Hai to the place where he rested, which was the city lord’s mansion.

There wasn’t anything inside this mansion, after all, Zhao Hai already took everything out of the Ark Continent. Although the mansion looked quite spacious, it was only due to it being empty.

However, it was also great the Fei’er and the others were quite capable people with formidable bodies. Because of this, they didn’t care about resting in this place. Fei’er didn’t even sleep in the bedroom, there was no need to do so since there was no bed.

After entering the empty hall, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile. He turned to Fei’er and said, “Mister Fei’er, I apologize. The things in this mansion has already been taken by me.”

Fei’er smiled faintly and said, “No problem, we’re already quite used to it. Right, why did mister come today? Is there anything you like to talk about?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Mister Fei’er, what opinion does the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus people have on me?”

Fei’er didn’t expect Zhao Hai to ask this question, he couldn’t help but smile bitterly. The Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus did indeed have some reservations towards Zhao Hai. However, Fei’er believed that they wouldn’t take revenge against Zhao Hai. This was because there was still a bigger enemy in the horizon.

And now that Zhao Hai asked, he didn’t know what to say. Zhao Hai saw Fei’er’s expression and sighed, “I know that they have some bad outlook towards me. After all, I can’t deny killing their own people. However, I hope that this wouldn’t affect our cooperation.”

Fei’er quickly replied, “Mister can rest assured, the cooperation wouldn’t be affected.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he said, “I have no choice at that time. I didn’t know that they weren’t part of the Divine Race. I expected them to be part of the Divine Race army.”

Fei’er looked confused at Zhao Hai. In their previous discussion, Zhao Hai seemed to know a lot about the Divine Realm. Normally, he shouldn’t be able to know about the Divine Realm’s matters.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and smiled bitterly, “Did you wonder why I’m very familiar with the Divine Realm?”

Fei’er nodded, Zhao Hai forced a smile and said, “Don’t forget that I’m a dark mage. After killing the Divine Race and turning them into undead, I can ask them about the matters of the Divine Realm.”

When Fei’er heard Zhao Hai, his eyes suddenly showed his understanding. He actually forgot that Zhao Hai was a Dark Mage.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and said, “Although I knew about the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus, my knowledge isn’t that much. The Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus haven’t been conquered in a day or two, so I wasn’t aware that they still held their resentment towards the Divine Race. When they planned to attack the Ark Continent, I can’t risk my people being killed. Because of that, I had no choice but to kill them.”

Fei’er nodded, he can understand Zhao Hai. To be honest, if Zhao Hai held back against the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus at that time, then the Ark Continent wouldn’t have been in its current state. Instead, the Ark Continent would have already fallen to the Divine Race. Moreover, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have been here to become their ally. Most importantly, Zhao Hai was very strong, it would be strange if he doesn’t go for the kill.

From what was said before, Fei’er didn’t intend to become allies with Zhao Hai, instead he wanted to invite the Demon Race. If Zhao Hai wasn’t strong, then they wouldn’t have been speaking at this time. Strength decides everything, this was something that Fei’er completely understood.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er’s expression and said, “This time, we need to quickly deal with the Divine Race, we can’t be slow. North of the Ark Continent is a rift to the Underworld. Undead from the Underworld have already come out of the rift. If we delay, the undead and the Divine Race might attack us from both sides. That wouldn’t be good for us.”

Fei’er nodded, his expression was somewhat heavy. Although he believed that they had the strength to deal with the Divine Race, he still didn’t underestimate the Divine Race. There were still 9 other Divine Race continents in the Divine Realm aside from the Taurus Continent. What reaction would the other continents have? This remained unknown. All their previous discussion was merely speculation.

If the other continents sent reinforcements towards the Taurus Divines, then things would be extremely difficult. All 9 continent’s doesn’t even need to send reinforcements. As long as a form of reinforcement came, then things would still get more difficult.

Chapter 832: Transformers? Mecha? What!?

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So Mister’s plan is?”

Zhao Hai replied, “We must attack, as soon as possible and in the shortest time. We need to attack the Taurus Divines while they still have a hold on their continent. This way, we lessen the chance of other continents joining the fight.”

Fei’er knit his brows and said, “Of course, it would be best if we attack immediately. However, if we are too aggressive, then we might exhaust our resources. If the other continents come, then we won’t have any energy left to resist.” Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “It would be worse if we don’t attack. The Divines should have already acquired the news by now and had gone to prepare themselves. If we don’t go at them hard, then things would be more troublesome for us.”

Fei’er thought for a moment and then nodded, “We don’t have any problems with that. And just like you said, the Divines should have already heard of what happened here and have been prepared. However, at this time, I still have no way to get in touch with my people. There’s no way for me to tell them about our decision. I’m afraid they won’t be ready to cooperate when the time comes.”

Zhao Hai thought about it and then said, “When we enter the Divine Realm and make our initial attack, you could use that opportunity to contact your people. Right, I’ll give this to you. This is a messenger fish, you can call me on this thing. If anything happens, use it.”

Fei’er gawked as he received the messenger fish. Fei’er looked curiously at the small fish. Zhao Hai didn’t say anything for a moment before he took out two messenger fishes and gave them to Fei’er, “Help me hand these two messenger fish over to the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus army. In any case, we are on the same side now.”

Fei’er nodded and received the two messenger fishes on Zhao Hai’s hand. Then he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “This Fei’er really admires Mister’s heart. Mister, rest assured, I will surely make Shan and Yue disregard any grudges between you and them.” Zhao Hai gave a forced smile and then said, “That won’t be easy. Right, Mister Fei’er, I don’t know if you have any good weapons to deal with the Divine Race. If you want, I can give you some blood lightning javelins.” Fei’er gawked, then his two eyes shone as he replied, “That would be great. Mister’s blood lightning javelins are more overbearing compared to the blood lightning beads that the Divine Race had.” Zhao Hai smiled faintly, but just before he was about to reply, his expression suddenly changed. Then he stood up, looked at Fei’er and said, “Mister Fei’er, I will prepare the javelins. When we fight the Divine Race, I will immediately send them over to you. I still have some matters to take care of, so I can’t remain here for long.”

After Fei’er saw Zhao Hai’s expression, he couldn’t help but stare for a moment. However, he also stood up and said, “Alright, then I won’t hold mister here.” Zhao Hai nodded before his figure vanished and appeared inside the Space.

The moment Zhao Hai appeared in the villa, he saw Laura looking at the screen. “What’s wrong?”, Zhao Hai said. Laura smiled bitterly as she replied, “Cai’er saw something. Ever since the underworld appeared in the Beastman Prairie, she made sure to scan the entire continent using the Space’s map. Today, she managed to discover something unusual on Blazing Island.”

Just as Laura said that, Zhao Hai shifted his attention towards the screen. The screen was currently showing the image of Blazing Island. However, what he saw on the island made him astonished.

Blazing Island had volcanoes everywhere. Living among those volcanoes were various fire element beasts and plants. Although Zhao Hai took the fire crystals as well as the river of earth fire, the temperature of the island was still quite high. On the dormant volcanoes, one could even see beasts moving about here and there.

But now, something completely out of place appeared on the island. Not only does it not belong to the island, these things doesn’t belong to the Ark Continent. They were huge metallic men!

Zhao Hai inspected these metallic men. They was over ten meters high and looked delicately made. Their components were shining and most importantly, there were all kinds of magic formations drawn all over their body.

When Zhao Hai saw these magic formations, his pupils couldn’t help but shrink. At this point, Zhao Hai already had some understanding about the formations in the Ark Continent. However, Zhao Hai still couldn’t identify the magic formations on these metallic men. The magic formations were too complex.

At this time, Cai’er talked, “Young Master, the Space had recorded something that happened before. Come and take a look.” Then the image on the screen changed into the same Blazing Island. But this time, there were several black spots seen on top of the island. These black spots moved very fast and before long they reached the island. Zhao Hai unexpectedly identified these black spots, they were aircraft!

Zhao Hai could swear that his eyes weren’t wrong. They were indeed aircraft. Zhao Hai stood up from his seat as he looked closely at the figures on the monitor.

After that, an exciting even happened. After flying around the island, the aircraft suddenly twisted its form. It’s metallic parts moved before forming into a huge metallic man!

Zhao Hai’s eyes almost went out of their sockets. Seeing these aircraft gave Zhao Hai excitement. This was because he only saw these kinds of aircraft back on Earth. The aircraft made him think that there might be a connection between Earth and the Ark Continent.

However, that idea soon faded when the aircraft transformed. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head. This aircraft was obviously a transformer! What is going on!?

Under the feet, in the middle of the palm, and at the back of these figures were flames shooting out. Before long, they slowly landed on the island.

When the magic beasts and flame demons spotted these metallic figures, they immediately charged in to attack.

However, these transformers just lifted their hands and shot out white lights towards the attackers. Almost immediately, the magic beasts let out a miserable cry before their bodies totally disintegrated. The flame demons might have resisted for some time but they too were erased by the white light.

Then the transformers made a fist and withdrew their attack. After that, their chests opened up and men came out of the metallic bodies.

As soon as he saw this, Zhao Hai understood. These weren’t transformers at all. These metallic men were machines controlled by people. Just like mechas that were written about back on Earth.

However, most of the mechas seen on novels were purely made out of technology. On the other hand, these mechas actually had a lot of magic formations. What is this?

Even more surprised than Zhao Hai were Laura and the others. They had no prior experience about these things. Because of that, they were all shocked by what they saw on the monitor.

Zhao Hai slowly sat down and closed his eyes. Then suddenly, something flashed inside his mind. He had read about something similar before, iron golems!

These things were indeed similar to the iron golems that he read before. However, these machines were more complicated in comparison. This caused some doubts within Zhao Hai’s mind.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and summoned a God-rank Divine. Then Zhao Hai beckoned towards the screen and said, “You, have you seen these things? Or maybe heard about them? What are those things?”

The God-rank Divine looked at the iron golems and then said, “I saw something similar. In the past, the Goblins used to make these things. However, those made by the Goblins weren’t this defined. Moreover, they act very slow and weren’t too useful. As for exactly those, I really haven’t seen them before.”

Zhao Hai stored the undead back before he let out a long breath, “It seems like another new plane has connected to the Ark Continent.”

The women looked at each other and saw the surprise on each others’ eyes. These things were quite new to them. Moreover, these metallic beings were very powerful. One must know that the beings in Blazing Island were almost 9th rank in strength. But even in their situation, they still couldn’t stop the metallic beings.

Laura and the others can also understand Zhao Hai’s current feeling. This matter was truly quite annoying. They were yet to find a way to deal with the Underworld but now another plane came. Zhao Hai was currently feeling like he was being bullied by fate!

Laura let out a sigh as well as she said, “Yet another plane connected to the Ark Continent. What happened to the Ark Continent? Did it’s barrier really got damaged that far?”

The group smiled bitterly. They held the same feeling as Laura. It seems like the Ark Continent’s barrier had been rendered useless.

Zhao Hai suddenly stood up and said, “I’ll go see them. I want to see whether I can communicate with them. If we could talk, then I’d ask how they arrived at the Ark Continent.”

The expression of the women immediately changed. Laura looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, it’s better if you don’t go. It’s too dangerous. You saw the attack made by those people, they’re too strong.”

Zhao Hai patted Laura’s hand and said, “Rest assured, nothing bad will happen. With my current strength, those people could do nothing to me.”

Naturally, Laura was quite confident in Zhao Hai’s strength. However, the attacks made by those mechas were just too strange. There was a white light and then the magic beasts just disintegrated. This wasn’t an attack that they had seen before.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “I’ll be fine, don’t worry. I promise you that the moment they attack, I will immediately go back to the Space.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and knew that there was no way to prevent Zhao Hai from knowing. Therefore, she just said, “Brother Hai, if they decide to attack, then immediately go back. Don’t fight with them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Rest assured, I will be safe. Alright, I’m going now.” Then Zhao Hai’s figure flashed as he went out of the Space. Laura and the others immediately turned their attention back to the screen to look at Zhao Hai’s situation.

Zhao Hai didn’t directly appear on Blazing Island. Instead, he appeared a distance away and then flew towards the island.

Zhao Hai saw that the skill of these people wasn’t that high. One could say that their strength was mainly dependent on the mechas. At this time, these people were resting on the island, outside from their iron golems. One could say that they couldn’t provide any threat to Zhao Hai.

ZHao Hai slowly flew towards the island. At the same time, he also instructed Cai’er to pay attention to the actions of those people. They seem to be resting on the island, leisurely talking and laughing there.

When Zhao Hai was not far from the island, these people finally moved. They quickly ran towards the iron golem and then started them up. However, they didn’t make a move as they just stood there and waited for Zhao Hai.

After being informed about this, Zhao Hai didn’t stop. Instead, he even sped up. He knew that this people doesn’t intend to attack him. It was for certain that they also wanted to know where this was. Therefore, they would want to communicate with him.

Before long, Zhao Hai arrived on Blazing island. He also saw the huge mechas. However, he didn’t show the fact that he had seen them before. Instead, he showed a shocked and curious appearance.

He slowly descended on the island as he stared at the mechas. When he was about a couple of steps away, he stopped. Then he proceeded to circle the mecha looking like someone who just discovered something new, ignorant about the fact that it might be dangerous.

Naturally, Zhao Hai was just acting out a play. He wanted these people to think that he had just accidentally came here to see these mechas.

While Zhao Hai was doing his thing, the person inside the mecha couldn’t wait anymore as a sound came out, “&#%@…”

After hearing this, Zhao Hai’s heart suddenly sank. This was because he couldn’t understand what this person just said. If there’s a language barrier, then it would be difficult to communicate. It might even result in some misunderstandings between the two parties.

However, Zhao Hai continued his play as he made a scared expression and loudly said, “What are you? How did you appear on Blazing Island?”

Zhao Hai knew that the opposite party would be unable to understand his words. However, this action still needed to be acted out.

Chapter 833: Atlanta Plane

The other party turned silent. While Zhao Hai was wondering about the other party’s reaction, a voice suddenly came from the mecha, “Hello, where is this place?”

What was heard was definitely the language of the Ark Continent. However, the tone was very awkward. It was just like how foreigners sound when they first studied chinese.

Zhao Hai stared blankly, he didn’t think that these people could actually speak the Ark Continent’s language. He looked at the mechas in front of him and asked once more. “Who are you? How did you appear on Blazing Island?”

Naturally, these people had seen Zhao Hai descend from the sky, therefore they didn’t dare underestimate him. The huge metal figures immediately arranged themselves into a row before one of the chest plates swung open. A person walked out and went forward to greet Zhao Hai. He placed his hand on his chest as he gave a short bow and said, “Mister, I am the captain of the fifth squad of the Atlanta Continent’s Flying Armor army. Eagle squad leader Axe. We arrived here by going through a spatial rift. Mister, where is this?”

Zhao Hai looked at Squad leader Axe and then returned the salute as he said, “Hello, this place is called Blazing Island, south of the Ark Continent. I am Ark Continent’s Buda Clan Patriarch, Zhao Hai Buda.”

Axe looked at Zhao Hai and said, “So it is Patriarch Zhao Hai. Patriarch, please feel at ease. We didn’t come with hostile intentions. Sir, please come and take a seat.” Then Axe took a few steps forward before arriving at an open area. Zhao Hai looked at the mechas standing there before he followed Axe and then sat down.

After Axe sat down, he turned his hand and took out two pieces of dried meat. He gave on of them to Zhao Hai and said, “Since we’re far away from home, I don’t have anything delicious to offer. I hope the Patriarch wouldn’t laugh at my dried meat. Please have a taste.”

Zhao Hai looked at Axe’s smug look and smirked inside. Axe seems to be proud of his spatial item. Zhao Hai smiled faintly before he also turned his hand to take out two bottles of beer. He gave Axe one of the bottles before he said, “Since we’re out here in the open, why don’t we drink some liquor? I also want mister have a taste of my Buda Clan’s special beer.”

When Axe saw Zhao Hai take out two bottles of beer, his pupils couldn’t help but shrink. Zhao Hai might not know about it, but spatial items were also very rare in the Atlanta Continent. Although Axe was just a squad leader, his identity wasn’t simple. The reason why he himself had a spatial item was because he was the heir of a Great Clan in the Continent. Since he loved adventure, he took the chance to enter the spatial rift along with his men.

Naturally, the people who came with Axe weren’t ordinary people. All of them were famed experts in the Atlanta Continent. Their magic armors were among the advanced ones in the army.

Since Axe had his current status, he felt the need to show off the fact that he held a spatial item to Zhao Hai. He wanted to see Zhao Hai’s reaction.

In the mind of Axe, Zhao Hai doing things on his own despite being a Patriarch only meant that Zhao Hai’s family wasn’t strong. In turn, Zhao Hai should not have the position to hold a spatial item. If Zhao Hai sees his spatial item and reveals his greed, then Axe would have the excuse to be impolite to Zhao Hai.

However, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai himself would also have a spatial equipment. Moreover, it seems like Zhao Hai treated these items as though they were nothing significant.

Axe couldn’t help but smile bitterly inside. He wanted to test the other party but in the end he came up with nothing. So Axe just received Zhao Hai’s bottle of beer before taking the top off and taking a drink.

However, it was quite obvious that Axe wasn’t used to drinking beer. He only took a sip and frowned slightly before he placed the bottle at the side. Then he took a bite out of his dried meat before he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Patriarch, you said that this is the Ark Continent? May I know the continent’s structure?”

Zhao Hai observed Axe. From Axe’s performance, it showed that he wasn’t just any ordinary squad leader. His every move and speech was controlled, obviously showing that he had undergone etiquette training. It seems like Axe’s status wasn’t low.

After hearing Axe’s question, Zhao Hai didn’t mind hiding things. Although he couldn’t reveal the continent’s current state, he can just tell Axe prior knowledge.

Zhao Hai paused for a moment before he replied, “We are at the Ark Continent. The continent is mostly comprised of one large landmass. Where we are today is called Blazing Island, a small island south of the continent. The island has volcanic eruptions all throughout the four seasons. The island has strong fire beasts and flame devils. Because of this, it was named as one of the continent’s forbidden areas. The humans in the Ark Continent are divided among five empires; the Radiant Empire, the Buddha Empire, the Lyon Empire, the Rosen Empire, and the Aksu Empire. Besides the five empires, there are also four other races. There sea’s Fishman race, the prairie’s Beastmen, iron mountains’ Dwarves, and the Elven Forest’s Elves.”

Axe eagerly listened to Zhao Hai’s introduction. After Zhao Hai’s statement, Axe asked once more, “Patriarch, which Empire does your family belong to? Do you have a lot of enemies in the continent?”

Zhao Hai sported an arrogant expression as he said, “My Buda Clan is the continent’s most powerful family. I myself am a hereditary marquis of the Rosen Empire and the strongest 9th rank expert.”

Axe had a confused expression as he looked at Zhao Hai, “Patriarch, the strongest people in the continent are 9th ranks? How can you determine a person’s strength?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “The Ark Continent’s professions are divided into two, namely warriors and mages. And both of them are divided into 9 levels, from 1st rank to 9th rank. You advance by improving your own strength. Once you receive the blessing of the heavens and granted flight, then you can be said to be a 9th rank expert.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, Axe’s eyes shone, then he said, “So it’s that. I didn’t think that there would also be warriors and mages in the Ark Continent.”

Now it was Zhao Hai’s turn to ask, “So mister means that there are also warriors and mages in the Atlanta Continent?”

Axe proudly lifted his chin as he replied, “Right. However, the professions in our continent are divided into three; warrior, mage, and magic armor master.”

Zhao Hai took a glance at the mechas and said, “These magic armors are truly mysterious. Metallic beings this large are actually able to move. It’s quite astonishing.”

Axe couldn’t hide his arrogance, “Naturally, these magic armors are the product of several thousand years of research. Their fighting strength is formidable. However, becoming a magic armor master isn’t that easy.”

Zhao Hai looked at Axe and asked, “It seems like the Atlanta Continent is more formidable than my Ark Continent. Can mister introduce me to the Atlanta Continent?”

Axe looked at Zhao Hai and snorted, “Originally, the Atlanta Continent is one large piece of land. After a huge war, the continent is divided into three continents; the warrior continent, the mage continent, and the magic armor master continent. Where I’m from is the magic armor master continent. Since childhood I’ve been immersed in the research and manufacturing of magic armors. However, there are also children who studied as either the warrior path or the mage path since childhood. The experts of our three continents are divided into 12 ranks. It is somewhat different to the Ark Continent, but it has similarities. After becoming 9th rank, one would be able to fly. Moreover, ranks ten to twelve have many times more strength compared to 9th ranks.”

Upon hearing Axe’s explanation, Zhao Hai concluded that the Atlanta Continent was the same type of plane as the Demon Realm and the Divine Realm, planes a cut above the Ark Continent. Ranks 10 to 12 should correspond to Demigods, Gods, and Saint Gods. It seems like the Atlanta Continent wasn’t so simple after all.

Zhao Hai also noticed that the way Axe talked to him had changed. Axe suddenly became high sounding that it made Zhao Hai feel uncomfortable. However, Zhao Hai didn’t say anything, he just kept listening to Axe’s babble.

After Axe’s explanation, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister might not believe it, but the magic armor of my squad are all 9th rank transforming armors. Let me show you.” Then as Axe waved his hand, his magic armor spouted blue flames on its foot, palm, and back. The metal armor flew up into the sky as it folded itself and transformed into an aircraft before zooming out into the horizon.

Zhao Hai looked at this in shock. Although he had seen the magic armor’s transformation on the screen, the impact in seeing it in person was too strong.

Now that he sat in front of this transforming mech, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. This caused him to have a dumbfounded look.

Axe paid close attention to Zhao Hai’s appearance. After seeing Zhao Hai’s reaction, Axe couldn’t help but laugh deep inside. At the same time, he also felt proud of his magic armor.

Axe didn’t reveal this information, but the strength of the Atlanta Continent was also quite formidable. Their research towards magic formation was extremely profound. And like the Divine Race, the people in the Atlanta Continent had also managed to conquer several planes.

Since they were still unaware of how strong the Ark Continent was, they were polite upon arriving. But after Zhao Hai revealed the state of the continent, Axe knew that the plane he was on was inferior compared to the Atlanta Continent. Because of this, his plan became more and more obvious. At this time, Axe was thinking that after he went back, he would immediately request his clan to dispatch troops and conquer the Ark Continent!

Chapter 834: Mutual Plan

Among the things that Axe withheld was the fact that there were no countries in the Atlanta Plane. Instead, families hold the power over everything. And also, Axe’s family was the most famous family in the Magic Armor Master Continent, the O’Neil Family. Finally, Axe was to be the O’neil Family’s next Patriarch.

In the Atlanta Plane, the power held by families was extremely inflated, they could even reach the same as those held by Empires. Under those Great Clans were other small families that serve them. Moreover, if a family conquers a plane, then that plane would become their own territory, further increasing the strength of that family.

But although the O’Neil family was the most famed family in the Magic Armor Master Continent, they were still yet to conquer a plane. This caused their strength to be inferior to other Great Clans.

The Atlanta Plane was different from the Divine Realm. The Divines were able to know which planes were around them. And once they know the plane, they would also know how to go there. Because of this, the Divines could just break that plane’s barrier and then proceed to conquer it.

On the other hand, the Atlanta Plane doesn’t have that ability. They don’t know whether there were any planes close to them, in turn, they won’t know where those planes were. Because of this, it would be difficult for them to seek a plane and conquer it.

The people in the Atlanta Plane would just set up a magic formation on a random place and hope for the best. This magic formation would only activate once a plane’s barrier was close. Otherwise, the magic formation would just ruin itself.

In the past, the Atlanta Continent had conquered planes using this method. However, the O’Neil family was quite unfortunate. They had arranged these magic formations many times, however, they were yet to get lucky in finding another plane. These actions brought losses to the family. One must know that arranging these magic formations wasn’t cheap. Otherwise, everyone would arrange these formations everywhere.

This time, the O’Neil family finally got their lucky break. Several days before, Axe heard a report from his subordinate that a spatial rift had appeared in a remote mountain valley inside the O’Neil family’s domain. Moreover, the rift was getting bigger and bigger.

After hearing this report, the entire O’Neil family was shaken. Their first thought wasn’t happiness, instead it was fear. They were afraid that a high-level plane had found them and broke through the plane’s barrier. They thought of this because this was the same as what they did to the lower planes.

Because of this, the O’Neil family immediately barricaded the mountain valley. They also blocked information about this rift from coming out. While the family was contemplating on what to do, Alex’s adventurous side rose up. He took his strongest and most loyal men with him and entered the spatial rift. Thus, they appeared on the Ark Continent.

Upon arriving on the island, Axe immediately felt relief. If this spatial rift was arranged artificially, then people would’ve been present on the other side of the rift. It would be impossible for those people to just leave their rift in the middle of nowhere.

However, Axe didn’t immediately send word back to the family. He wanted to take a look at this new plane first. Because of this, he immediately commanded his men to fly around randomly. Just as they were travelling southward, they came upon Blazing Island. It was here that they were detected by Cai’er.

Axe wanted to talk to Zhao Hai because he wanted to know the strength of the Ark Continent. If the Ark Continent was strong, then the O’Neil family would establish a business cooperation with them. However, if they were weak, then Axe would go back to his family and prepare for an invasion of the Ark Continent.

After getting the continent’s strength from Zhao Hai, Axe immediately knew that the opportunity has come for the O’Neil family. The Ark Continent was so weak that the O’Neil Family could easily usurp them.

Because of this thought, Axe’s tone got more and more arrogant as his conversation with Zhao Hai went on. Zhao Hai had met people like Axe before, so how could he miss the change of tone on Axe’s voice. However, Zhao Hai didn’t care. What he revealed to Axe was the original state of the Ark Continent. Naturally, the present Ark Continent was completely different compared to before. If Axe had any bad ideas for the continent, then it was his own fault for miscalculating.

After a short while, Axe’s mech went back and landed. Zhao Hai looked at the mech with envy as he said, “These things are truly wonderful. If the Rosen Empire had these, then we would have already conquered the rest of the continent. Mister Axe, i wonder if you can sell me a few of these. I just went forward to see the path and my fleet would be arriving in two days. Initially, we came to Blazing Island in order to get some special products to refine medicine with. I shall wait for my fleet to arrive. When they dock, I will approach mister for the trade. I will buy your magic armors no matter what price mister Axe wants.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Alex’s expression couldn’t help but change. It took a moment for Alex to calm down before he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, this request, I can’t promise something to you right now. I need to head back to the family and discuss things, I’m sure they would be interested in the trade. If the family agrees, then we will send someone over to find you. What do you think?’

Zhao Hai had a regretful expression as he replied, “That’s a pity. Well, take this, this is my clan’s token. If mister’s family agrees to the trade, then you can bring this token to the Rosen Empire. When that time comes, my Buda Clan would definitely give you a warm welcome.”

Axe received the thing that Zhao Hai handed over. From what he saw, it seems like a token made out of red crystal. It looked very refined. On the token were two characters that read ‘Buda’.

Axe didn’t suspect anything as he held the token and said, “Alright. Mister, I’ll immediately head back to the family and discuss this matter. I can assure you that we’ll be swift in our reply.” Zhao Hai nodded. Then Axe jumped into his mech as him and his team proceeded to fly southward.

Zhao Hai looked at Axe’s departing back. He sneered before his figure vanished and returned to the Space. Laura and the others were currently in the living room, their expressions quite difficult to behold. When Zhao Hai came, Laura immediately said, “Brother Hai, I hate that man. It’s obvious that he has bad ideas for the Ark Continent. His fake expression is too irritating to watch.’

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine, there’s no need to be angry. I told him that I have my fleet behind me in order to see his reaction. If he doesn’t have any ill will towards us, then he would definitely stay and talk. But it seems like he did have bad ideas. If I hadn’t told him that I have my people behind me, then he would’ve already killed me in order to suppress the news. After all, his party mostly consisted of 9th ranks. If he isn’t sure that he can kill me and my fleet, then he wouldn’t act rashly.”

Laura coldly snorted and said, “Just let them come. In any case, their presence would only make the Ark Continent even livelier. I want to see what their expression would be when they face the Divine Race and the Underworld.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Actually, this is also an opportunity for us. Once they appear in the Ark Continent, then that would be the best time to declare war on the Divine Race. When they arrive, we can slowly whittle them down. At that time, we would be able to obtain a batch of powerful magic armors. That would surely increase our strength.”

At this time, Lizzy frowned and said, “Big Brother Hai, I’m sure you’ve also heard Axe say that their plane has experts up to 12th rank. In other words, God-ranks also exist in their plane. Their attack surely wouldn’t be weak. Can we deal with them?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “No matter which plane, strong experts are surely rare. Those at the top are the least populated group. Also, I don’t believe that Axe’s family is more powerful compared to the Taurus Divines.”

Lizzy also thought of the same thing. No matter which race, it would be impossible for them to surpass the strength of the Divine Race. If God-ranks were that abundant, then the Ark Continent would’ve already fallen a long long time ago.

Lizzy looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, what’s the deal with that token? Why do I feel like it’s the same as the blood ghost staff?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “You’re not wrong. That is a part of the staff. I wanted to try and see if I can separate a part of the staff from the main body. That small part would allow us to monitor the person. I didn’t expect that the experiment would be a success. Cai’er, show us the state of that fellow.”

Cai’er immediately complied and changed the image on the screen. The display showed a very small space. Inside this space was a person wearing a type of helmet. There was also some kind of contraption attached on this person’s arms and legs. Moreover, it can be clearly seen that this person was Axe.

Chapter 835: Free State

Laura stared, her eyes widened as she said, “So that’s how those magic armors were operated. Interesting, interesting.”

On the other hand, Zhao Hai’s pupils narrowed. He saw a lot of things from Axe’s setup. Although Axe’s way of controlling the mech was very bizarre, but you have to say that it was actually very convenient. Mechas aren’t usually controlled this way, that’s why ordinary people were unable to pilot them. It seems like the people of the Atlanta Plane had truly developed their magic armors to the extreme.

The image showed Axe controlling his mech to fly at a very fast speed. Since there was nothing else that happened, Zhao Hai decided to change the image to the Thunder Clan.

Zhao Hai had only spoken with Fei’er for a moment before he was interrupted with Axe’s arrival. At this point, Zhao Hai doesn’t know what Fei’er was doing.

After the image changed, Zhao Hai saw Fei’er hurrying along. And since nothing happened, Zhao Hai shifted the image once more towards the Goblins.

Once the image changed to the Goblins’ background, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. At this time, the background had changed. Below the massive bread trees were small houses. Although small, they were beautifully constructed. Zhao Hai carefully inspected the houses and saw that they were made out of straw and mud. The decorations on the houses were made out of bread fruit shells.

Zhao Hai turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, what things have these Goblins traded? I want to see.”

Cai’er complied as she pulled out a detailed list. There were some ordinary tools and nothing special. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but nod, it seems like these Goblins were quite smart. Otherwise, they wouldn’t have been able to make these houses with these simple tools.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Good. Right, Cai’er, how were the Goblins doing lately? Did they only build houses?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “No. Young Master, you don’t know but there are still some Goblins who were educated. At this time, those with knowledge were educating those who didn’t know anything. Inside the houses they built were magic formations. Those formations were quite clever, they actually made the houses quite comfortable.”

Zhao Hai changed the image and looked at the rooms of the Goblins. There really were magic formations inside, moreover, they looked very well-made.

Zhao Hai nodded, then he smiled and said, “It looks like my idea is correct. These Goblins aren’t the same as those in the Atlanta Plane. Their inheritance has been destroyed by the Divine Race. If they kept developing, they might have become as strong as Axe right now.”

Laura stared, then her two eyes shone as she said, “Brother Hai, you mean those Goblins can make those magic armors that Axe and the others used?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes. Initially, I want to have those Goblins research this technology. Now that Axe has appeared, it gave me the opportunity to see how advanced the magic formations are. It seems like it needed to be studied for many years. The Goblins are talented in this aspect. Let’s just have them study magic formations and maybe they can make something great.”

Laura nodded, “That would be good. Now that the Goblins have been freed, their knowledge can now flourish once more. Making complex magic formations shouldn’t take too long.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “With how the Goblins have been treated, it was now close to impossible for them to pass their inheritance down. Their magic formations look quite good, but it can be seen that their entire knowledge is still broken. If an average race had reached their point, then I’m afraid they won’t recover. The Goblins being able to maintain their current state is amazing enough.”

Lizzy and the others agreed. The Goblins’ resilience was really something worthy of admiration. For them to still pass some of their knowledge down despite being suppressed by the Divine Race was a very great matter.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I initially thought that they had zero knowledge of their civilization, so I refrained from showing them magic formations from the Ark Continent. It seems like my plan needs to be pushed forward. Let’s have some undead mages teach the Goblins some words and knowledge regarding magic formations. Right, Laura, how is father-in-law doing nowadays?”

Laura smiled and said, “Father is still researching the defensive magic formations. I reckon he’ll complete it soon. Why? Do you need him for something?”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but stare. He had asked Karen to research defensive formations before mainly to defend against the Demons and the Divine Race. But now that the Ark Continent has moved to the Space, these things were now not needed. In the end, Zhao Hai had forgotten about this task. Zhao Hai didn’t expect Karen to still continue with this research, moreover, they were even close to succeeding.

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “This is my fault. I actually forgot about this. Tell father-in-law to take a rest. He’s been exhausted these days. Now that our strength is enough, there’s no need to use that formation.”

Laura smiled and said, “I already told father about this. But father said that he would still do it. He said that he’s very interested in these things. Let’s just let him be. In any case, we have people looking after him and he’s still taking a rest from time to time.”

Zhao Hai nodded, then he turned to Laura, “Laura, once father-in-law is done with this research, tell him to stop studying for some time. I want him to compile his knowledge so that we can make a book out of it. We can use those books to teach the Goblins as well as the people in the Ark Space. We’ll have everyone start researching themselves, what do you think?”

Laura’s eyes showed his agreement, she said, “Good, that would be great. Father always wanted to do that but the people of the Ark Continent doesn’t take magic formations too seriously. They always see magic formations as secondary needs. Even if father printed his book, I’m afraid people wouldn’t even take a look at it. Now that there’s a purpose, I think he will be happy to share his knowledge.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then turned his head to Cai’er, “Cai’er, scan the formations on the magic armor that Axe used. I want to compile them and have father-in-law look at it in the future. Laura, you also need to take care of father-in-law. He’s not young anymore, he needs to refrain from being exhausted.”

Laura smiled and said, “Rest assured, father has been well taken care of. Although he likes his research, he hasn’t been going all out recently. Moreover, this is what he likes to do, if he is forbidden to work, then it would be like torture for him. Also, he’s now a 9th rank expert, so his lifespan should already be long. Just have him do his thing, there won’t be any problems.”

Zhao Hai nodded and didn’t say anything else. Karen’s current body has been really good. In addition to the environment, the food and water in the Space adds up to the benefits that he gets. Currently, Karen looks younger and more energetic compared to before. Zhao Hai couldn’t even describe him as an old man anymore.

After arranging this matter, Zhao Hai turned the image on the monitor towards the underworld’s creatures in the Beastman Prairie. The undead seems to have advanced further.

Zhao Hai looked at the undead and couldn’t help but sigh. The advancement of these undead has been too fast. At this time, they had already occupied two-thirds of the Beastman Prairie. Moreover, their advancement was still going on.

It was fortunate that the people in the Ark Continent had already moved out. This reduced the headaches that Zhao Hai felt. Zhao Hai opened another screen showing the state of the Northern Icefield. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get shocked by what he saw. The Space’s monitoring capabilities seem to have improved.

Before he met the Divine Race, they would place a magic formation everytime they go on a meeting. Because of this, the monitor would just display a white scene. This was the same for the underworld’s fog, the Space couldn’t penetrate deep inside it.

Because of these, Zhao Hai knew that the Space’s monitor had many limitations.

However, just now, Zhao Hai discovered that the monitor’s penetration distance seem to have increased. Zhao Hai didn’t expect this to happen.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but look at Cai’er and said, “Cai’er, it seems like the monitor has been improved.”

Cai’er had a smug look as she nodded and said, “So Young Master has noticed. When the Space levelled up, the monitor’s abilities have also been strengthened.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You couldn’t blame me for this. I’ve been too busy to take note of this. Hahaha. Good, it’s great that it improved. Later on, we can spy on anything we like.”

Cai’er smiled as well, “I also have something else that will make Young Master happy. The ingredients in the magic backgrounds can now be used. By my calculations, they should be enough to make ten God rank potions. Moreover, the output of these ingredients would slowly increase. And most importantly, crops grown on the magic background can quickly replenish our supply of gold goins. When the time comes, Young Master can buy those remaining backgrounds.”

Zhao Hai clapped his hands, “Fantastic! Finally we can get rich. Having no money really affected my confidence. That’s good. Right, Cai’er, make those God-rank potions.” Then Zhao Hai turned to Laura and the others and said, “Since we don’t have any pressing matter to take care of, let’s go to Grandpa Green and have a dinner with them.”

Laura and the others happily obliged. They had been too busy with the Demons and the Divine Race lately that they had no chance to share a meal with Grandpa Green and the others. Since they had nothing to do at the moment, they might as well eat with the elders.

As Cai’er arranged the God-rank potions, Zhao Hai and the others flashed towards the Ark Space, on the island occupied by the Buda Clan. The island wasn’t too far from the new Ark Continent. However, the status of the people living on the island had become extraordinary. This was because of the Buda Clan, Zhao Hai’s family. There’s no person in the Ark Continent that dared disrespect members of the clan.

However, it was also because of this status that Zhao Hai reduced the contact between the island and the mainland. At this point, the Buda Clan is no longer trading with the continent. This was because there was no way to do proper business when it came to the Buda Clan. Once the family sells on the mainland, no haggling on prices occured, the other party might even insert extra money on the side. If Zhao Hai does business this way, then the people’s respect towards him would become bad. At this point, Zhao Hai would only buy the least amount of things from the mainland as possible.

The Buda Clan’s island was quite similar to the black wasteland’s structure. Those who lived in the island were no longer just the Buda Clan and their slaves. Elves, Dwarves, and a substantial number of Beastmen also lived on the island.

When the new continent was made, Zhao Hai had the people from the Black Wasteland return to their homes. Some Dwarves, Elves, and Beastmen chose to leave the island but there were also some of them who decided to stay. They liked the way the Buda Clan ran things as well as the island’s environment. Because of this, they stayed and chose to become members of the Buda Clan.

The island had now become its own small self-sustaining continent. The Elves could make their artworks on the island and then sell them to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai would then choose some artworks for himself while selling the others to the Space. Although the artworks would be sold for a higher price on the continent, the Elves were still satisfied with the price given by the Space. As long as they have food, water, and a place to stay, that was already good enough.

The situation with the Dwarves was also similar. They like to forge stuff. In the past, they would continually make weapons and armor on demand, they held no freedom in what they can make. However, things were different in the island, they now have the freedom to make anything they want. Dwarves built their own houses and forges and then went on to do what they like. In any case, they don’t need to worry about things to eat and drink.

One could say that the Buda Clan’s island was its own free state. Here, everyone can do whatever they wanted. As long as they don’t break the rules, then nobody would judge them for what they do.

Chapter 836: A Rare Relaxation

Being a free state doesn’t meant that one can do crimes without repercussions. There were still laws in place in order to punish you. Being a free state meant that nobody would tell you what to do. You are free to be anything you like.

Zhao Hai hasn’t returned to the island for quite some time. Currently, the island was given an interesting name by the people of the Ark Continent, Haven Island.

It is certainly impossible for the people of the Ark Continent to not know about the story of the Haven products. They knew that the Buda Clan wanted to use this to name their products. Because of this, the name Haven Island came up.

Zhao Hai didn’t know this, but since the products of the Buda Clan rarely appeared on the continent now, Haven products had become extremely valuable items. People who had Haven products regarded these items as family treasures.

Also, Zhao Hai already spread his method of making liquor. He taught the Humans how to make grain wine. On the other hand, the Elves focused on making fruit wine while the Beastmen stayed with their milk whine. The Dwarves also kept making their sweet potato wine.

The Dwarves had plenty of cubed potato. This cubed potato was quite similar to sweet potatoes back on Earth. Zhao Hai only passed down the technique of distillation so naturally each group had their own preference.

When Zhao Hai arrived at the island, he saw the slaves working the fields. As they were working, they were talking with each other and laughed, they looked very happy.

What made Zhao Hai happy was the fact that these people looked like they loved their work. The tools each person used was different. Although the conventional tools were already refined, there were still some of them who wanted to try different types of tools.

Zhao Hai didn’t disturb them as he entered the castle along with Laura and the others. At this time, the liquor production of the castle had stopped. Even if some liquor were brewed, they were only going to be used for personal consumption. Because of this, the castle looked more spacious compared to before.

On the other hand, the people on the castle wasn’t few. The 100 initial slaves that Zhao Hai had brought used to help manage the new slaves. But now that they weren’t needed, they all returned to the castle.

After the people in the castle saw that Zhao Hai had come back, they immediately went to give him their greetings. Zhao Hai looked at the slaves and saw their neat appearance. It seems like they were living quite well. There were even some of them who showed a sense of elegance. This was evidently because they had become learned people.

Zhao Hai smiled at those who met him and said, “How are you doing? Is everyone doing fine?”

Everybody gave out a laugh before a fairly fat man replied, “Happy! We are very happy, Young Master. We can now eat meat every day, completely different to before when we were starving. I even got fat now, Young Master, look” Zhao Hai looked at the fat man. This person wasn’t that tall, only about 1.8 meters tall. However, he looks like he weighs more than 250 pounds. Seeing someone this fat was very surprising.

However, Zhao Hai can see that although this person was fat, he didn’t look weak at all. What made Zhao Hai surprised was the fact that this person was actually 9th rank, just one step left until becoming God-rank.

Zhao Hai waved his hand and said, “Come here, aren’t you Silas? When you came here, you were very small and skinny. I didn’t think that you would get this fat. Hahaha. Good, good. Just make sure that you won’t stumble. Right, did you like cultivating that much?”

The fatty named Silas didn’t expect Zhao Hai to call him by his name. His face couldn’t help but blush as he said, “I didn’t think that the Young Master would remember my name. I’m not very intelligent, so I couldn’t do anything complicated. However, I loved cultivating so I did that. I didn’t think that the Young Master would recognize me.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You continue with your diligent work. If you succeed, you will the first member of the Buda Clan to break  through to God-rank without outside help.” The fatty obviously wasn’t someone who had any idea about this. But when he heard Zhao Hai, he happily nodded his head.

Zhao Hai also greeted everyone else before entering the fort. Zhao Hai rarely came here anymore since his main operations were made inside the Space’s villa. At this time, Green and the others were already waiting for him in the main hall. After Zhao Hai came in, Green immediately gave his greetings, “Young Master, why did you decide to pay a visit today? Did something bad happen?” Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Everything’s fine, things have been calm these days so there’s nothing to worry about. I only came here for a simple visit.” Green’s worries vanished when he heard Zhao Hai.

After talking to Green, Zhao Hai also greeted Kun, Karen, and the others. After the group had sat down, Zhao Hai explained what happened outside, including the matter with the Atlanta Plane. After hearing Zhao Hai talk, Green said, “So there’s another spatial rift in the Ark Continent. It seems like the newcomers don’t have any good ideas for the plane.”

Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he gave a nod, “It seems to be like that. The Atlanta Plane should be as strong as the Demon Realm. However, they have their formidable magic armor. These magic armors were 10 meters high and covered in magic formations. Moreover, it can improve one’s attack strength, each one of them had peak 9th rank power.”

Upon hearing this, Karen knit his brows and said, “What magic formations? Can you let me take a look?”

Zhao Hai already guessed that Karen would be interested in this, so he smiled faintly and said, “Father-in-law, don’t worry, I ‘ll definitely show them to you. I need two days in order to compile everything we recorded. There are a lot of them and each part has different functions. When the time comes, you can study them closely.’

Karen’s was evidently satisfied with this answer. He initially started to study magic formations in order to forget his bitter memories regarding his wife, but who would’ve thought that he became obsessed with research. Green turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Young master, can you really fight with the Divine Race in this short amount of time?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “At this point, only remnant soldiers of the Taurus army are left in the Radiant Empire. Also, I reckon the Taurus continent would also stop sending reinforcements. This is a good opportunity to attack them with the Thunder Clan.” Green and the others didn’t oppose to this, they too held great resentment towards the Taurus Divines. For the Divines to use a huge blood sacrifice was already too much for them to accept. Not to say Zhao Hai, even Green and the others were seething with anger at this event.

After seeing that nobody opposed to this, Zhao Hai continued, “Grandpa Green, I need advice. The Space’s magic backgrounds are now ready for harvest. I already had Cai’er use the ingredients there in order to make 10 God rank potions. How do you suggest to divide them?”

Green gawked, then his eyes lit up as he asked, “Really? We can make that much?”

Zhao Hai nodded, the other people in the room were also evidently happy. Green thought for a moment and said, “Little Hai, how about this. I think you should give those potions to the people of the Ark Continent. You can give two potions to the Elves, two potions to the Humans, two potions to the Dwarves, two potions to the Beastmen, and the final two to the Fishmen. This way, they would feel grateful to you.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he knit his eyebrows as he said, “I wanted to give the potions to you. We can use the next batch for them.” Green smiled and said, “Give it to them this time. The next time, we can have them. In any case, we won’t leave the Space. What are you afraid of? These old bones are still very strong, we won’t die soon.” Zhao Hai nodded and followed Green’s suggestion. At this time, Merine came in bringing some food. Then the group proceeded to eat their meal.

Zhao Hai spent three days in this peaceful state. These three days were rare times of relaxation for him. He went with the slaves and conversed with them. He also gave a visit to the Giant-horned Bulls, the Diamond Apes, the Dwarves, and the Elves. He went and visited everyone he could visit.

Times spent in relaxation always passes by quickly. Three days passed in a blink of an eye. Although Zhao Hai wanted to keep this time of leisure, the matters outside didn’t allow him to stay.

Fei’er and the others had already reached the borders of the Radiant Empire. They were ready to attack the Divine Race and Zhao Hai couldn’t be absent for this event.

These days, Zhao Hai also took the effort to visit Fei’er as well as see the Great Demon King’s progress in moving the Demons to the Space. Although the Demons were busy with their migration, the Devil Legion was still ready to make an attack at any time.

In addition to the progress of the Demons, the magic formations have also been sorted out. Karen had succeeded in developing the defensive magic formation. Zhao Hai was now more confident in dealing with the Divine Race.

Currently, Zhao Hai didn’t lack in his supply of crystal stones. What he lacked were things to use crystals with. The appearance of the defensive formations was just right for his current needs.

Karen’s defensive formation wasn’t simple. During the process of experimentation, Karen had written all its properties in a very detailed manner. This magic formation can be used by ten thousand people, fifty thousand people, and 100 thousand people. Although the number of people using it varied, the need for crystal stones didn’t exponentially increase. It was only after this property was achieved did the formation deemed a success.

Chapter 837: Fire

An army had already converged outside the Radiant Empire. However, the attackers didn’t attack immediately. They just kept their formations in preparation for their charge.

Inside the Radiant Empire, the Divine Race has now gathered 20 million troops to fight. The borders of the Empire already had a long wall built equipped with magic cannons. All of the soldiers were in a neat formation floating in mid air.

On the opposite side, there were also troops floating in mid air; the two armies of the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus, Zhao Hai’s undead army, and the Demon Race’s Devil Legion. The small number of Thunder Clan people were also present in the center.

While looking at the Divine Race’s desperate situation, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh, “I didn’t expect us to be this quick to turn on the Divine Race. To be honest, when the Divine Race and you came, I didn’t think I would be able to see this day.” Zhao Hai was currently sitting inside the Demon Dragon King’s carriage, talking with the Demon Dragon King.

The Demon Dragon King smiled and said, “When we came to attack the Ark Continent, we also didn’t expect to be able to settle inside a place much better in comparison.”

Zhao Hai gave out a chuckle, “In truth, if it weren’t for the Demons using an non-wicked method to come here, I wouldn’t have allowed you to settle in the Space. You should know that since the residents of the continent had moved, I didn’t have extra worries anymore. When the time comes, I can just slowly grind away at the Demons and the Divine Race.”

The Demon Dragon King knew that Zhao Hai wasn’t speaking nonsense. To be honest, after entering the Space, Zhao Hai’s mysterious ability, the Demon Dragon King already understood that if they didn’t become Zhao Hai’ allies, then they would sooner or later be tidied up.

The Demon Dragon King smiled and then said, “This is the luck of our Demon Race. You should know that the Blood Void Formation needed live sacrifice as well. It’s fortunate that we chose the Demons, otherwise we would have suffered the same fate as the Divine Race.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, “It’s good that the Demons think that the Dragons are better compared to the Humans. Or else you would’ve used Humans instead of Dragons.”

Just as the two were talking, Fei’er arrived by their side. Zhao Hai looked at Feier as the latter gave a salute, then Zhao Hai said, “Is everything prepared?” Fei’er nodded and said, “Yes, but as you can see, there are massive magic cannons placed on the walls. Even God-ranks are unable to resist the attacks from those cannons. Moreover, their range is much farther than the magic cannons of your Ark Continent. It is only because those things are huge and heavy that they were very inconvenient to bring to the battlefield. What we need to do right now is to take care of those cannons. Does mister have any way to do it?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Leave it to me.” Then he waved his hand as he released a few rows of undead dragons. Mounted on top of their heads were magic cannons. Moreover, these cannons weren’t those from the Ark Continent, instead, they were the Divine Race’s magic cannons.

Fei’er looked at the Dragons and stared. He has been with the Divine Race army for a long time so naturally he could identify that these magic cannons were from the Divine Race. Fei’er just didn’t expect that Zhao Hai would have those cannons of his own.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and smiled, “When I attacked the Radiant Empire, I also took the opportunity to snatch some magic cannons for myself. It just so happens that they’re quite convenient to use today.”

Fei’er said, “It seems like we’ll have the Divine Race taste their own magic cannons.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly but he didn’t say anything. The magic cannons of the Divine Race were indeed large, however, Zhao Hai still didn’t think that they were strong enough. It was mainly because they lacked a good energy source. In the past, the Divine Race only used ordinary crystals to power them. Those magic crystals were in no way comparable to the magic cannons that Zhao Hai had now.

With the superior crystals in his hands, Zhao Hai was able to improve the power of the magic cannons. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to take them out.

Zhao Hai didn’t give an explanation to Fei’er as he waved his hand. After that, the dragons proceeded to go towards the Radiant Empire. They would only stop if they reach their firing distance.

Besides the cannons, there were also four undead on top of each dragon, they’re main purpose was to man the weapon. Although Zhao Hai didn’t have that much magic cannons, he was still confident that his cannons were superior.

No matter what, the might and firing distance of the cannons was improved thanks to Zhao Hai’s crystals. When the attack happens, the Divine Race’s cannons would be useless against Zhao Hai’s army.

The dragons stopped when they reached their firing distance, at the same time, the undead started to arm the cannons. It didn’t take a long time before 40 red lights started to fly towards the Radiant Empire’s walls. This caused the Divines manning the cannons to be startled. They weren’t even able to get a defensive formation out before they were blasted by the red lights.

One could say that the might of these cannons were far superior compared to the cannons of the Ark Continent. Although its crystal consumption was greater, Zhao Hai didn’t care about that right now, power was what he needed.

Zhao Hai’s attack was beyond the Divine Race’s expectations. The Divine Race has heard of the Ark Continent’s cannons. Although they suffered a few attacks from the Ark Continent’s cannons, they still believed that their magic cannons were better.

Because of this, the Divine Race were confident in defending the Radiant Empire. They were also able to see Zhao Hai’s undead dragons. Although the Dragons held the Divine Race’s giant cannons, the DIvine Race knew that Zhao Hai didn’t have that much with him. In their minds, they could fully suppress the enemy’s advance.

However, they didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s magic cannons would have a better firing distance compared to the Divine Race’s cannons. This caused the Divine Race to begin worrying about their defense.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about the Divine Race’s thoughts. At this time, he made the undead continue on with their assault. To be honest, the walls were useless at this point. The Divine Race seemed to have focused their research on the magic cannons and had forgotten to study strong defensive formations.

If the Divine Race had good defensive magic formations, they wouldn’t have been harassed by Zhao Hai’s tactics. Unfortunately, the Divine Race didn’t take magic formations very seriously.

When the Divine Race had wars with the other races, they were always on the winning side. Because of this position, their rear areas were never attacked.

This caused  the Divine Race to grow complacent as time passed. Their arrogance had reached to the point that they had deemed defensive formations to be unnecessary. In the end, they neglect their study on defensive magic formations, this resulted in their suffering in the hands of Zhao Hai.

Once the Divine Race found out that their cannons were virtually useless, they had no choice but to abandon their magic cannons and slowly retreat.

When Zhao Hai saw that the Divine Race had abandoned their magic cannons, he couldn’t help but be happy. He immediately released the undead loaded with the Ark Continent’s magic cannons. Although they had a smaller power compared to the Divine Race’s cannons, the Divine Race had already abandoned their advantage the moment they left the walls.

The Divine Race were also able to discover this. However, it was already impossible for them to return to their cannons. The Ark Continent’s cannons had reached their firing distance, so if the Divine Race returned, then they would be placed under a rain of fire.

The Divine Race also knew that if they continued on like this, then they would only be defeated and wouldn’t be able to fight back. Because of this, the Divine Race soldiers proceeded to rush towards Zhao Hai.

Just as the Divine Race were more about 1000 meters away from Zhao Hai, a dark cloud was immediately spotted. Upon seeing this, Zhao Hai immediately knew what it was. The Divine Race just threw their javelins.

Although these javelins weren’t the same as Zhao Hai’s blood lightning javelins, their firing distance was still quite far. Moreover, they were quite lethal to average people.

However, they were up against Zhao Hai’s undead army. Against the undead, these javelins could only deal minimal damage.

Nobody could blame the Divine Race for not being able to adapt. After all, when they were planning to attack the continent, they knew that it was unlike the planes of the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and the Thunder Clan. The Ark Continent was just a lower plane with no God-rank experts.

Because of this information, the Divine Race didn’t develop new weapons upon coming to the Ark Continent. This caused them to lack attacking methods to deal with Zhao Hai. Their methods were either useless or did only a small damage to Zhao Hai.

Although the Taurus Divines had started to make new means of dealing with Zhao Hai, the time to develop this weapon would take more than one or two days. If they wanted to depend on this new weapon, then they would need to hold Zhao Hai back for some time.

Chapter 838: Fighting to Win

In the past, Zhao Hai was quite worried about the Divine Race’s javelin attack. However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry anymore. Now that Karen’s research has been completed, they could now use it in the army.

As the Divine Race’s javelins hit the periphery of the undead army, a red shield suddenly appeared. Upon hitting the red shield, the javelins were immediately burned to ash.

Currently, the crystals that Zhao Hai had the most were the fire element crystals. Therefore, Zhao Hai decided to use it for the defensive formation. At the same time, he also wanted to see how powerful the defensive formation was.

Sure enough, the defensive formation didn’t disappoint Zhao Hai. Not only were the javelins blocked, they were also burned to ash. This was a testament to the defensive capability of the shield.

The Divine Race were shocked by the scene before them. It wasn’t only the Divine Race who were startled, Fei’er and the others held the same shocked expression on their faces. Only the Demon Dragon King kept calm, but he couldn’t stop the smile emerging from his face.

The reason why the Demon Dragon King was smiling was because Zhao Hai also equipped the Devil Legion with this defensive formation. This formation was mounted behind a large undead and was able to cover a large area. With this, whether advancing or retreating, the army would be protected either way.

The defensive shield shouldn’t be underestimated. Even if the shield wasn’t defensively strong, it still could block attacks. This would reduce casualties and in turn improve the soldier’s morale.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I won’t dare fighting the Divine Race before, but now, hehe.” Then he had the magic cannons retreat as the other undead proceeded to push on.

This undead rush made the Divine Race panic. The reason for this was because the undead were all Divine Race soldiers. They were the fallen allies that were turned into undead.

The undead Divines initially rushed in a cube formation. But when they were about a kilometer away from the Divine Race army, they immediately turned into a rotating cone formation.

To be honest, there were only a few soldiers among the Divine Race army that wanted to face the Ark Continent at this point. Being faced with this cube formation composed of Divine Race undead made them utterly flustered.

However, the Divine Race were still worthy of their title. When the two armies clashed, their formation still kept solid. They were quickly able to establish their Domains and their formations.

But then, a scene of horror appeared in front of the Divine Race. As they raised their shields, the undead army did the same. This caused the initial state of battle to remain unchanged.

The speed of the cone’s rotation became even faster. This rotation didn’t have one person acting as the tip, instead, it had four people. Each member of the formation had sword-shaped Domains, it caused the entire formation to become a huge weapon.

There were a lot of these formations flying through the air, heading towards the Divine Race’s defensive formation. Each cone slowly became like sharp bamboo spears, spiralling towards the enemies.

These bamboo spears proceeded to skewer the Divine Race army. The formation became a meat grinder, every area they passed through would have flesh and blood flying all around.

Although the Divines had established their Domains, they became helpless in front of these bamboo spears. Ony by one, each of their Domains were broken through, shattered before they met their deaths.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation without any change to his expression. The Demon Dragon King by his side was also looking towards the clash, his face failing to hide his shock. To be honest, he knew that even the Devil Legion wouldn’t be able to accomplish such a formation. The coordination needed to perform such a feat was astronomical, not one person was allowed to fail. Even a small mistake would completely derail the formation.

The Demon Dragon King also knew that if the Devil Legion were to meet such a formation then even them would be punctured to death, there was no doubt about that.

At the same time, Fei’er and the others were also shaken by what they saw, all of them were rendered speechless. If Zhao Hai decided to deal with them using the same method, then they would surely be finished.

Although Zhao Hai was paying attention to his undead army, he had asked Cai’er to pay attention to his allies’ reactions. The reason he revealed the might of the cannons as well as the bamboo spear formation today was to show these people how formidable he was.

In any alliance, a leader would need to be present. Otherwise, the alliance would be in a state of disunity. Not to say dealing with the Divine Race, an alliance leader would be needed to reduce infighting.

But if one wanted to become the alliance leader, then one needed to show their might. This meant that Zhao Hai needed to stun his allies with this strength. Only with this method would the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and Thunder Clan listen to him. Otherwise, if Zhao Hai can’t do it, he might as well go back to the Space and sleep.

The thoughts of the Barbarians and Winged Pegasus have already been confirmed by Fei’er. It was precisely because of this that Zhao Hai decided to use the Divine Race as an example. He would kill the chicken in order to frighten the monkeys. This way, the Barbarians and the Winged Pegasus would be afraid of him and obey his commands.

Zhao Hai was very glad about this alliance. This was because he knew that it would take a long time to deal with the Divine Race if he was alone. But with the help of more people, the time needed would be greatly reduced.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t want to listen to another person’s command. He still had the vigor of a young male, he didn’t want someone to dictate  his actions.

Now it seems like the results were very good. The Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and the Thunder Clan were all shaken by his action. Later on, they wouldn’t have any reservations in following his command.

At this point, the Divine Race were flustered. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai’s attack to be this fierce. It gave them little to no chance to retaliate.

This time, the bamboo spear blistered into smaller bamboo spears. This caused the Divine Race army to be disturbed, finding it hard to keep their shape. In the end, the previously fearless Divine Race army started to have some deserters among their numbers.

In fact, Zhao Hai had used this bamboo spear formation once before, but since there weren’t so many people in the formation, its might wasn’t that big. But now that Zhao Hai had a lot of undead Divines in his hand, this allowed the formation to show its true might.

As the Divine Race soldiers ran away, Zhao Hai immediately gave an order to the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and the Thunder Clan to give chase.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai directed his other undead to clean the battlefield. All weapons discarded by the Divine Race were all captured, this included the big magic cannons up on the walls.

The Divine Race soldiers left inside the Radiant Empire wasn’t a lot. The 20 million soldiers were almost all of the soldiers left. Now that the army has been routed, the entire Radiant Empire was now ripe for takeover.

All involved in this fight were strong experts, it wouldn’t be a problem for them to fight continuously for one or two days. However, the Divine Race were completely scared off by Zhao Hai. This caused them to be unable to muster up some courage. All of them were scampering to return back to the Divine Realm.

Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t just have them retreat easily. They continuously chased the Divine Race soldiers up to the rift. While the others were going with the assault, Zhao Hai was actually in the Radiant Empire gathering all the supplies that the Divine Race had left. The most important harvests that Zhao Hai gained were grains, Goblins, and magic cannons.

There were plenty of supplies inside the Radiant Church, all of which were taken by Zhao Hai. The Radiant Empire was different compared to the rest of the Ark Continent. The people of the Radiant Empire were all sacrificed by the Radiant Church. Because of this, their belongings were still present. This caused Zhao Hai’s harvest to be more than expected.

These supplies were not really good, most of them were even quite old. There wouldn’t be anyone in the Ark Continent who would want to use them. Even the Beastmen would decline such items. Zhao Hai had made a place like the church in the Beastman territory. This allowed the Beastmen to trade their goods for living materials that they need.

But this didn’t matter since Zhao Hai planned to hand these supplies over to the Demons and the Goblins. The Demons were completely lacking in living materials, they really didn’t have anything good to live with. Just like the Demon Dragon said, the Demons could quickly pack all of their belongings as well as get magic beasts and plants before moving to the Space. Even with this, there would still people who would come empty-handed. For these people, the Demon Dragon King had them carry stones for the Space in order to build their houses. The Demons were completely solid in their decision to keep the Space’s environment intact.

There was no need to say anything about the Goblins. Besides their old and ripped pants, they simply didn’t have anything else. Giving them these supplies would surely elevate their situation.

The Demon Dragon King has always been with Zhao Hai, therefore, he was able to see the undead basically scraping everything off the ground and then taking it to the Space. As long as something was useful, then it would be taken away. No matter if it was in good condition or bad, whether it was new or old, everything was taken. This caused the Demon Dragon King to be confused. However, the Demon Dragon King still kept an eye out for these things, the Demons were just too poor.

While Zhao Hai was proceeding with his plunder, the Divine Race continued to run back to the Divine Realm. In the final moments, a defensive troop stayed behind to stop the pursuing soldiers.

Although they were yet to attack the Divine Realm, Fei’er and the others were still very happy. They just managed to repel the Divine Race, this was definitely a good start to their plans. At the same time, it provided them confidence to fight against the Divine Race.

Zhao Hai also left some cities untouched. These cities were to be handed over to Fei’er and the others to rest in.

After exchanging words with Fei’er and the others, everyone went back to take a rest. Zhao Hai led the Devil Legion as they went back to the Demon’s Space.

Zhao Hai discovered that the Demon Space has greatly changed. A lot of Demons already had their houses built. Those who didn’t have their own house were also in the process of building them. The reason they were slow was because they almost exclusively used materials from the Ark Continent or the Demon Realm. They rarely acquired materials from the Space.

After seeing his people bustling about inside the Space, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but smile as he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, I really want to give you my utmost gratitude. If it weren’t for you, I’m afraid my people wouldn’t be able to live this kind of life.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he waved his hand, “There’s no need to be too polite. Right, I just gained a lot of materials from the Radiant Empire. If you need them, I can provide a share of those things to you. What do you think?”

When the Demon Dragon King heard this, he couldn’t help but smile, “That would be great. Thanks.” Zhao Hai smiled before he took out piles of those supplies out into the Space.

When the piles appeared, the Demon Dragon King immediately had people distribute them. After the Demon Dragon King was finished with his task, he was immediately invited by Zhao Hai inside the sword carriage. After the two sat down, Zhao Hai said, “Demon Dragon, I want to tell you something. A few days ago, another spatial rift appeared in the continent….” Then Zhao Hai told the Demon Dragon King about the Atlanta Plane.

The Demon Dragon King’s expression stayed tranquil. Now that the Demons were going to enter the Space, he doesn’t need to worry about this anymore. However, he knew that Zhao Hai must have a reason to tell him about this. Therefore, he kept listening. After Zhao Hai finished speaking, Demon Dragon asked, “What does mister want to do?”

Zhao Hai’s tone turned to serious as he said, “Eliminate them when they come. Then we’ll snatch their magic armors and use it to deal with the Divine Race.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded and said, “Does mister want us to send some troops?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “I only have my eyes on them, but I can’t guarantee if we can use them in the future. I just told you about it so that you can prepare. I also want you to pick some Demons who are enthusiastic about magic formations. We’ll have them make their own magic armor as soon as possible.”

The Demon Dragon King wrinkled his brows as he said, “Mister, why would you go through so much trouble? We can just grab their method of production and reproduce them in the Space. If Mister’s strength isn’t enough, the Demons can send troops to help you.”

Chapter 839: Demon Realm’s Beast Tide

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile as he heard this. It was a completely Demon-like response. If you want it, just rob it. It was just like when the Demons fancied the Ark continent. They didn’t think too much about it and just proceeded to invade.

After seeing Zhao Hai smile, the Demon Dragon King couldn’t help but be worried, “Mister? Did I make a mistake?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “There’s nothing wrong. I don’t want to have a war with three planes right now. Therefore, we’ll just prepare to receive them in the future.”

The Demon Dragon King stared, then he immediately understood Zhao Hai’s plan. Zhao Hai was currently in a war against the Divine Race, but the Underworld was also slowly creeping in. If the Atlanta Plane was added, then Zhao Hai would have three enemies. Having war with these three parties meant that the Ark Continent would be at war with three planes.

The Demon Dragon King frowned and said, “Then what is mister planning to do?”

Zhao Hai replied, “We’ll wait for them to invade the Ark Continent, then we’ll snatch their technology for our research. We’ll wait until we settle in the Divine Realm before thinking about going to the Atlanta Plane.”

The Demon Dragon King thought about it before nodding. Their most important enemy at this time was the Divine Race. Although the people from the Atlanta Plane were also very dangerous, their threat was still inferior compared to the Divine Race. Moreover, they were now allied with the Barbarians, Winged Pegasus, and the Thunder Clan. If they shift their target to the Atlanta Plane, then that would be unfair to them. So first they need to deal with the Divine Race and then deal with the Atlanta Plane in the future.

The Demon Dragon King asked, “So what do we do now?”

Zhao Hai replied, “First, we need to deal with the Divine Race. We’ll focus on this goal first, we’ll put the other matters to the side.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded. At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly felt his messenger fish move. Zhao Hai stared before he immediately took it out. From the messenger fish was the Great Demon King’s voice, “Mister, are you in?’

Zhao Hai stared for a moment before he quickly replied, “I’m here. Your Majesty, do you need something?”

The Great Demon King immediately replied, “Mister, quickly close your spatial rift. A beast tide just formed in the Demon Realm. We don’t want those demon beasts to enter the Space.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then his body immediately flashed towards the spatial rift. Currently, the spatial rift was outside a medium sized settlement in the Demon Realm. This allowed easy entry for the Demons heading towards the Space. However, the situation outside wasn’t very good to look at.

This wasn’t the first time that Zhao Hai had seen a beast tide. In the past, the Black Wasteland had also suffered a similar event. However, compared to the Black Wasteland, the beast tide of the Demon Realm was much much worse.

At this time, a flock of demon beasts blotted out the skies. These magic beasts were poised to attack the city while some were heading towards the spatial rift.

When Zhao Hai saw this scene, his two eyes immediately shone. He immediately gave the Great Demon King a reply through the messenger fish, “Your Majesty, there’s no need to worry. As long as I make some adjustments, I can also absorb those magic beasts into the Space.”

Zhao Hai was just wondering as to how he could take magic beasts of the Demon Realm to the Space. But now, this opportunity actually came, so how could he just let this go. Zhao Hai didn’t close the spatial rift but instead shifted the destination. Instead of the Demon Space, the spatial rift was connected to the hell background.

The hell background was suited for darkness creatures to survive in. Since most of these magic beasts were of the darkness attribute, Zhao Hai could just place them all inside the hell background.

If they want to take those beasts to the Space, then they could only grasp them one by one or bait them in just like what Zhao Hai did in the Carrion Swamp. However, both of those methods were very hard to accomplish.

But now that the magic beasts were rushing towards the rift, Zhao Hai can use this opportunity to take them to the Space. Although these beasts were hostile towards him, the Space can just change this sentiment down until it disappears entirely.

The Space considers people and magic beasts to be two different beings. If a person has hostility towards the Space, then the Space couldn’t just change it instantaneously. It can only slowly turn the will of that person, subtly influencing that person’s thoughts.

But for magic beasts, the Space held more power. As long as Zhao Hai takes them to the Space, the magic beasts would immediately surrender. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about these magic beasts rampaging upon reaching the Space. Also, they might even provide some improvement to the Space’s level.

Although the Great Dragon King couldn’t understand Zhao Hai’s action, he still didn’t oppose to it. He believed that Zhao Hai knew what he was doing. And since he was busy defending the city, he didn’t have the focus to deal with Zhao Hai’s decision. Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King immediately stored the messenger fish.

Before the magic beasts entered the Space, Zhao Hai quickly changed the background and opened new spatial rifts. This way, it would be easier for the magic beasts to enter the Space.

Then something shocking happened to the magic beasts. As Zhao Hai opened new rifts, the magic beasts immediately swarmed towards them, almost to the point where they were throwing themselves over.

The magic beasts attacking the city stopped their advance as they shifted their focus on the spatial rifts. Weaker magic beasts were even trampled by those much stronger than them.

Zhao Hai himself couldn’t help but get shocked upon seeing this. Although he wanted the magic beasts to enter, he didn’t think that it would be this case. This was completely out of his expectation.

The magic beasts went straight into the Space just like moths to a fire. This scene also attracted the attention of the Great Demon King. The Great Demon King was immediately worried about his people. He was afraid that those magic beasts would flood the Demons inside the Space. Because of this, he immediately took his messenger fish and contacted Zhao Hai, “Mister, mister, can you hear me?”

Zhao Hai took his messenger fish out and said, “Your Majesty, I can hear you. There’s no need to worry. I took the magic beasts to a place completely different from the Demon Space. Your Majesty can rest assured.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai, the Great Demon King’s heart couldn’t help but skip a beat. Although Zhao Hai’s words seemed simple, it gave the Great Demon King another piece of information. Zhao Hai’s Space actually had another place other than the Ark Space and the Demon Space. It might even be multiple other places.

The Great Demon King found out that everytime he gauges Zhao Hai’s strength, he would still be underestimating him. If Zhao Hai can settle the Ark Continent’s residents on one place while settling the Demons to another, then this means that Zhao Hai could settle another race inside a different Space. If Zhao Hai continues to accumulate people this way, then his faith power would be greater than what the Divine Race would provide.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about any of these as he was look satisfactorily at the magic beasts rushing towards the Space. This was a completely good thing for him. He also heard prompts here and there as the Space introduced different magic beasts to him while also subduing them. Later on, Zhao Hai would be able to use these magic beasts as his subordinates.

Zhao Hai fancied these magic beasts from the Demon Realm. Their strength was formidable. Moreover, they were the most suitable to become mounts. In addition to their strength, each one of them were unafraid of death. This was a problem prevalent with magic beasts found in the Ark Continent.

There were too many magic beasts, so it took them some time before they entered the Space. Fortunately, these magic beasts were completely focused on the Space. This allowed Zhao Hai to stop worrying about them.

After looking at it for a while, Zhao Hai returned to the Space’s villa. When he arrived at the living room, he saw Laura and the others sitting there, looking at the Demon Realm’s beast tide.

After seeing this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, then he turned to Cai’er and said, “Cai’er do you know why those magic beasts suddenly rushed to the Space?”

Cai’er smiled and said, “It’s possibly because the young master has changed the background. Most of these beasts had the darkness attribute and the hell background can improve the darkness attribute. For these magic beasts, it was basically an instinct to seek for improvement. Possibly, they were able to sense the hell background and couldn’t help but rush towards it.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then replied, “That’s great. Having those beasts inside the Space is definitely a good thing for us. If those magic beasts come, then it’s possible that they can upgrade the Space.”

Cai’er smiled and said, “I don’t think that would be possible. Although there are a lot of magic beasts, the types present aren’t many. Moreover, most of them are weak magic beasts. If they didn’t enter the Space, they would’ve been killed by stronger magic beasts. Depending on these beasts to upgrade the Space is just not possible.”

Zhao Hai agreed, he nodded and said, “Even if they can’t upgrade the Space, having them is still good for us. A lot of these magic beasts are quite strong, not quite inferior compared to God-ranks. Having them enter the Space would improve our strength.”

Chapter 840: Fighting a Battle To Force A Decision

The beast tide of the Demon Realm, although it was only a fleeting event, allowed Zhao Hai to gain a lot of benefits. After the magic beasts charged to the Space, Zhao Hai immediately changed the spatial rift’s destination back to the Demon Space. After that, Zhao Hai went and informed the Great Demon King to have the Demons continue their move.

Zhao Hai had also finished his matter with the Demon Dragon King, so naturally he wouldn’t stay in the Demon Space for long. He went to rest in the villa for a while before walking out to find Fei’er.

Fei’er and the others were now resting inside the cities of the Radiant Empire. Since the cities were converted into military compounds, they still had few commodities present, so Fei’er and the others weren’t worried about what to eat. However, the fight that just happened had truly given them a shock.

Zhao Hai’s fighting strength stunned them. They didn’t think that Zhao Hai was so strong, he wasn’t any weaker than the Divine Race.

Most importantly, after killing the Divine Race today, Zhao Hai would gain more undead Divines, improving his strength once more.

Because of this, after Fei’er and the others settled their people, they immediately gathered together and discussed Zhao Hai. It can be seen that the result of Zhao Hai’s use of power has yielded its result.

Fei’er looked at Shan and Yue as he sighed and said, “You two, you should have seen Zhao Hai’s strength. To be honest, I wasn’t expecting him to be that strong as well. I know you have some reservations towards him for killing your people. Nevertheless, we’re going against a common enemy right now. WIth Zhao Hai being the main powerhouse, our people would die less. I hope you two can put your enmity aside and cooperate with Zhao Hai.”

Shan and Yue looked at each other before simultaneously nodding. Yue then said, “It’s true that we have some hatred towards Zhao Hai, however, we hate the Divine Race even more. Moreover, we haven’t seen Zhao Hai use our people in his battles. It’s quite obvious that he wants to save face for us.”

Shan added, “Right, compared to the Divine Race, our hatred for Zhao Hai is small. In fact, we really can’t blame Zhao Hai for killing our people. It is the Divine Race’s fault for sending them to the battlefield. Zhao Hai is just trying to defend his homeland.”

Upon hearing the two, Fei’er let out a sigh of relief. Then he gave a nod as he said, “Then that’s good. Our greatest enemy is the Divine Race, we should focus on them.”

Shan and Yue nodded. They weren’t clueless people, they knew that Zhao Hai’s strength can only bring them benefits and no harm. As for what happens after they defeated the Taurus Divines in the Divine Realm, they didn’t think about that yet. They weren’t even sure if they could do such a thing.

Shan looked at Fei’er and said, “Feier, with the current situation, our people have already started out move. At this point, the Divine Race have guarded the spatial rift. Should we attack the Taurus continent like mister Zhao Hai said?” At this time, a soldier suddenly gave a report, “Mister Zhao Hai came to talk.”

The three looked at each other before they all stood up. “Quickly invite him inside”, Fei’er said. Then the three went forward to see Zhao Hai.

After Zhao Hai came in and saw that the three were together, he couldn’t help but smile. Then he gave the three a salute and said, “I didn’t think all three of you would be here. Let’s discuss what to do next.”

Fei’er smiled and said, “We’re also about to talk to mister regarding this. However, we didn’t have the means to meet mister, please excuse us.” Fei’er purposely forgot about the messenger fish that Zhao Hai gave him.

Zhao Hai understood that Fei’er was just being polite, he didn’t mind it as he smiled and said, “It’s fine. I also like to go around places, so you don’t need to worry.” After that, all of them entered the hall.

The place they were in was a church in the city. This was a strange thing in the Radiant Empire. Generally, the city lord’s mansion would be the most noteworthy structure in any place, however, in the Radiant Empire, it was the church.

The church was made magnificently. Its walls were full of murals, it was very beautiful. The murals depicted scenes glorifying the Divine Race, like how they managed to defeat Demons. There really wasn’t much history shown.

This was the first time that Zhao Hai managed to see the inside of a church. Now that he saw it, he couldn’t help but admit that it looked good. One could feel how tranquil it was inside, the murals were very artistic as well.

Suddenly, Zhao Hai noticed Winged Pegasus people on one of the murals. The Winged Pegasus were riding their mounts as they held their knight’s spear and battled with a Demon.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but chuckle, then he turned to Yue and said, “I didn’t think that the Winged Pegasus people would be part of the Radiant Church’s stories. They could even fight alongside the Divine Race.” Then he pointed towards the mural.

Yue had just met with Fei’er, so he wasn’t able to notice the mural. Now that Zhao Hai pointed it out, he turned his head to look at it. Then he snorted and said, “Those are just nonsense made up by the Divine Race. Those bastards, we’ll never worship them.”

What Yue said wasn’t wrong. While the Divine Race drew the Winged Pegasus on the mural, they don’t actually treat them as equals. Instead, the Divine Race wanted to assimilate them into their civilization by erasing their culture. This way, they would become the Divine Race’s faithful dog.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “The Divine Race has always been like this. They also wanted to control the Ark Continent by using the Radiant Church. If it wasn’t for our early discovery about their plot, the situation wouldn’t have been like this.”

Fei’er and the others nodded. Then after the group had sat down, a Thunder Clan member brought over some clear water. The Divine Race prohibited wines being consumed by their troops, so they didn’t bring anything with them. At this point, the only thing they can provide Zhao Hai was water. Zhao Hai didn’t mind it too much as he took a sip of the water before he said, “I came to visit because I want to discuss how to attack the Divine Race. I also want to listen to your thoughts.”

Fei’er and the other two looked at one another, they had a gaze that Zhao Hai didn’t understand. After some time, Fei’er turned his head and said, “What does mister plan to do?” Zhao Hai looked at the three before he smiled and said, “I plan to force a battle so that the Taurus Divines would be compelled to make a move. We need to take care of the remaining Taurus Divines before we can proceed to the Divine Realm.”

The three nodded their heads. They understood how this worked. Shan opened his mouth and said, “We also thought about this matter. I believe our people have already started to battle with the Divine Race. At this point, the Divine Race wouldn’t be able to send more troops to deal with us. We can use this opportunity to attack the Divine Race in one swoop.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So you already thought about it, then that makes everything better. Right, since we’re now allies, I won’t hide things from you. As you can see, the Demons have already become part of my people. Also, in the Ark Continent’s Beastman Prairie, a spatial rift to the underworld has appeared. At this point, the underworld’s dark mist and undead creatures are already slowly creeping their way into the center of the continent. Moreover, on the south of the continent is another spatial rift. This rift is connected to a plane called the Atlanta Plane. The people from that plane aren’t weak. Most importantly, they have 10-meter tall magic armors made out of iron. These magic armors can be controlled by the people from the Atlanta plane and are very powerful. With these two enemies, I decided to move the entire population of the Ark Continent. I need to be clear about this to you three. The situation is very bad for us. We need to eliminate the remaining Divines and set a foothold in the Divine Realm. Otherwise, we would be sandwiched between two powerful enemies.”

Fei’er and the others were shocked upon hearing this. They never expected these things to be present in the Ark Continent. Especially those people with magic armors.

Suddenly, Fei’er’s eyes shone, he looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, are those magic armors like the ones made by the Goblins?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “They are. However, their magic armors are much better in comparison. If the Goblins had the same quality of magic armor, then they wouldn’t have been reduced to being slaves.”

Fei’er nodded. He had seen Goblin-made iron golems before. This golem was treated as a victory trophy by Thunder Yun at his home.

Actually, this trophy wasn’t acquired by Thunder Yun himself. Instead, it was something passed down in their family. The Goblins were subjugated way before the Thunder Clan were discovered. When Fei’er became Thunder Yun’s guard, the name ‘goblin’ was already synonymous with slave.

However, that iron golem actually scared Fei’er. Compared to the Thunder Clan, the body of those iron golems were much bigger. Because of this, the memory of that golem failed to escape Fei’er’s mind.

Chapter 841: Right to Speak!

In fact, when the Divines were subjugating the Goblins, they having quite the trouble. Although the Goblins didn’t focus their research on weapons, they still had their magic cannons and magic armors. The power of both of those were extraordinary.

The Divines were completely terrified about those two things. They believed that if they made the Goblins continue to develop then they would sooner or later reach a dominant status compared to the Divine Race. Because of this, the Divines decided to eliminate the Goblins and prevent them from continuing on with their research.

The magic cannons were left to the Divine Race, of which they used to conquer various other planes.

The Divine Race also thought about researching the metal armors to improve their overall strength. However, the metal golems were just too complex. The Goblins used a lot of secret techniques in order to manufacture them, and those secrets couldn’t be acquired by the Divine Race. In the end, the Divines did their best to stop those things from being made. After all, the iron golems were able to kill a lot of Divine Race soldiers.

Fei’er and the others didn’t know about any of these. In the Divine Realm, the battle against the Divines and the Goblins were minimally recorded. Fei’er only saw a broken metal armor, but although it was broken, it still left a very deep impression on him.

Now that Fei’er heard that Atlanta Continent’s magic armors were more advanced than the ones made by the Goblins, he couldn’t help but stare. After some time, his complexion turned ugly as he said, “Mister, are you telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “How could I lie about this matter. Right, I have some kind of magic. I learned it from the Fishman Race. It allows me to save what I had seen before. Take a look.” Then he waved his hand and showed the scene with Axe.

The big metal armor made Fei’er and the others gasp. Only when Axe’s armor transformed into an aircraft and left  Blazing Island did they manage to recover. But it still took them a long time before a word went out of their mouths.

Zhao Hai retrieved the monitor before he looked the three and said, “Those are the flying magic armors of the Atlanta Continent. Before I arrived, they already eliminated magic beasts and flame demons of Blazing Island. Moreover, it only took them a short time to do so.”

Fei’er looked confused at Zhao Hai as he asked, “Mister, how did you know that they have arrived in the Ark Continent?”

Upon hearing Fei’er, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, “Everybody wonders how I am able to know what happens in the Ark Continent. Let me tell you in simple words. I have scouts all throughout the continent. Almost all of the continent is under my watch.”

Fei’er didn’t say anything, he believed Zhao Hai’s words. When Zhao Hai was fighting against the Divine Race, he was always a step ahead. If Zhao Hai didn’t have his eyes on the continent, that feat would’ve been impossible.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and said, “But me discovering them only came due to an accident. At that time I wanted to sneak an attack against the Radiant Empire. Since you were entangled at Accra Mountain, I encircled all around to attack the south of the Empire. It was then that I managed to see them.”

Fei’er and the others didn’t doubt this point. After they came here, they found out that the Radiant Empire has already been destroyed. Moreover the damage seemed to come from the southeast then headed northwest. It wouldn’t be strange if Zhao Hai met the people from the Atlanta Plane at that time.

Barbarian Shan looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Is mister confident in blocking the attack from the Atlanta Continent?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I’ve already considered this point. Don’t forget, there’s a strange and dangerous enemy currently in the Ark Continent. The Underworld!”

The Divine Race only understood about half of the underworld. Just as Zhao Hai said, the underworld was too strange. Even the Divine Race wouldn’t dare open a spatial rift towards the underworld since they didn’t have a full grasp of its properties.

It was because of this mystery that it was deemed dangerous. Fei’er and the others nodded, they also understood what Zhao Hai said. Now that the underworld’s spatial rift has been opened, its creatures would surely reach the center of the Ark Continent. Once the Atlanta Plane decided to conquer the Ark Continent, they would surely come into conflict with the Underworld. At that time, the Atlanta Plane would have no time attack Zhao Hai’s group.

After hearing this, Fei’er and the others relaxed. However, their expression suddenly changed, they remembered that the Underworld affected them as well.

The Underworld being in the Ark Continent meant that the underworld creatures would surely reach the spatial rift. When the time comes, they would be able to reach the Divine Realm. If they were to overrun the Divine Realm, then that would be extremely troublesome.

Zhao Hai looked at their expressions and immediately knew what they were thinking. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “You don’t have to worry, they won’t reach us for some time. We’ll deal with the Divine Race first. Even if we can’t finish it, we can still use the Taurus Continent as a battlefield. Additionally, we can also find ways to close the spatial rifts of your own planes. You can’t do it before because of the Divines, but now nobody will be able to stop it.”

Fei’er and the others thought that Zhao Hai’s idea was reasonable. In the past, the Divine Race were stopping them from closing the spatial rift. But now they weren’t under the Divine Race’s control anymore. As long as the Taurus Divines were dealt with, who would be able to stop them?

Fei’er nodded and said, “That’s true. So it looks like dealing with the Divine Race is our foremost goal. Mister, will we be attacking tomorrow?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It would be best if we do our attack tomorrow. Moreover, I’ll tell you that the Demons already had a prior meeting with the underworld. A spatial rift appeared in the Demon Realm that was connected to the Underworld. In the end, they were able to seal that rift. So as long as we buy enough time, we should be able to seal the spatial rift here. You don’t have to worry about it.”

Fei’er and the others felt their hearts loosen. Then Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Then we’ll prepare for the attack tomorrow. Right, Mister, can we have some liquor? Our people have been stressed all this time. They needed to some liquor to aid their weariness.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That is not a problem. I’ll have some people send it later. But don’t drink too much, we don’t want to affect your performance tomorrow.” Fei’er immediately nodded.

Zhao Hai discussed further details about tomorrow’s attack before taking his leave. While Zhao Hai left, Fei’er and the others remained inside the hall. Shan turned to Fei’er and said, “Fei’er, do you think that mister Zhao Hai’s words are true?”

Fei’er nodded, “They’re true. Actually, he only told that in order to tell us that the attack on the Divine Race isn’t only about revenge. He needed a chance to bind them so that he can deal with the underworld.”

Yue nodded, “That would be good. Mister Zhao Hai’s strength is formidable. If he can face the Divine Race, then we would be more confident in defeating them as well.”

At this time, Fei’er’s tone turned serious, “However, we can’t count on Mister Zhao Hai at all times. We need to make him understand that our three races aren’t worse than him. Otherwise, we’ll lose any courage to look at mister in the eye.”

Shan and Yue weren’t fools, they immediately understood what Fei’er meant. Therefore, both of them nodded.

To put it bluntly, although Zhao Hai was their ally in dealing with a common enemy, their alliance was actually quite frail. There was small resentment between them so who knows if Zhao Hai would use some plot to deal with them in the future. Because of this, they needed to keep their right to speech in this alliance. Otherwise, the only ones to suffer losses would be them.

Fei’er looked at the two and said, “Alright, let’s go back and prepare. Tomorrow, we need to fight against  the Divines. It’s best if we combine our three armies, otherwise we’ll look weak in comparison to mister Zhao Hai.”

The two nodded, then after exchanging a few more words they dispersed.

After Zhao Hai returned to the Space, he immediately arranged his undead to deliver some liquor to Fei’er and the others. Zhao Hai didn’t spy on Fei’er and the others since he knew that they would make the right choice. This alliance could only bring benefits, especially to the three races. It would be a stupid idea to separate from it.

At this time, Zhao Hai was focused on the Atlanta Plane’s situation. After two days of observation, he came to know that the Atlanta Plane didn’t have any countries. Also, he came to know that Axe’s family is called the O’Neal Family.

Axe’s status in his family wasn’t low, so this allowed him to listen to the things discussed by the family. This was quite fortunate for Zhao Hai because he would also be able to listen to the O’Neal family’s discussions. Upon eavesdropping, Zhao Hai was also able to gauge the strength of the family.

However, when the family discussed about their magic armors, Zhao Hai was like a duck listening to thunder and lightning. He was completely clueless regarding what they were talking about.

Although he couldn’t find out about the power of those magic armors, Zhao Hai could still understand some of the words of the family. It seems like the family’s magic armors were no less than 100 thousand, this wasn’t a small amount.

Imagine having a battle on Earth involving 100 thousand tanks. What scene would that show? Now replace those tanks with mechas.

However, if the O’Neal family were to attack the Ark Continent, they wouldn’t be able to do it in a day or two. They still need some time to move and prepare their magic armors. Also, the O’Neal family doesn’t want to inform the other families about the newly appeared spatial rift. It can be said that they wanted to take the whole continent for themselves. Because of this, the preparation needed for the task would take a bit longer. It might take a few months or so before they are finished.

Naturally, the O’Neal family wouldn’t just do nothing. At the very least, they had already located the spatial rift and placed a thousand magic armor soldiers to watch over it. This way, even if the Ark Continent were to find out, they would have no way of closing it down.

For the O’Neal family’s approach, Zhao Hai didn’t intend to stop it. He just wanted the O’Neal family to attack the Continent so that he can acquire some magic armors and give them to the Goblins to study. At this time, Zhao Hai had sent some literate undead to the Goblins in order to teach them. And it seems like the Goblins were learning very fast.

Zhao Hai was now able to make sense about why the heads of the Goblins were too big. It seems like it had something to do with their learning and thinking capacity.

The living materials acquired from the Radiant Empire have also been given to the Goblins, besides the ones being provided to the Demons. Although they were old items, the Goblins were still very happy to get them.

While looking at the Goblins’ expressions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but think about the initial expression that his slaves had. When the slaves received their first belongings, they also had the same reaction.

Although the slaves’ lives had been improved in Haven Island, you can only see few slaves wearing gold and silver. This was because their pursuit wasn’t based on riches. Instead, they were coming after their ability. Even if they had no talent in magic or battle qi, the slaves were still working hard on their craft.

The reason why the slaves were doing this was because in their heart, Zhao Hai the most importance. They knew that the greater their ability, the greater help they could provide Zhao Hai. Because of this, they made sure to focus on improving themselves every day. This action touched Zhao Hai’s heart.

Zhao Hai was now hoping that the Goblins would become the same as the slaves. He believed that once the Goblins regain their previous vigor, they would be able to make even more powerful magic armors.

After thinking about those magic armors, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get the urge to understand why the Divines decided to destroy the Goblin civilization. Because of this, Zhao Hai summoned a high ranking Divine Race general. He wanted to get the exact details as to why the Divines decided to eliminate the Goblins.

This general has been transformed by Zhao Hai into an advanced undead specifically to provide intel regarding the Divine Race. However, since he has been quite busy, Zhao Hai was never able to ask things in detail.

Chapter 842: Secret

Zhao Hai sat there silently in the living room. He had just listened to the undead general about the reason why the Divine Race decided to eliminate the Goblins. Initially, Zhao Hai thought that the Divines were scared of the Goblins’ technology so they decided to destroy their civilization before everything gets out of hand.

However, after listening to the explanation, Zhao Hai discovered that things weren’t as simple as he imagined. The Divine Race destroyed the Goblins not only because of the technology, but also because they were asked to do so by Lu Wei.

Lu Wei usually gave the Divines an order through the shadows. Every few days or so, the Divines would make a report to Lu Wei, telling him about the events happening in the Divine Realm.

The Divine Race’s destruction of the Goblins happened nearly a thousand years ago. At that time, Lu Wei’s appearance was the same as his appearance when Zhao Hai saw him. Because of this, the Divines thought that Lu Wei must have been god.

Eliminating the Goblins was an order given by Lu Wei himself. At that time, the Goblins had just started to make their iron golems. Naturally, the Divine Race had heard about this and reported it to Lu Wei.

After hearing the report, Lu Wei actually paid great attention to it and immediately ordered the Divine Race to destroy the Goblins at all cost, and they weren’t allowed to develop their technology in the future. Since the Divines also felt threatened by the iron golems, they immediately agreed. It was precisely because of these two reasons that the Goblin civilization was suddenly destroyed, all inheritances were cut off.

This thing might seem like nothing special, however, in Zhao Hai’s mind, it felt somewhat strange.

It was impossible for the Goblins to know about the existence of Lu Wei, he didn’t appear before the Goblins before. So why did he immediately order the destruction of the Goblin civilization once they made their iron golems? This was too unusual.

There was another thing that confused Zhao Hai. If Lu Wei was really opposed to these magical constructs, then how could the existence of the Atlanta Plane be explained? Their mechas were more advanced than the iron golems made by the Goblins. So why did Lu Wei allow the Atlanta Plane to prosper with their magic armors while he destroyed the Goblins for making iron golems? Something was definitely not right.

Laura and the others were also confused as they all frowned. They were smart people so they were able to notice this peculiarity.

Laura suddenly opened her mouth and said, “Brother Hai, maybe Lu Wei suffered a loss from these iron golems before. And because of this, he didn’t want the goblins to make their own.”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “That shouldn’t be the reason. If Lu Wei had really suffered a loss against those magic constructs, he shouldn’t have stopped the Goblins from making them. Instead, he would have just studied them to find some weak point that he could exploit in the future. Moreover, why would the Atlanta Plane have magic armors while the Divine Race didn’t? Isn’t that a little too strange?”

Laura and the others nodded, they were truly confused about this. Zhao Hai looked at the monitor and said, “Perhaps we can only find out once we reach the Immortal Cultivation Realm. We’re just wasting time thinking about it right now.”

Laura nodded, “Then Brother Hai should take a rest. Tomorrow, we still need to attack the Divine Race’s defensive line.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “It looks like we need to use the Domain Weapon tomorrow. We need to deal with the Divine Race in the shortest time. We don’t want them to have an opportunity to fight back.”

Laura agreed, “Right, but it won’t be very easy. The Divine Race would be prepared for our javelins, magic cannons, and formations. Dealing with them using the same methods would be a challenge.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “I know what to do. Besides, with our current strength, I doubt they would be able to resist. Nothing will go wrong, you can rest assured.”

The rest of the day quickly passed. The next day, Zhao Hai woke up early then he called the Demon Dragon King to lead the Devil Legion. He also took his undead out before he met Fei’er and the others. This enormous party then started to go towards the Divine Race’s defensive line.

After the alliance gathered, the Divine Race immediately sounded their horns. It didn’t take long before the defensive line started to move.

Zhao Hai didn’t even think about these defending people. He knew that it would be impossible for them to stop the alliance army’s advance.

Zhao Hai had the group slowly form as they advanced towards the Divine Race’s defensive line. And just like what was expected, the defenses differed compared to before. Their magic cannons were placed indoors, with only the tip seen outside. This limits the flexibility of the cannons, but it made the cannons more secure.

Moreover, there were also additional things installed. Zhao Hai glanced at the new additions and could see some ballista-like things. It seems like the Divine Race were really placed in a very disadvantageous position. They were even compelled to take these kinds of things out.

Fei’er and the others were standing next to Zhao Hai. Things haven’t started yet, so they don’t have to be with their armies to take command. Therefore, they went to Zhao Hai’s side to discuss additional matters.

Fei’er looked at the Divine Race’s defensive line and frowned, “It seems like breaking through won’t be easy. Don’t underestimate those structures made to shelter the magic cannons. Those aren’t made with ordinary magic. It’s a kind of magic developed by the Divine Race in the past few years. Those structures are very hard, no worse than steel. In the Divine Realm, this magic is called iron earth spell.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he raised his eyebrow and said, “Iron earth? Interesting. Although the Divine Race didn’t research any new weapons, it seems like they are more skillful when it comes to using magic.”

Fei’er agreed and said, “The Divine Race have indeed become more skillful when it comes to magic. Moreover, their research made a lot of new magic spells. However, not many people were interested in them and it had little use to the military. It seems like the Divines have brought over some people from the magic academy this time.”

Zhao Hai looked curiously at Fei’er and said, “Magic academy? What is that?”

Fei’er smiled faintly and said, “The magic academy is a place the Divines use to research magic. That is also the place where children go to study magic. However, those who are admitted mostly belonged to Nobles, Royal Clans, and talented people. Their strength is formidable. The students and teachers of the academy can go against a regiment of God-ranks.”

Zhao Hai stared, he gave out a light ‘hoh’ before he said, “I didn’t think that the Divine Race would have a place like that. Good, it’s good that people from the academy came. It seems like the Divine Race has reached a dire state.”

Fei’er nodded, “Right. In the Divine Realm, the status of the magic academy is very high. If they aren’t in dire straits, the Taurus Divines wouldn’t have asked for their help. However, with the magic academy here, our troubles wouldn’t be small.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “That doesn’t matter. Let’s try attacking first. Let’s see how they receive it.” After he said that, the army had already surrounded the defensive line. Then they proceeded to enter the Divine Race’s firing distance.

Zhao Hai waved his hand to make the army stop. Zhao Hai looked at the defensive line before he waved his hand once more. A squad of about fifty thousand made one cone formation and threw themselves towards the defensive line.

The Divine Race was very clear that this was only a probe. However, they knew that they couldn’t just let this small squad off. Who knows what things were installed inside those undead.

This squad hadn’t entered the firing distance yet but the cannons had already started to fire. White lights shot out from the defensive line and went straight towards the undead.

The undead squad suddenly sped up. They had a few javelins inside their bodies, but since they weren’t in fighting distance, they still kept flying forward.

Fei’er looked at the undead and couldn’t help but feel envy. The undead were really the best kinds of soldiers. They weren’t affected by pain nor were they afraid of death. Even if half of their bodies were wiped out, they could still continue to fight. No other army could achieve this.

However, Fei’er was also clear that other than Zhao Hai, no other person is able to command an undead army as large as this. The undead didn’t have their own thoughts, commanding them would need more than just an ordinary commander.

Naturally, Fei’er doesn’t know about the existence of the Space. He was comparing Zhao Hai to other dark mages. Ordinary undead could only receive commands such as advance, retreat, and attack. For them to exhibit such complex formations was completely impossible.

Fei’er and the others watched the undead acting like fish as they evaded the Divine Race’s barrage. Zhao Hai also discovered something about the magic cannons’ attack. These cannons could only target one person while causing minimal damage to those around the target. It looks like they were using water element stones to power the cannons.

Chapter 843: The Bastards, They Dare To Trick Me!

Then Zhao Hai changed his mind as he understood what was going on. The Divine Race did indeed use some magic crystals to power their magic cannons, however, the crystals were much worse compared what Zhao Hai had. Zhao Hai’s fire element crystals were able to do massive area damage. If the Divine Race’s cannons used an area attack, then the power of the cannons would be greatly reduced. They might not even be a threat for God-ranks or 9th ranks.

Zhao Hai wanted the fifty thousand undead to see what the defensive line had. Besides the magic cannons and ballistas, he wanted to see if there was anything else.

At this time, the undead had already reached their firing distance. They immediately took their javelins and proceeded to throw them towards the Divine Race.

But at the same time, the defensive line also released a batch of arrows. These arrows were fired from the ballistas. Their range was quite far, and the heads were bigger compared to the javelins thrown by the undead.

What Zhao Hai didn’t expect was the arrows actually managed to explode the undead. The undead squad were ravaged, a lot of them were directly smashed to pieces.

Zhao Hai gawked, then he raised an eyebrow as he chuckled, “Interesting. I didn’t expect the Divine Race to have this kind of weapon. Fei’er, do you know what those arrows are? Why did they explode?”

Fei’er’s expression was quite ugly, then he said, “It’s possible that they’re a secret weapon. I hadn’t heard about them before.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He didn’t care about it anymore as he waved his hand and released a hundred thousand undead. The 50 thousand that he lost was just a negligible amount.

However, the 100 thousand that Zhao Hai sent this time was different. The 50 thousand undead before didn’t have any defensive measures since Zhao Hai wanted to see how strong the magic cannons were. After seeing that the cannons were inferior, Zhao Hai became relieved. 9th ranks might die to the cannons, but God-ranks should be able to survive.

The reason why Zhao Hai sent a shield along with his undead this time was to see the properties of those new arrows. If those arrows could penetrate the shields, then more casualties would come up.

The Divine Race seemed to understand Zhao Hai’s plan. The small shield containing 100 thousand undead slowly entered the range of the magic cannons. As the undead approached, the magic cannons shot over and over. Zhao Hai also found a problem, although the shield was very good in defending, the people behind it can only wait for the attacks to finish before they could make their move. If the arrows could break through the shield, then the undead casualties would surely mount up.

The Divine Race kept attacking with their magic cannons, they wanted to consume the energy of the shield. They don’t want the undead to go too far into the frontlines, they alsol wanted to see the other cards in Zhao Hai’s hands.

However, the Divine Race had underestimated the shield made by Karen. This defensive formation can be used to defend a city, this was a testament to its defensive might. Although there weren’t any improvements to defensive formations for a long time, this also meant that they were already strong. It was difficult to improve because it had small shortcomings. If there were weaknesses anywhere, then they would’ve already been improved.

The power of the magic cannons used by the Divine Race was inferior compared to Zhao Hai’s. And now that those magic cannons were against a shield powered by Zhao Hai’s crystals, it was for certain that the cannons had no effect. The shield didn’t even tremble, it’s like the magic cannons were only giving it a scratch.

The Divines begane to panic, however, they quickly settled down. After entering the firing range of the ballistas, the defensive line began to launch their attacks once more. Zhao Hai didn’t let the undead use their javelins, he wanted to see how the Divine Race deals with it.

The arrows quickly came in contact with the shield. There was a fierce explosion on the point of impact. However, Zhao Hai was able to see that the shield only shook gently, it was still up!

Zhao Hai relaxed, then he immediately ordered the undead to throw their javelins. The javelins directly soared towards the ballistas. At this time, earthen walls suddenly rose up, blocking the javelins. However, the power of these blood lightning javelins was much stronger compared to the cannons or the arrows used by the Divine Race. The earthen walls were blown up after a few javelins hit them..

But still, Zhao Hai slightly frowned, it seems like this wall was also made out of iron earth magic. Otherwise, it wouldn’t have been this resistant to explosions. It seems like the Divine Race had made sufficient preparations this time.

Fei’er and the others’ expressions were also somewhat ugly. They have battled with Zhao Hai, so naturally they were aware about how strong these javelins were. They didn’t expect the other party’s earth walls to actually block a few of those javelins.

Fei’er turned to look at Zhao Hai, his gaze asking whether Zhao Hai had any means to deal with this. Zhao Hai turned to Fei’er and smiled, “The probe is at its end, we’ll start the official attack. I will have the undead go first, otherwise, our casualties would be too big. You go back and wait for my order.”

Fei’er and the others complied. Fei’er and the others were already convinced of Zhao Hai’s ability, so when they heard his words, they didn’t have any misgivings at all.

After Fei’er and the others left, Zhao Hai turned to the Demon Dragon King and said, “Demon Dragon, after I let the undead attack, don’t have your soldiers follow. Although their strength isn’t weak, their ranks aren’t high. I don’t want them to die in vain. Later on when I’m able to mass produce God-rank potions, we can promote their strength. Only then can they enter the battle.”

The Demon Dragon King gawked, then he nodded. He can understand why Zhao Hai would tell him this. Demons took bravery very seriously. If you let their armies into the battlefield but you refrain them from fighting, then they would treat it as an insult. If Zhao Hai didn’t explain these things, then the Demon Dragon King would think that Zhao Hai was looking down on them. When the time comes, it would create a misunderstanding.

Now that Zhao Hai took the effort to explain, the Demon Dragon King didn’t become offended, instead he even felt grateful. After seeing the Demon Dragon King nod, Zhao Hai said, “You go back to the Devil Legion. This time, don’t attack, just wait for my orders.” Demon Dragon gave his affirmation before he went back to the Devil Legion. Zhao Hai remained in his place, standing calmly in front of his dense undead army.

Zhao Hai looked at the Divine Race’s defensive line and then waved his hand. The undead immediately threw themselves towards the Divine Race’s defensive line. Now that the undead can charge behind a shield, they weren’t afraid of the magic cannons. Among them were huge undead carrying magic cannons. There were even some undead with larger bodies capable of carrying more magic cannons.

The large magic cannons were almost exclusively mounted on top of dragons. Dragons have the most strength among all of the undead, both their attack and defense were the best. Zhao Hai also moved forward with the undead army. At this time, their position was about two kilometers away from the Divine Race army. This distance was beyond the scope of the monitor, what Zhao Hai wanted to do now was to place the defensive line within the Space’s range so that he can use the undead with more flexibility.

Not long after Zhao Hai started his advance, the Divine Race’s cannon attack started to arrive. Although the magic cannons weren’t as good as Zhao Hai’s, their range was quite far and they were enough to deal with most 9th ranks. Moreover, the Divine Race had a lot more of those magic cannons compared to Zhao Hai. Also, the Divine Race’s cannons were under reinforced shelter, this prevented Zhao Hai from shooting them down.

However, Zhao Hai had his magic shield, so it was impossible for the cannons to do any damage to the undead army. Additionally, Zhao Hai also had his cannons. Once these cannons reach their range, the cannon fire would become two-ways.

Before long, Zhao Hai’s magic cannons had reached their range. With Zhao Hai’s order, about ten thousand lights began to approach the Divine Race’s defensive line.

Although the shelters were made out of reinforced magic, it was still impossible for it to sustain so much damage. So even if these shelters had blocked Zhao Hai’s attack, there were still parts where they had been destroyed.

At this moment, something unexpected appeared in Zhao Hai’s sight. The Divine Race’s ballistas suddenly shot their arrows. The undead army were yet to enter its firing range!

This was out of Zhao Hai’s expectation. Upon further observation, Zhao Hai discovered that these ballistas should have more range compared to those used in the Ark Continent. It seems like the Divine Race were holding back, they intentionally reduced their range!. Zhao Hai thought, those bastards, they dared to trick me!

At the thought of this, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get angry. He also took some ballistas with him. However, their range was worse than a 9th rank throwing javelins. They were used back in the Accra Mountain because of the height advantage. But in this battle, they weren’t that appropriate to use. It was better to have the undead carry javelins and throw it themselves.

Chapter 844: Lu Wei Appears

Zhao Hai looked at this situation and made a command in his mind. Then in the middle of the ballista troops, undead started to appear. All of these undead were God-ranks. Upon appearing, all the  undead proceeded to attack the Divines manning the ballistas.

These Divines didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have this trick, naturally they were caught off guard. Before long, the Divine Race didn’t have any means to fire their ballistas.

The God-rank undead that Zhao Hai sent were all from the Divine Race. Their fighting strength was no weaker than their brethren, conversely, they were even stronger in battle.

The other Divines quickly responded to the attack on the ballistas and sent support troops over. Zhao Hai knew that these support troops couldn’t be allowed to besiege the undead. If the undead were surrounded, then they would certainly suffer losses.

Zhao Hai immediately retrieved the God-rank undead back into the Space. Several of the undead took ballistas along.

However, the undead didn’t just retreat. After taking several ballistas along, they immediately left behind some blood lightning beads, destroying the Divine Race’s ballista shelter..

After destroying the ballistas, the Divine Race’s base became somewhat panicked. At this time, the magic cannon shelters were also being besieged by the undead. The sudden appearance of the undead once again surprised the Divines. Before the Divines respond, they were already killed by the undead.

One by one, Zhao Hai captured the magic cannon and ballista shelters. However, Zhao Hai didn’t relax. He expects that the Divine Race would have more than this. Therefore, Zhao Hai held Fei’er and the others back. He just had the undead continue on with their attack.

Just like Zhao Hai thought, as the undead proceeded another batch of light came out from behind the defensive line. One could see that the lights were from the cannons, there were also arrows trailing behind.

Zhao Hai saw this and understood that the Divine Race had set up two bases. The ones captured by Zhao Hai was a fake one. The real base was now armed and ready.

Moreover, Zhao Hai discovered that he couldn’t see any magic cannons nor ballistas in this base. Zhao Hai let the Space look into it but he couldn’t see anything. Behind the fake defensive line was just displayed as a huge white blot.

Besides the monitor, Zhao Hai also couldn’t see the cannons using his own eyes. It didn’t take long for Zhao Hai to understand that the Divine Race was using illusion formations to hide their base. This would make it difficult for Zhao Hai to find their ballistas and magic cannons.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, the Divines really prepared well this time. But will this stop him? The Divine Race were too naive.

As the undead advanced, they suddenly discovered that they were blocked. In front of them was a shield barring their entry.

From time to time, there were cannon fire and arrows coming from behind the shield. Zhao Hai’s undead were completely under attack right now, without the chance to fight back.

It’s good that Zhao Hai’s army also had their own defensive formation. Otherwise, the would’ve suffered huge losses. However, Zhao Hai knew that this couldn’t drag on. The Divine Race were certainly buying time to deal with the Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and the Winged Pegasus people. If they were done dealing with the three races, then they would begin to turn on the Ark Continent. At that time, the losses would be bigger. For Zhao Hai, this was completely disadvantages, he couldn’t have this situation happen.

Zhao Hai finally made his move. He established his Domain and then released the sword carriage. The Domain turned into a giant as he held the Domain Weapon, ready to strike through the protective shield.

There was nothing in front of it, but the giant sword seems to be blocked by a transparent bubble. There was no way for it to go through.

Zhao Hai increased the strength of his thrust, making the sword sink further. Then before long, the bubble exploded, revealing the huge base in front.

This base had magic cannons, ballistas, soldiers, summoners, and cavalry. At this time, there were people in the base wearing mage robes who were vomiting blood. The other Divines looked in shock at Zhao Hai and the Domain Weapon.

Zhao Hai didn’t delay as he made another move and killed his way towards the Divines. At the same time, he also gave Fei’er and the others an order to attack.

Zhao Hai believes that this was the Divine Race’s final stronghold, it was impossible for it to become yet another fake base. Once Fei’er and the others received the order, they immediately charged towards the Divine Race.

However, the Divine Race were quick to recover. They started to go all out, there were light beams, arrows, javelins flying up in the air. War cries could be heard all along the battlefield.

At this time, the summoners also made their move. Under the protection of the soldiers, they started to chant their spell. Upon hearing this, Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but change. This was the incantation used to summon Lu Wei.

Sure enough, after the incantation was finished, white lights suddenly shot out from the summoners. When the lights coalesced, a spatial rift appeared in the sky. From that spatial rift, a shadow of a person came out.

After seeing this person, Zhao Hai’s pupils shrunk. This person was no other than Lu Wei. In the past, Lu Wei used the pagoda as a medium to send his incarnation to the Ark Continent. That incarnation almost killed Zhao Hai. Fortunately, Zhao Hai was able to deal with the situation.

Zhao Hai knew that Lu Wei wouldn’t just stop at that. But he didn’t think that Lu Wei would send another incarnation this early. Does he think that he could deal with Zhao Hai this time?

Zhao Hai just stood within his Domain and coldly looked at Lu Wei. Lu Wei was also looking at Zhao Hai. After some time, Lu Wei smiled and laughed before he said, “I didn’t think that you would actually survive. Moreover, you also dared to face my incarnation once more. Hahaha. It seems like trash still had their uses. I need to thank them for giving me the opportunity to take my revenge.”

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei and then sneered, “What? Are you confident in beating me this time? Don’t be too naive. Last time, you even managed to gift me a magic treasure.”

Lu Wei looked at Zhao Hai with hatred as he said, “Don’t worry, this young master will surely take your soul out and refine it. I’ll make sure that you suffer eternal torment without any way to reincarnate!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly as he retrieved his Domain and stored the sword carriage. He knew that these things were useless against Lu Wei. Then while standing still, Zhao Hai took the tiny pagoda out. The pagoda was glittering and shiny, it was quite attractive.

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei and said, “I know that you’re quite strong. It seems like your avatar this time is much stronger compared to the one before. But that all of that is useless against me. Hahahaha. For you, it might be difficult to be strong, but to me, it’s quite easy. Do you know why? Because you are already old, you’re past your prime!”

Lu Wei was shocked upon seeing the pagoda on Zhao Hai’s hand. His eyes couldn’t hide his astonishment, but it was quickly replaced with the look of greed. He looked up at the sky and loudly laughed before he said, “Good, you’re quite good, kid. I didn’t expect your crafting skill to be this high. You actually refined the pagoda and added ten thousand year old ice. Hahahaha. Good, good. As long as I retrieve the pagoda, my strength would increase. It seems like I need to give you my gratitude.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly before he gently swung the pagoda. The bells on the pagoda started to chime. The Divines who heard this sound immediately had a look of suffering on their faces. On the other hand, Lu Wei’s expression couldn’t help but change.

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei and said, “So you discovered the artifact spirit. It’s different from before, no? Do you think that connecting to your soul would make the pagoda return to you? You’re too naive. I’ve already destroyed your soul inside the pagoda.”

Lu Wei’s complexion changed. His shocked face turned to Zhao Hai, “This is impossible. How can you know all of these? This is impossible!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “Sect Elder Lu, everything is possible in this world. Since I managed to defeat you last time, I can defeat you this time as well.” After that, Zhao Hai had the pagoda fly up. As the pagoda rose, it immediately turned into a massive pagoda capable of holding the heavens and the earth.

The bells on the pagoda chimed, all who heard the sound felt their minds go tranquil. Their heart for battle was immediately quenched.

Lu Wei knew about this kind of spiritual attack. He just didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be able to achieve it here.

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei and smiled. He waved his hand and had the pagoda charge towards Lu Wei’s incarnation. At the same time, Lu Wei waved his hand and retrieved a carved shield made out of the head of an animal. Once the pagoda hit the shield, it shook, however, it wasn’t able to push through.

Lu Wei saw this and couldn’t help but smile. He looked at Zhao Hai and laughed, “It’s like a wax tipped spearhead, completely useless. You’re dead, kid!”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but show his amazement. He turned to Lu Wei and said, “i didn’t expect your incarnation to be this powerful. It seems like you really intend to deal with me this time.”

Lu Wei had a wicked gaze as he looked at Zhao Hai, then with a cold voice he replied, “You’ve made a huge mistake. I manage this place, and it would provide me with faith power. But because of you, all faith power disappeared. Not only did I lose faith power, I also lost an avatar. I became a laughinstock in the sect because of that. So how could I just let you go off easily? If I can’t take your soul out and make you suffer in eternal hell, I won’t be able to erase my hatred!”

Zhao Hai’s expression changed. He took the pagoda back to protect his body. At the same time, Lu Wei patted his small bag and took out a ship.

This ship was divided into 18 floors. It’s body was fully pitch black. On the ship were black masts with the character for ‘prison’ written in red ink.

On each floor on the ship were murals. Each mural depicted various punishments for 18 different sins. The eighteen floors corresponded to the 18 hells!

After the ship was taken out, it immediately floated in mid-air and turned into an extremely huge ship. The ship was completely covered with a ghastly mist. There were also wailing coming out of it from time to time. All those who heard these wailings would feel pain in their heart.

Zhao Hai’s complexion turned ugly, the pagoda’s bells continued to ring as it resisted the wailing emitted by the ship. At the same time, Zhao Hai also made a retreat. His face slowly turned blue as the veins on his head started to darken.

Lu Wei looked at Zhao Hai’s appearance and couldn’t’ help but let some steam out from within. Although he had suffered several losses before, it was either from those with the same rank or higher. He could still accept those losses, but Zhao Hai? This person was just a single dust in a small plane that he managed. This person actually defeated his incarnation and stole an artifact from him. How could Lu Wei just accept it? He was indescribably mad.

After seeing that Zhao Hai retreated, Lu Wei immediately had the ship collide with the pagoda. The ship’s speed was very fast, causing the wailing sound to get sharper. With no time to respond, Zhao Hai had to hit the ship with the pagoda.

The pagoda violently shook, a fissure can clearly be seen on its body.

Zhao Hai’s expression turned ugly, his body emitted a layer of white light and shot it towards the pagoda. But at this moment, the second impact of the ship came. The pagoda shook even more violently. Zhao Hai couldn’t stop the blood from going out of his mouth as he made a sudden retreat.

Naturally, it was impossible for Lu Wei to let Zhao Hai retreat like that. His body appeared on the back of the ship as they went on to chase Zhao Hai.

Chapter 845: Great Dao Lotus Formation

Fei’er and the others were also able to see this fight. For them, the scales of the battle was beyond their capability.

They had seen Zhao Hai use the domain weapon before, but to be honest, after seeing Lu Wei’s ship, they were certain that the domain weapon would shatter upon meeting this ship.

Their heads couldn’t help but keep looking towards Zhao Hai and Lu Wei, their clash was just too shocking.

Similarly shocked was the Demon Dragon King. He had seen Lu Wei’s portrait before, however he didn’t see him with his own eyes. Because of this, he still had some disbelief regarding this matter. But now that Lu Wei was literally in front of him, it was impossible for him to reject it.

Lu Wei hasn’t changed his appearance. Therefore, he still looked the same as the one in the portrait. He didn’t even change his clothes, it’s not possible for the Demon Dragon King to mistake him with someone else.

At this time, Zhao Hai can see that this ghastly ship was the medium that Lu Wei was using to manifest his incarnation. Moreover, the ship was certainly more powerful than the soul sucking pagoda.

Zhao Hai was currently retreating while spurting out blood. The alliance members were stunned. They knew that if Zhao Hai cannot stop Lu Wei, then they could only wait for their deaths. They couldn’t help but get worried for Zhao Hai’s situation.

The ones focusing on the fight wasn’t only the alliance, the Divines were concerned about the result as well. In fact, this summoning was because of Lu Wei. He couldn’t stomach the humiliation from last time, so he commanded the Divine Race to summon him. He wanted to deal with Zhao Hai himself.

Lu Wei’s plan was good, but he didn’t think that Zhao Hai was expecting him to come back at some point. Therefore, Zhao Hai had been ready, causing Lu Wei to have problems in swiftly getting rid of him.

As the chase went on, they eventually arrived back at the Ark Continent. At this moment, Zhao Hai stopped, he stood still as he smiled at Lu Wei.

After seeing Zhao Hai’s expression, Lu Wei stared. He stopped his chase and carefully went forward. He was afraid that Zhao Hai might have some traps. Lu Wei looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Kid, there’s no need to be mysterious. Either way, you will die today!”

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei as he smiled faintly and said, “I just want to thank mister Lu Wei for giving me yet another magic treasure. Hahaha. Aren’t you confused as to why I stopped? Then see it for yourself.” After he said this, Zhao Hai’s body vanished.

Lu Wei stopped and looked around, there seems to be no change in the surroundings. But the complete disappearance of Zhao Hai took him by surprise. Then he operated the ship to fly forward. However, after some time, there seems to be no change.

The scenery kept passing by him, but Lu Wei still couldn’t see Zhao Hai. This confused Lu Wei even more. He went in all directions but Zhao Hai still wasn’t there.

Lu Wei’s complexion turned gloomy. He suddenly thought that Zhao Hai had left him here to go and deal with the Divine Race.

After thinking about this, Lu Wei immediately turned around towards the Divine Realm. But when the turned, he was suddenly shocked. The rift joining the Ark Continent and the Divine Race had vanished!

Lu Wei stared, he looked all around and saw no changes in the surrounding. He tried to fly forward and the scenery moved with him, when he stopped, the scenery stopped. Everything was normal besides the fact that the spatial rift had vanished. It was this abnormality that Lu Wei understood, Zhao Hai had trapped him in a weird array!

An array was a special method of attacking and trapping someone in the immortal cultivation plane. It didn’t exist in the Ark Continent, nor did it exist in the Divine Realm. The magic formations that the Ark Continent was completely different than these magic arrays.

But generally speaking, magic formations and magic arrays both used the power of the heavens to serve its purpose. However, compared to formations, arrays were more profound, their formidability was several folds more. Magic formations of the Ark Continent would look like drawings of a three-year old while magic arrays were something studied by university students.

In the immortal cultivation realm, no matter what you do, you must use an array. Otherwise, things would be difficult. If one makes an immortal cave, one should use an array. When one fought, arrays were crucial. Even in crafting weapons, arrays held an important role. It can be said that arrays and the people of the immortal cultivation realm were mutually related.

Because of this , after several tries, Lu Wei was able to affirm that he has been trapped in Zhao Hai’s array.

Now he can understand why Zhao Hai vanished. He didn’t go and kill the Divine Race, he was operating the array.

Lu Wei was indeed inside Zhao Hai’s formation, however, contrary to what he thought, the formation didn’t need someone to control it. It was because the place where Lu Wei was now was inside Zhao Hai’s Dao Lotus.

After Zhao Hai controlled the dao lotus, he discovered that it had countless uses. Not only could it help him cultivate, it can also attack and trap his enemies. Most importantly, the dao lotus was like a living being. It can absorb energy from the world and cultivate.

The dao lotus was constantly helping Zhao Hai in his cultivation, increasing his level all the time. At the same time it also absorbs some energy for itself. For every seven units of energy that Zhao Hai absorbed, the lotus would have three units absorbed for its own cultivation.

But during a fight, all the energy that the lotus absorbed were all given to Zhao Hai. Because of this, Zhao Hai wasn’t dissatisfied of the lotus taking his energy for itself. In any case, the dao lotus was his innate life weapon. The stronger the lotus got, the stronger he would be.

The reason why Zhao Hai retreated was because he was baiting Lu Wei towards the dao louts, only then could he do something to the incarnation. Lu Wei’s projection was very strong. Even if Zhao Hai went all out, it would still be difficult. However, if Lu Wei was trapped inside the lotus, things would be different.

The Dao Lotus was itself a magical array, and it was very strong. Zhao Hai even compared it to the tiny pagoda. In the end, the pagoda couldn’t compare to the lotus.

Zhao Hai didn’t want Lu Wei to know about the lotus. Therefore, Zhao hai used the Space to arrange the lotus array in the Ark Continent. Then he showed that he was weak to lure Lu Wei in.

Zhao Hai doesn’t believe that Lu Wei’s incarnation would be able to break out of the dao lotus. There simply was no way for him to go out. Lu Wei thought that he was inside Zhao Hai’s array, but he didn’t think that he was trapped inside a magic treasure.

Zhao Hai was in the Space looking calmly at Lu Wei. Lu Wei was currently standing in place and had a thinking expression on his face. Zhao Hai understood that Lu Wei must have discovered his current situation and was trying to think of a way of breaking out.

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei and then at the ship. In fact, they were in the same place since the beginning, they didn’t leave. Zhao Hai knew that Lu Wei was still quite lucky since the attacks were yet to come. Once Zhao Hai starts attacking, Lu Wei wouldn’t be having a good time.

At this time, Lu Wei started to move. He patted the bag on his side and took out a plate. Along with the plate were a lot of small flags.

Lu Wei raised his hand as the plate flew out from his hand. Then the plate slowly grew larger before it buried itself in the ground. At this point, the small flags had increased their size to a normal flag.

Lu Wei walked inside the area covered by the plate and pulled out a flag and placed it in the middle. Zhao Hai saw Lu Wei continue to go about and place the flags on certain places. His array seemed to be controlled by the plate and the flags.

Zhao Hai didn’t worry too much as he spectated Lu Wei. This was because Zhao Hai had found out that everything has already been overpowered by the Dao Lotus, including the plate and flag array. Although Lu Wei could see some effects, Zhao Hai knew that the plate and flags were already broken. At this point, the effects were only an illusion made by the Dao Lotus.

However, Lu Wei didn’t know about this. He was still planting flags as he used his formation. He kept grabbing phantom threads in the surroundings, not knowing that they were illusions made by the lotus.

After a some time, Lu Wei saw a crack in the space. He flew out of the the plate’s range and looked around. He nodded before he entered the crack.

Zhao Hai knew that things had reached its end. This was because Lu Wei was advancing towards the center of the lotus. As long as he flew forward, the Dao Lotus would proceed to attack him.

Before long, Lu Wei’s flight speed had slowed down. His speed kept decreasing as though he was mired in a swamp.

Naturally, Lu Wei quickly realized what was happening. His complexion changed as he immediately stopped. Then he ordered his ship to retreat. However, he didn’t know that invisible forces had already surrounded him, proceeding to attack!

Chapter 846: Human Fueled Ship

Zhao Hai looked at Lu Wei and knew that it was time to end things. Fei’er and the others were still fighting in the Divine Realm, so things couldn’t be delayed. Since physical their physical attacks were useless against Lu Wei’s avatar, then Zhao Hai might as well use soul attacks.

After thinking up to here, Zhao Hai immediately released the pagoda to help the dao lotus to deal with Lu Wei. Actually, the pagoda wasn’t badly damaged at all. Zhao Hai just deliberately seem like it was broken so that he can lure Lu Wei in. One must know that ten thousand year old ice couldn’t be easily broken.

Lu Wei was in big trouble now. He was continually attacked from all sides. In Zhao Hai’s eyes, there was just a cloudless sky. But for Lu Wei, he was surrounded by dark clouds that attacked him with constant lightning strikes.

Lu Wei felt distressed while receiving these attacks. He had discovered that these lightning were fatal to him.

Zhao Hai thought that these attacks wouldn’t do great damage to Lu Wei. After all, Lu Wei was only a projection, because of this, he had the pagoda go to help.

Actually, Zhao Hai’s understanding of the dao lotus was still too limited. In fact, the dao lotus’ main attacks were dealt directly to the soul. Otherwise, it would have been impossible for it to trap the enemy.

However, Zhao Hai having the pagoda help was the right decision. Although the pagoda couldn’t compare to the dao lotus, its soul attacks were more sinister. The Dao Lotus would just attack the soul while the pagoda would directly swallow it, refining the soul to become its own energy.

Lu Wei didn’t know that Zhao Hai had sent the pagoda after him. At this point, he was commanding the ship to resist the various attacks.

At this time, Lu Wei was resisting the pressure mounted on top of him. But suddenly, the pressure vanished. Lu Wei stared blankly. At this moment, a strong suction suddenly came from the top of his head, sucking Lu Wei in. Upon sensing this attack, Lu Wei immediately commanded the ship to counter the suction. However, he suddenly found that his connection to the ship has vanished.

Lu Wei became surprised. His divine sense was attached to the ship. If he lost contact with the ship, then this body would lose its strength.

Lu Wei looked around and discovered that he had arrived inside a room. It seems like he was inside a pagoda. Upon thinking about this, Lu Wei’s expression sank. He understood that he had been trapped inside the soul sucking pagoda.

He was only a simple soul right now, his formidable strength was gone. At this point, he was as good as dead.

However, Lu Wei also thought that this was an opportunity. Because he remembered that he just used the ship to crack the pagoda. As long as he blows a part of his soul and destroys the pagoda, then he could have the opportunity to ascend back to the immortal cultivation realm.

The reason why Lu Wei thought about this was because although his soul was inside the pagoda, his divine will was still inside the ship. As long as his soul escapes the grasp of the pagoda, then the ship would still be under his control. Although he can’t defeat Zhao Hai, the ship can still return.

After thinking up to here, Lu Wei immediately blew himself up. After a bang, Lu Wei’s soul became weaker. However, the Pagoda actually didn’t move. While Lu Wei was stunned, a lot of mouths suddenly appeared, ripping Lu Wei’s body to pieces.

As Lu Wei’s soul was shredded, the ship finally lost its master. It slowly shrank until it became as small as one’s palm. Then it proceeded to fall towards the ground.

Naturally, Zhao Hai won’t have the ship fall into the ground. A spatial rift appeared below the ship and then absorbed it into the Space.

When the ship entered the Space, a prompt was immediately heard, “Hostile program detected in the Space. Proceeding to subdue. Program has surrendered. Item with rich death qi detected. Its uses need further research. Host is be able to use the item right now.”

Zhao Hai gave a sigh of relief. Then he proceeded to input his energy inside the ship. As it absorbed Zhao Hai’s energy, the ship also became larger.

Zhao Hai’s energy caused the ship to enlarge up to a meter long. Then Zhao Hai carefully inspected the ghastly ship. He discovered that the ship had more energy amplification compared to domain weapons. After his energy enters the ship, the amount that would be used was countless times more. Naturally, domain weapons could do the same, but they were much worse compared to the ship. Compared to domain weapons, the ship could amplify energy 10 thousand times more. The difference was just too far.

Zhao Hai gave a satisfied nod. After receiving the dao lotus and pagoda, Zhao Hai released the ship and stood on its bow as he headed towards the Divine Realm’s spatial rift.

In the Divine Realm, the undead, Demons, Thunder Clan, Barbarians, and Winged Pegasus were still fighting against the Divine Race army. At this point, the Divine Race were at a high morale. They just saw Lu Wei hit Zhao Hai to the point of vomiting blood. In their opinion, Zhao Hai’s time was nearing its end.

At the same time, Fei’er and the others’ morale was also greatly affected. They were unaware of it, but they were now depending on Zhao Hai. Now that they saw him getting injured, their mood couldn’t help but sink.

At this time, a ship slowly entered the Divine Realm. When the Divines saw this, they couldn’t’ help but let out a loud cheer. Now that the ship has returned, this meant that Zhao Hai was gone.

However, the Divine Race’s cheer came at an abrupt stop. This was because the person standing on the ship’s bow wasn’t Lu Wei.

Those present focused their gazes and found out that it was actually Zhao Hai. The Divines were completely dumbfounded while Fei’er and the others felt indescribably glad.

Zhao Hai looked at the Divines and coldly smiled, “What? Still waiting for your deity? Sorry but he will not be coming back.”

All of the Divines were staring at Zhao Hai. They didn’t expect that Zhao Hai, who had just vomited blood, would actually eliminate their Deity.

Zhao Hai didn’t become polite as he immediately directed the ship to hammer towards the Divine Race. The speed of the ship was very fast, the dazed Divines didn’t even have time to recover before they had been smashed by Zhao Hai. Blood immediately splattered in the air. Those hit by the ship were almost immediately flattened and killed. Those who didn’t die were crippled. At this time, the dead bodies were all sucked into the ship.

It wasn’t Zhao Hai taking the bodies into the Space, instead, the ship was taking them for itself. This caused Zhao Hai to be slightly stunned. Then he used his divine sense to scan the ship. He discovered that the ship was refining the corpses of those who died. Upon refining, the energy produced was used to power the ship. At the same time, the souls of those who died were transformed into ghosts. This ship actually used people to fuel itself.

The more people it refined, the more imposing the ship became. Zhao Hai finally understood that this ship was of the devil attribute. It would fuel itself with the bodies of its enemies, making it stronger as more people were killed.

While Zhao Hai was inspecting the ship, Fei’er and the others immediately took the chance to overrun the Divine Race. At this point, the Divine Race’s morale had sunk into a steep decline.

After Zhao Hai finished his inspection, he discovered that there were no longer enemy soldiers in front of him. The Divine Race army had unexpectedly been routed.

Zhao Hai quickly understood why this was the case. Lu Wei’s status with the Divine Race was very high. Therefore, the more powerful Lu Wei seemed, the more confidence the Divine Race had. And now that Lu Wei was killed, the morale of the Divine Race would naturally be greatly reduced. At this point, it would be hard for them to stop the attack of the alliance.

After beating the Divine Race army, Zhao Hai and the others didn’t stay. Instead, they advanced into the Taurus Continent. While they advanced, Zhao Hai came across something that surprised him. They had just passed through a village with no person inside.

Zhao Hai carefully looked at the village. It seems like the people inside didn’t move out recently, but days before. Moreover, their retreat seems to be organized. Everything that was usable and consumable were all taken away.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but knit his brows. Did the Divine Race know that they couldn’t block the alliance?

At this time, Fei’er and the others also arrived by Zhao Hai’s side. At this point, Zhao Hai had already stored the ship, but Fei’er and the others were looking at him with respect. Zhao Hai and Lu Wei’s battle had made them understand the disparity between their strengths.

Zhao Hai looked at Fei’er and said, “Where did the Divine Race retreat to?”

Fei’er immediately answered, “They should be in Holy Light City, the nearest big city in this region. It has a population of more than 20 million. Moreover, its defensive capability is quite strong. From what I can remember, there should be about 5000 magic cannons protecting the city. It also has plenty of ballista. Most importantly, the city is protected by a strong defensive formation.”

Zhao Hai frowned when he heard this, then he said, “How strong is the Divine Race’s defensive formation?”

Fei’er answered, “Generally, the defensive formations of the Divine Race are quite strong. Even God ranks would have problems breaking through it. This was because of the foreign races. The Taurus Divines knew their capabilities so they strengthened the defenses of their cities.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Let’s stop here first, have everyone rest. At the same time, send people to the spatial rift while I have my undead repair the Divine Race’s defensive line. We might have use for it later on.”

Fei’er and the others immediately nodded before turning around to leave. After they left, Zhao Hai frowned. He looked towards the Taurus Continent, wondering about what their plan was.

Chapter 847: Hell King’s Ship

Naturally, Zhao Hai wasn’t just looking at the scenery. To be honest, the Divine Realm wasn’t that much better compared to the Ark Continent. The grass and landscape here was no different. This was what confused Zhao Hai.

At this time, Zhao Hai wanted to know why the people of the village retreated. Did they expect Lu Wei to fail? Is that the reason? However, if that was the case, then the Divine Race’s rout was unjustified.

If the Divine Race didn’t have any confidence in Lu Wei, then they wouldn’t have lost their will when he was eliminated. Now that they retreated, this meant that they trusted Lu Wei to succeed. But if they were confident in Lu Wei, then they wouldn’t have evacuated their people.

It was a contradictory thing, Zhao Hai was unable to make sense of it. After all, he doesn’t understand how the Divine Race thinks.

Fei’er and the others had returned to Zhao Hai’s side. At this point, they were already treating him as the alliance leader.

After the group got into the ship and sat down, they saw Zhao Hai’s puzzled expression. Upon knowing why, Fei’er and the others were similarly confused.

After some time, Shan opened his mouth and said, “Maybe the Divine Race wanted us to come to the Taurus Continent. They would block the spatial rift and then trap us in here.”

Zhao Hai frowned, then he said, “That is impossible. The Divine Race knows about our strength. And with your three races, it would be impossible for them to surround us. Luring us deep into the continent would be an unwise decision.”

Fei’er knit his brows as he added, “I agree with mister. It might seem like the Divine Race had a lot of troops to face us, but mister might not have noticed that there were a lot of recruits among them. For these people, their emotions greatly affected their performance. After Lu Wei was eliminated and mister appeared with his ship, they were immediately routed. If this was the true Divine Race army, this would not happen.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he knew the tenacity of a regular Divine Race army. They have fought in the Accra Mountains for days without anybody abandoning the army. The soldiers this time were very quick to go back.

Fei’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Therefore, I think that the Divine Race didn’t have regular troops available right now. Those Divines we faced today might have been composed of civilians. This would explain their lack of will. If this is the case, then it would be unlikely for the Divine Race to lure us into the continent. That would just be a death wish.”

Yue frowned, then he said, “What about the Divines doing this intentionally? They sent such an army so that we could be confident when entering the Taurus Continent. Then they would deal with us.”

Zhao Hai also frowned, then he turned his head to the others and said, “Thinking about it at this time is useless. How about we just follow our original plan. You can leave the spatial rift to me. Fei’er, you go and send elite troops to contact your people. Go and see their current situation. Also, give a deadline to the person you’ve sent. If they don’t return by that time, then it means that your people are in dire state. What we need to do now is confront the Divines in Holy Light City. Let’s not think about going too deep.”

Fei’er and the others nodded. Then the Demon Dragon King, who had not yet spoken, said, “Mister, have you thought about the simplest possibility? Maybe before Lu Wei appeared, the Divine Race already took their people back. That is to say, Lu Wei only came here to deal with you. If this was the case, then that would be a reasonable explanation for this.”

As soon as he heard the Demon Dragon King, Zhao Hai stared blankly. He smiled bitterly and said, “It seems you’re right. It’s possible that we’ve been thinking about it too much. But in any case, we still cannot underestimate the Divine Race. Let’s go according to our plan. We must capture Holy Light city and make it our base.”

Fei’er and the others were also thinking that this was their safest choice. So they gave Zhao Hai an approving nod. Zhao Hai looked at the group and then said, “If there’s nothing else, then I won’t be holding you back for long. Demon Dragon, help me rebuild the defensive line. Have the Devil Legion guard the place as well, we need to ensure the safety of our retreat. I will leave magic cannons and javelins to you. Right we should study the Divine Race ballistas. I want to know the reason why they shoot much further.”

When he heard Zhao Hai, Fei’er smiled faintly and said, “Mister, there’s no need to think about the ballistas. The reason they shoot farther is simply because they used more advanced materials. The inhabitants aren’t the only strong people in the Divine Realm. The the plants and beasts are stronger as well. Because of this, it’s natural for the ballistas made here to be better than the ones in the Ark Continent.”

Zhao Hai thought about it and nodded, “So it’s like that. Haha. I’ve been thinking too much into things lately. It seems like we should remake our javelins with materials from the Divine Realm. This way, it’ll be better for us to deal with the Divine Race.”

The group gave a chuckle. Zhao Hai looked at them and then said, “You don’t have to worry about supplies, I’ll take care of it. Right, have your messenger ask if your people need anything. I’ll try my best to provide some help.”

Fei’er and the others nodded. Although their faces were calm, all of them knew that their people were having a hard time. This was especially true when it came to weapons. Meanwhile, Zhao Hai had a lot of good weapons. Magic cannons, javelins, and even defensive magic formations. All of these things are very useful against the Divine Race. If Zhao Hai could provide them, then their people would be more relaxed in their battles.

Zhao Hai smiled and then said, “Alright, you can go back to your armies. Also, arrange some alarms. We don’t want the Divine Race to sneak an attack. Although they are frightened, we cannot rule out the possibility of counter attack.”

After Fei’er and the others left, Zhao Hai went back to the Space with the Demon Dragon King. After they entered the Space, Zhao Hai looked at Demon Dragon King and said, “Demon Dragon, when you leave, go and take the sword carriage with you. I have this ship now, so the carriage is useless to me. You can use it to improve your combat power.”

The Demon Dragon King stared, then a smile couldn’t help but bloom on his face. The Sword Chariot was the Divine Race’s Domain Weapon. Zhao Hai had used it twice before, so the Demon Dragon King knew about its might. He didn’t expect Zhao Hai to give it to him.

Although the Demon Dragon King’s Domain was a black dragon, black dragons still had their claws, he could still hold the Domain Weapon. Having the sword carriage would surely amplify his strength. Later on, he wouldn’t be afraid of facing the Divine Race’s most powerful people.

The Demon Dragon King quickly bowed to Zhao Hai and said, “Mister, thank you very much!”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “It’s fine, don’t be too polite. Right, I’ll have some people sent to rebuild the defensive line. Go prepare the Devil Legion and then send them there. Have them be familiar with the weapons as soon as possible.”

The Demon Dragon King nodded. Then Zhao Hai waved as he took the sword carriage out and gave it to the Demon Dragon King. Actually, domain weapons didn’t need animals to pull them. As long as its owner provides energy, then they can move by themselves. However, this was more troublesome compared to having it pulled by magic beasts. Because of this, most people would have their domain weapons pulled by magic beasts.

Since he doesn’t need it anymore, Zhao Hai gave the domain weapon to Demon Dragon. It can be said that the Demon Dragon King was well prepared to receive it. He already had magic beasts pulling his black dragon carriage, so he didn’t need to pick his magic beasts. He can just command his dragons to pull the sword carriage instead.

Then Zhao Hai sent the Demon Dragon King to the Demon Space before he returned to the villa. Laura and the others were currently inspecting the pagoda and the ship. At this time, the pagoda and ship were in their smaller form. The crystal pagoda looked very beautiful, like a piece of art. The ship was also quite beautiful, but its ghastly vibe was something hard to like.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “How is it? Aren’t they nice?”

Laura nodded, then she said, “They’re nice. But I don’t like the ship. It’s gloomy, it makes me uncomfortable.”

Zhao Hai agreed, “That ship is quite a problem. I want it modified. How about we go to the processing machine. Let’s see if there’s a way to improve it.”

When Laura and the others heard this, they became excited. Then they pulled Zhao Hai to the processing machine.

Upon arriving at the processing machine, Zhao Hai placed the pagoda and the ship on the ground before he pushed the start button. The processing machine gave out a white light, then a voice was heard, “Items rich in Yin energy detected. The two items are compatible and can be combined. Requirements for the upgrade is moon profound water, river of earth fire, golden sand, tree of life, goldmetal wood, and 1 million gold coins. Needs 48 hours to complete. Host may choose the final appearance.”

Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t think that the processing could actually combine the two items. Moreover, it seems like he could choose its shape. This surprised Zhao Hai.

He immediately turned to the page with the item’s final form. There were numerous ships shown. But the common thing among them was that they were all very attractive.

Zhao Hai’s eyes couldn’t help but hurt upon seeing the multiple choices. After a while, he turned to Laura and the others and said, “Which one would you choose?”

As if in agreement, Laura and the others pointed at a picture of a ship. The ship looked very beautiful. It had a light colored hull with a pointed corner at front. It still had 18 decks, and it had a cabin with 9 floors. A flag was set up in front of the ship but the image was left blank. It seems like Zhao Hai was free to choose what flag to place there. Between the topmost deck and the cabin was another floor with a door. Behind the door was a circular pool. The pool’s pattern was like the Taiji figure. Half of it was water, the half was fire. Outside the taiji pool was the eight trigrams chart. Moreover, there were innumerable golden threads going out of it, merging throughout the ship. It looks like the pool was the one powering the ship.

Underneath the ship was water, which was just like waves of the sea. However, it surrounded the ship, clumped up and not flowing down.

Behind the ship were circular holes with flames blowing out from time to time.

Besides these things, there were also cannons on both sides of the ship. There were 64 cannons on each side, 128 cannons in total.

There were also carvings on the 18 layers of hell on the ship. Although they looked horrible, one could still look at it as some kind of unique art.

On the top deck of the ship were four bells, one for each angle. The little bells were transparent, they seemed to be made of crystal, looking very attractive.

Compared to the other ships, this ship was surely a step up, no wonder the women liked it. Zhao Hai smiled faintly and then said, “Good, then we’ll have this ship. As for the flag, the Buda Clan’s WIld Dragon Flag should be good. As for its name, do you have any suggestions?”

Laura thought for a moment and said, “I don’t have any problems with the flag. As for the name, since it has carvings of hell, how about we name it Hell King’s ship? What do you think?”

Zhao Hai looked at Lizzy and the others, who gave him a nod. Naturally, Zhao Hai wouldn’t decline this suggestion, so he nodded and said, “Alright, then this ship will be named Hell King’s ship.” Then Zhao Hai pressed the screen and chose the ship’s image.

The processing machine let out a bright light as it absorbed the tiny pagoda and the ship. Zhao Hai could also see his hard earned money being taken away. At the same time, profound moon water, the river of earth fire, golden sands, a goldmetal tree, and a tree of life also vanished from the Space.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but sigh upon seeing this as he said, “It took so much, let’s just hope that the result is worth it.’

When they heard Zhao Hai, the women couldn’t help but let out a tender smile.

Chapter 848: Having a Meal with the Demons

Zhao Hai and the others returned to the Space. Then after looking at the Divine Race for some time, Zhao Hai sighed and said, “Cai’er, arrange some undead to repair the defensive line. Also, have some people collect plants and animals from the Divine Realm. No matter what, we need to increase the plant reserves of the Space.” Cai’er nodded and then went on to take care of it. At this time, Zhao Hai suddenly feel his messenger fish move. He took a look at it and saw that it was connected to the Great Demon King.

Zhao Hai held his messenger fish and immediately said, “Your Majesty, do you need me for something?” Then the Great Demon King’s happy voice was heard, “Mister, all of the Demons had already move into the Space. Mister can now close the spatial rift. Also, I want to invite mister over for a feast. I know mister has a lot of things, but I want to ask you to taste the food of the Demon Realm.” Zhao Hai stared, he didn’t expect the Demons to move this quickly. Actually, the reason why the Demons were slow was because of the magic beasts. Now that the beast tide has passed, the Demons had little to worry about. This caused their speed to quicken.

Zhao Hai immediately gave his response, “Alright, I will certainly go. Your Majesty can rest assured.” Then he stored the messenger fish before looking at Laura and the others. He smiled faintly and said, “I wonder what the food of the Demon Realm tastes like.” Laura smiled as well and said, “I haven’t eaten their food before. So what do we do? Do we go now?” Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Yeah. Right, we need to prepare some gifts.” Zhao Hai’s gift wasn’t expensive, only some magic beasts and all sorts of wine.

Any race would like these things. Moreover, although they weren’t precious to Zhao Hai, they still held some value to the Demons.

The Space was currently rich with things. Although it lacked gold coins, it was only because they still haven’t emptied the warehouse. If they sold the things in the warehouse, then Zhao Hai  would definitely earn a load of money. However, there was only a small advantage in selling those things in the Space. And even if Zhao Hai wasn’t rich, he still had ample money to spend on things.

Not being able to purchase the ten magic backgrounds and 20 ordinary backgrounds was no big deal for Zhao Hai. Most of these places would only be used to grow plants and animals, and there was no need to rush it right now.

The reason why Zhao Hai wanted to upgrade the Space in the past was because he wanted to train God-ranks. But now, the need for God-ranks wasn’t as great as before. At this time, there were several millions of God-ranks in the Space. Also, there were some undead in the hell background who had broken through. Zhao Hai was in no need for additional God-ranks at this point.

After preparing his gifts, Zhao Hai led Laura and the others to the Demon Space. Upon arriving, Zhao Hai can see the Devil’s Chariot and Sword Carriage up in the air. Both of them were waiting for Zhao Hai.

When the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King saw Zhao Hai and his wives,they immediately went forward and gave a salute, “Mister, welcome!” Zhao Hai hastile returned the salute, “Your Majesty, Demon Dragon, you’re too polite. Right, let me introduce you to my wives….” The Great Demon King didn’t expect to see a Demon among Zhao Hai’s wives. He stared at Berry and then said, “i didn’t think mister would have a Demon as his wife. Madame, are you a Demon from the Demon Realm?” The Demon Dragon King forced a smile as he gave a reply, “Your Majesty, madame is someone we sent to guard the Demonic Abyss. I believe madame is named Berry?” Berry gave the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King a salute. Then she smiled faintly and said, “I have seen Your Majesty and the Demon Dragon King. I am indeed named Berry.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “You should know about the custom of the Succubus Clan. I broke Berry’s spiritual attack, so she took me as her husband. Hehe. Right, you have to thank Berry. If not for her, I wouldn’t have been confident in taking the Demons to the Space.”

When the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King heard this, they immediately gave Berry a salute. They were thankful to Berry. To the Demons, the Space was literally Heaven.

Berry was a clever woman, she understood that Zhao Hai only did this in order to elevate her face. Therefore, she didn’t say anything.

After exchanging their greetings, Zhao Hai said, “Alright, we shouldn’t be too formal here. Didn’t you invite me to a meal? Let’s go eat.” When the Great Demon King and Demon Dragon King heard this, they couldn’t help but chuckle. Then the Great Demon King said, “Alright, then let’s go down.”

Zhao Hai smiled, then he said, “I’ve brought some gifts as well. Here.” Then he took the magic beasts and liquor out.

Besides these, Zhao Hai also used this opportunity to give grain seeds and vegetable seeds. Also, he provided some methods of raising magic beasts. And lastly, there were methods of making liquor.

In the past, the Demons were living in the material-poor Demon Realm. Cultivating plants was mostly non existent in that plane. Moreover, most of the plants there were poisonous. Their seeds might be edible, but the plants themselves couldn’t be grown on one’s house, it was a potential hazard to those around it.

Naturally, the Great Demon King knew how important these things were to the Demons. He took a look at these things and then suddenly bowed to Zhao Hai, “I represent all the Demons in expressing our gratitude!” Zhao Hai quickly waved his hand and said, “It’s fine. These are things I ought to do. I got you into the Space. You have to treat your neighbors properly, right? There’s no need to be too polite” At this time, the Demon Dragon King suddenly said, “Mister, don’t you need some gold right now?” Zhao Hai stared, he looked puzzled at Demon Dragon as he asked, “Demon Dragon, what do you mean? Do you have a lot of gold?”

Demon Dragon forced a smile and said, “Mister, you might not know, but gold is completely useless in the Demon Realm. We have several gold ore deposits in the Demon Realm, and they are high-grade ores as well. We Demons only use gold to make our weapons look more terrifying. I seem to have heard that gold is very useful in the Ark Continent. If mister needs some gold, then Me and His Majesty can point some areas out for you.”

Zhao Hai gawked, then he turned to look at the Great Demon King. The Great Demon King smiled bitterly and said, “Mister, I forgot out it. Demon Dragon King is telling the truth. The Demon Realm has a lot of various ores. If mister needs them, we can give you their locations.”

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “Alright, that would be great. To be honest, I really need gold right now. How about this, I’ll get you a map of the Demon Realm tomorrow. You can just mark those places there and I’ll get them myself. I want everything!” When the Great Demon King heard this, he wasn’t offended, instead he said, “Alright, mister can rest assured. We will certainly mark everything, we won’t miss a spot.” Zhao Hai laughed once more before following the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King.

This place wasn’t the Great Demon King’s new palace, it was just a place where Demons had grouped up. There were no construction projects here, only Demons gathering around.

These Demons were the first soldiers to enter the Space. At this point, they had already settled their people. They only came here to greet Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai looked at everyone. Then he smiled faintly and said, “Everyone is here. It seems like you really want me to have a good feast. But with so many people, I’m afraid I won’t be able to eat everything.”

Contrary to what Zhao Hai imagined, the people didn’t laugh, everyone just stayed silent. Zhao Hai saw this and didn’t know what to do, he even felt a little embarrassed.

At this time, the Demons simultaneously knelt. Then the knocked their heads to the ground and loudly shouted, “Thank you, mister!” Then they knocked their heads once more and shouted, “Thank you, mister!”….

After knocking their heads nine times, they stopped. Zhao Hai looked at the Demons and couldn’t help but get teary eyed. He was moved by their action. He calmed himself down as he looked at the Demons and said, “Alright, everyone, don’t be too polite. Now that you’ve entered the Space, we’re already part of one family. Don’t be too respectful to me. Just be yourself, I’m just here to taste some dishes that you made.”

The Demons laughed and then prepared the food. At this time, Zhao Hai turned to the Great Demon King and the Demon Dragon King and said, “Next time, don’t let them do that. It scares me a lot.”

The Great Demon King smiled and said, “Everyone just wanted to express their gratitude. Moreover, I didn’t plan this thing, they did it themselves. I wouldn’t be able to stop them.” Zhao Hai smiled bitterly and didn’t say anything else. After the group found a place to sit down, Zhao Hai turned to the Great Demon King and said, “Your Majesty, I need you to take your devil’s chariot and help me in the next two days. I want to attack the Divine Race’s Holy Light City. However, the ship I just acquired was being refined and needs two days before I can use it. I’ll need to depend on you until that time.”